<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าเป็นทหารแห่งไม้กางเขน</thainame>
   <englishname>Am I a Soldier of the Cross</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าเป็นทหารแห่งไม้กางเขน เดินตามพระเยซูเจ้า  ไม่ควรกลัวที่จะเป็นพยาน หรืออายเมื่อออกพระนาม</verse1>
      <verse2>การไปสวรรค์นั้นไม่ใช่ง่าย อาจต้องลำบากเหนื่อยใจ   มีบางคนต้องสู้จนตัวตาย เขาจึงได้ความมีชัย</verse2>
      <verse3>เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 233 ข้าเป็นทหารแห่งไม้กางเขน จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ข้าเป็นทหารแห่งไม้กางเขน เดินตามพระเยซูเจ้า  ไม่ควรกลัวที่จะเป็นพยาน หรืออายเมื่อออกพระนาม  2. การไปสวรรค์นั้นไม่ใช่ง่าย อาจต้องลำบากเหนื่อยใจ   มีบางคนต้องสู้จนตัวตาย เขาจึงได้ความมีชัย</verse3>
      <verse4>ถ้าหวังมีชัย ข้าต้องต่อสู้ ขอพระองค์ช่วยชูแรง  ข้าเชื่อมั่นคงในพระเยซู ทรงช่วยให้ข้าเข้มแข็ง...</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Am I a soldier of the cross, A follower of the Lamb, And shall I fear to own His cause,Or blush to speak His Name?</verse1>
      <verse2>Must I be carried to the skies On flowery beds of ease, While others fought to win the prize, And sailed through bloody seas?</verse2>
      <verse3>For a dif­fer­ent ar­range­ment, see When the Bat­tle’s Over. Music: Ar­ling­ton, Thom­as A. Arne, 1762; ar­ranged by Ralph Har­ri­son in his Sac­red Har­mo­ny–A Col­lect­ion of Psalm­tunes, An­cient and Mo­dern (Lon­don: 1784) (Am I a Soldier of the Cross) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org Am I a soldier of the cross, A follower of the Lamb, And shall I fear to own His cause,Or blush to speak His Name? Must I be carried to the skies On flowery beds of ease, While others fought to win the prize, And sailed through bloody seas?</verse3>
      <verse4>Sure I must fight if I would reign; Increase my courage, Lord.I’ll bear the toil, endure the pain, Supported by Thy Word.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>
