<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ใครมีความทุกข์หนักอกอ่อนใจ</thainame>
   <englishname>Art Thou Weary, Art Thou Languid</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ใครมีความทุกข์หนักอกอ่อนใจ ไม่มีความสุขหรือ องค์พระเยซูเชิญมารับความสุขสำราญ</verse1>
      <verse2>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ใครมีความทุกข์หนักอกอ่อนใจ ไม่มีความสุขหรือ องค์พระเยซูเชิญมารับความสุขสำราญ</verse2>
      <verse3>ทรงมงกุฎอันรุ่งเรืองแวววาม เยี่ยงกษัตริย์หรือไม่ ทรงมงกุฎนั้นซึ่งสานด้วยหนามน่าอับอาย</verse3>
      <verse4>ถ้ายังคงติดตามพระองค์ไปที่สุดได้อะไร ได้พ้นทุกข์เหนื่อยยากหายไปและพ้นความตาย</verse4>
      <verse5>ถ้าขอให้พระองค์ต้อนรับเราทรงยอมรับหรือไม่ ไม่ว่าโลกและฟ้าสิ้นสูญไปทรงช่วยได้...</verse5>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Art thou weary, art thou languid, Art thou sore distressed? “Come to Me,” saith One, “and coming,Be at rest.”</verse1>
      <verse2>Neale gave it the unusual title Idiomela, in the Week of the First Oblique Tone. However, Neale later said these lyrics contained little of the original Greek version. This hymn was sung in the 1940 movie Our Town, which was nominated for several Academy Awards. Stephanos Henry W. Baker, 1868 เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 209 ใครมีความทุกข์หนักอกอ่อนใจ  (Art Thou Weary, Art Thou Languid) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org Art thou weary, art thou languid, Art thou sore distressed? “Come to Me,” saith One, “and coming,Be at rest.”</verse2>
      <verse3>Hath He diadem, as monarch, That His brow adorns? Yes, a crown in very surety, But of thorns.</verse3>
      <verse4>If I still hold closely to Him, What hath He at last? Sorrow vanquished, labor ended, Jordan passed.</verse4>
      <verse5>If I ask Him to receive me, Will He say me nay? Not till earth and not till Heaven Pass away.</verse5>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </chord>
</song>
