<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ภาชนะว่างเปล่าเอามา</thainame>
   <englishname>Bring Your Vessels,Not a Few</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ปรารถนาจะเติมให้เต็มล้น  ด้วยพระพรแห่งพระเจ้าหรือ ทั้งเช้าค่ำอิ่มหนำปรีดา พระสัญญาที่พระบิดาของเรา  ตรัสไว้จงยึดให้มั่น เช่นในกาลสมัยโบราณ</verse1>
      <verse2>ภาชนะเรือนดินชำระ ด้วยพระโลหิตของพระเยซู ใจเหือดแห้งกระหายจงมา  พากันถ่อมใจกราบลง  ตรงพระบาทาหน้าพระที่นั่งนั้น จนพระวิญญาณทรงลงมา</verse2>
      <verse3>เหมือนอย่างน้ำมันที่จะหลั่งไหล  และไม่รู้จักหมดสิ้นลง ความรักที่ไม่รู้ปรวนแปร ตามพระสัญญาพระเยซูจะโปรด ประทานพระวิญญาณมา จนกว่าใจทั้งหลายจะเต็ม</verse3>
      <chorus>พระองค์ทรงเติมดวงใจให้ล้นด้วยความยินดี  เหมือนอย่างที่พระเจ้าสั่งให้  ภาชนะว่างเปล่า เอามา  จะทรงเติมดวงใจให้ล้นหลั่งไหลในวันนี้  ด้วยฤทธีและพระวิญญาณ</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Are you longing for the fullness  Of the blessing of the Lord  In your heart and life today? Claim the promise of your Father;  Come according to His Word, In the blessèd, old time way.</verse1>
      <verse2>Bring your empty earthen vessels, Clean through Jesus' precious blood. Come, ye needy, one and all;  And in human consecration Wait before the throne of God Till the Holy Ghost shall fall.</verse2>
      <verse3>Like the cruse of oil unfailing  Is His grace forevermore, And His love unchanging still;  And according to His promise, With the Holy Ghost and power  He will every vessel fill.</verse3>
      <chorus>He will fill your heart today to overflowing   As the Lord commandeth you,  &quot;Bring your vessels, not a few.&quot;  He will fill your heart today to overflowing   With the Holy Ghost and power.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
