<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>พระคริสต์มาในไม่ช้า</thainame>
   <englishname>Christ Is Coming</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ยามแสงทองส่องฟ้าสว่างแล้ว และความมืดกำลังศูนย์หาย ค่ายประตูใหญ่ในสวรรค์เปิด ข่าวประเสริฐเผยแพร่กระจาย แล้วมีเสียงกระซิบที่ใจข้าฯ และชาวฟ้าพากันร้องเพลง เนื้อเพลงนั้นสำคัญแก่ตัวข้าฯ คือพระคริสต์มาเป็นราชา เนื้อเพลงนั้นสำคัญแก่ตัวข้าฯ คือพระคริสต์มาเป็นราชา</verse1>
      <verse2>บางเวลาเหมือนเสียงพระบาทา ทรงดำเนินมาอยู่เคียงข้าง แม้หนทางข้างหน้ามืดมัวแต่ พระเยซูเป็นแสงสว่าง จงร้องเพลงยินดีด้วยจริงใจ เหมือนได้ร้องกับเหล่าเทวา จงเตรียมตัวเพราะจวนหมดเวลา แล้วพระคริสต์มาครองโลกา จงเตรียมตัวเพราะจวนหมดเวลา แล้วพระคริสต์มาครองโลกา</verse2>
      <verse3>คอยพระองค์เป็นเวลาช้านาน จะปรากฎแก่เราไม่ช้า แล้วความบาปความโศกเศร้าศูนย์หาย ข้าฯคอยท่าพระองค์จะมา และเดี๋ยวนี้จวนหมดเวลาแล้ว เมืองสวรรค์จะลอยลงมา เป็นความหวังแน่นอนแก่ใจข้าฯ คือพระคริสต์มาในไม่ช้า เป็นความหวังแน่นอนแก่ใจข้าฯ คือพระคริสต์มาในไม่ช้า.</verse3>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>In the glow of early morning, In the solemn hush of night; Down from Heaven’s open portals, Steals a messenger of light, Whispering sweetly to my spirit, While the hosts of Heaven sing: This the wondrous thrilling story: Christ is comingóChrist my King. This the wondrous thrilling story: Christ is coming Christ my King.</verse1>
      <verse2>Oft methinks I hear His footsteps, Stealing down the paths of time; And the future dark with shadows, Brightens with this hope sublime. Sound the soul inspiring anthem; Angel hosts, your harps attune; Earth’s long night is almost over, Christ is coming coming soon. Earth’s long night is almost over, Christ is coming coming soon.</verse2>
      <verse3>Long we’ve waited, blest Redeemer, Waited for the first bright ray Of the morn when sin and sorrow At Thy presence flee away; But our vigil’s nearly over; Hope of Heav’n, oh, priceless boon! In the east the glow appearing, Christ is coming coming soon. In the east the glow appearing, Christ is coming coming soon.</verse3>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </chord>
</song>