<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ผู้ลำบากเหน็ดเหนื่อย</thainame>
   <englishname>Come unto Me, Ye Weary</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ผู้ลำบากเหน็ดเหนื่อยมาเถิด เราช่วยหายเหนื่อยเดี๋ยวนี้” นี่คือดำรัสพระเยซู ตรัสแก่ผู้ถูกกดขี่ บอกเรื่องยินดีน่าชื่นใจ ทรงยกบาปให้อภัย ความสุขเช่นนี้ไม่เสื่อมคลาย ทรงรักท่านจนสุดปลาย  2 “ผู้ที่หลงจงมาหาเรา ท่านจะรับความสว่าง” พระสุรเสียงแห่งความรัก จักบอกให้ท่านรู้ทาง ดวงใจซึ่งเต็มด้วยความโศก วิญญาณหลงโลกต้องตาย บัดนี้ได้รับความชื่นใจ เพราะจิตสว่างสบาย  3. ผู้อ่อนเปลี้ยเพลียใจเชิญมา เราให้ชีวาเป็นอยู่” พระสุรเสียงพระเยซู หนุนใจให้ท่านต่อสู้ ศัตรูเข้มแข็งและร้ายกาจ เด็ดขาดต่อสู้อยู่นาน แต่องค์พระคริสต์ทรงฤทธิ์เดช ไม่มีผู้ใดต้านทาน    4. “ผู้ใดที่เข้ามาหาเรา จะไม่ทอดทิ้งเขาเลย” เสียงเชิญของพระเยซูเจ้า เรียกท่านอย่าได้ทำเฉย พระเยซูทรงร้องเชิญให้บรรดาคนบาปกลับใจ พระองค์ประทานชีวิตใหม่ โดยไม่คิดค่าใดๆ</verse1>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>&quot;Come unto Me, ye weary, And I will give you rest.&quot; O blessed voice of Jesus, Which comes to hearts oppressed! It tells of benediction, Of pardon, grace, and peace, Of joy that hath no ending, Of love that cannot cease.  &quot;Come unto Me, ye wand'rers, And I will give you light.&quot; 0 loving voice of Jesus, Which comes to cheer the night! Our hearts were filled with sadness, And we had lost our way; But Thou hast brought us gladness And songs at break of day. &quot;Come unto Me, ye fainting, And I will give you life.&quot; 0 cheering voice of Jesus, Which comes to aid our strife! The foe is stern and eager, The fight is fierce and long; But Thou hast made us mighty And stronger than the strong.  &quot;And whosoever cometh, I will not cast him out.&quot; O patient love of Jesus, Which drives away our doubt, Which, though we be unworthy Of love so great and free, Invites us very sinners To come, dear Lord, to Thee!</verse1>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
   </chord>
</song>
