<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ตามไป ตามไป</thainame>
   <englishname>Follow On</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ไปกับผู้ช่วยขึ้นเขาลงห้วยข้าฯก็ไม่กลัว แม้ฝ่าอันตราย ข้าฯก็เต็มใจไปจนทั่ว เมื่อนำข้าฯไปที่ใด ข้าฯก็เต็มใจไปที่นั่น เดินตามรอยพระบาทไปจนถึงเมืองสวรรค์</verse1>
      <verse2>ไปกับผู้ช่วยขึ้นเขาลงห้วย ข้าฯก็ไม่กลัว แม้พายุจัดน้ำพัดเชี่ยว ข้าฯเที่ยวไปจนทั่ว เมื่อจูงด้วยพระหัตถ์ ข้าฯก็ไม่พลัดหลงทางไปไกล อันตรายไม่กล้ำกราย เมื่อผู้ช่วยอยู่ใกล้</verse2>
      <verse3>แม้ว่ารบในเหวลึก หรือสู้ศึกบนเขาสูง เต็มใจมอบชีวิตให้พระเยซูเป็นผู้จูง พระองค์ทรงนำข้าฯในทางที่ทรงเคยดำเนินนั้น เพื่อเข้าเฝ้าพระเจ้าพร้อมบรรดาผู้เลือกสรร</verse3>
      <chorus>: ตามไป ตามไป ข้าฯจะตามพระเยซู ทั่วทุกแห่ง ทุกตำบล ข้าฯตามพระองค์ไป ตามไป ตามไป ข้าฯจะตามพระเยซู พระองค์นำไปไหน จะเดินตามพระองค์ไป</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Down in the valley with my Savior I would go, Where the flowers are blooming and the sweet waters flow; Everywhere He leads me I would follow, follow on, Walking in His footsteps till the crown be won.</verse1>
      <verse2>Down in the valley with my Savior I would go, Where the storms are sweeping and the dark waters flow; With His hand to lead me I will never, never fear, Danger cannot fright me if my Lord is near.</verse2>
      <verse3>Down in the valley, or upon the mountain steep, Close beside my Savior would my soul ever keep; He will lead me safely in the path that He has trod, Up to where they gather on the hills of God.</verse3>
      <chorus>Follow! follow! I would follow Jesus! Anywhere, everywhere, I would follow on! Follow! follow! I would follow Jesus! Everywhere He leads me I would follow on!</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>