<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก</thainame>
   <englishname>God Be with You</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก เฝ้ารักษาปกป้องประคองท่าน ทรงบันดาลแต่สุขเกษมสานต์ ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก</verse1>
      <verse2>ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก ขอพระองค์ปกป้องคุ้มครองท่าน และทรงโปรดทุกวันมีอาหาร ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก</verse2>
      <verse3>ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก ถ้าความบาปรบกวนท่านมากมาย ขอพระหัตถ์พระองค์ทรงคุ้มภัย ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก</verse3>
      <verse4>ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก ให้ความรักดำรงทุกเวลา แม้นความตายจะมาอยู่ตรงหน้า ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก</verse4>
      <chorus>จนเราเจอ จนเราเจอ จนเราเจอที่บาทพระเจ้า จนเราเจอ จนเราเจอ ขอพระเจ้าอยู่ด้วยจนเจอกันอีก</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>God be with you till we meet again; By His counsels guide, uphold you, With His sheep securely fold you; God be with you till we meet again.</verse1>
      <verse2>God be with you till we meet again; Neath His wings protecting hide you; Daily manna still provide you; God be with you till we meet again.</verse2>
      <verse3>God be with you till we meet again; When life’s perils thick confound you; Put His arms unfailing round you; God be with you till we meet again.</verse3>
      <verse4>God be with you till we meet again; Keep love’s banner floating o’er you, Strike death’s threatening wave before you; God be with you till we meet again.</verse4>
      <chorus>Till we meet, till we meet, Till we meet at Jesus’ feet; Till we meet, till we meet, God be with you till we meet again.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
