<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>

<thainame>พระเจ้าดีตลอดเวลา</thainame>
<englishname>God is Good All The Time</englishname>
<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
<order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,chorus,chorus2,verse5</order>

<thai>
    <verse1>พระเจ้าดี ตลอดเวลา ใส่บทเพลงสรรเสริญ อยู่ในใจของฉัน</verse1>
    <verse2>พระเจ้าดี ตลอดเวลา ในราตรีที่มืด แสงพระองค์ฉาย พระเจ้าดี พระเจ้าดี ตลอดเวลา</verse2>
    <verse3>ก่อนเป็นคนบาป ไม่มีค่าเลย เพื่อพวกเราพระองค์ยอมตาย เจิมเราด้วยไฟพระวิญญาณบริสุทธิ์</verse3>
    <verse4>เราจึงยืนยันและเป็นพยาน ความรักพระองค์ เป็นนิรันดร์กาล และพระเมตตาไม่เคยหมดสิ้นไป</verse4>
    <verse5>ถึงแม้ฉันจะไม่เข้าใจ ตลอดแผนที่พระองค์ให้ ชีวิตอยู่ในพระองค์ และด้วยดวงตาแห่งความเชื่อจะได้เห็นชัดเจน</verse5>
    <chorus>หากเราเดินผ่านหุบเขามืดมน และปัญหามารุมล้อมเรา อย่าได้กลัว พระองค์จะนำเรา และรักษาเราให้มั่นคง</chorus>
    <chorus2>พระองค์สัญญา จะไม่ทอดทิ้งเรา หรือเพิกเฉยเรา และพระคำพระองค์นั้นจริง</chorus2>
</thai>

<english>
    <verse1>God is good all the time. He put a song of praise in. this heart of mine.</verse1>
    <verse2>God is good all the time. Through the darkest night, His light will shine. God is good, God is good. all the time.</verse2>
    <verse3>We were sinners so unworthy. Still for us He chose to die. Filled us with His Holy Spirit.</verse3>
    <verse4>Now we can stand and testify. That His love is everlasting. And His mercies they will never end.</verse4>
    <verse5>Though I may not understand all the plans You have for me. My life is in your hands. And through the eyes of faith. I can clearly see.</verse5>
    <chorus>If you’re walking through the valley. There are shadows all around. Do not fear He will guide you. He will keep you safe and sound.</chorus>
<chorus2>'Causes He's promised to never leave you. Nor forsake you and His Word is true.</chorus2>
</english>
    
<mienthai>
    
</mienthai>

<chord>
    <verse1></verse1>
    <verse2></verse2>
    <verse3></verse3>
    <verse4></verse4>
    <verse5></verse5>
    <chorus></chorus>
        <chorus2></chorus2>
</chord>

</song>