<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>พระคุณล้ำเลิศของพระเยซูเจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>Grace Greater Than Our Sin</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>พระคุณล้ำเลิศของพระเยซูเจ้า  และพระคุณนั้นอยู่เหนือบาปของเรา    ที่ไม้กางเขนพระองค์ถูกตรึงตาย เพื่อเรารอดได้ด้วยพระโลหิตไถ่</verse1>
      <verse2>เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 137 พระคุณล้ำเลิศของพระเยซูเจ้า จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.พระคุณล้ำเลิศของพระเยซูเจ้า  และพระคุณนั้นอยู่เหนือบาปของเรา    ที่ไม้กางเขนพระองค์ถูกตรึงตาย เพื่อเรารอดได้ด้วยพระโลหิตไถ่   พระคุณ  พระคุณ   เป็นอำนาจซึ่งล้างใจให้สะอาด พระคุณ  พระคุณ  เป็นพระคุณใหญ่หลวงมีฤทธิ์อำนาจ</verse2>
      <verse3>ความบาปมืดมิด  ใครจะปิดไว้ได้ อะไรสามารถล้างบาปเราให้หาย มีแต่โลหิตของพระเยซูเจ้า ผู้ทรงพระชนม์อยู่เป็นนิจช่วยเรา</verse3>
      <chorus>พระคุณ  พระคุณ   เป็นอำนาจซึ่งล้างใจให้สะอาด พระคุณ  พระคุณ  เป็นพระคุณใหญ่หลวงมีฤทธิ์อำนาจ</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Marvelous grace of our loving Lord, Grace that exceeds our sin and our guilt! Yonder on Calvary’s mount outpoured, There where the blood of the Lamb was spilled.</verse1>
      <verse2>Music: Daniel B. Towner, 1910 (Grace Greater Than Our Sin) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org Marvelous grace of our loving Lord, Grace that exceeds our sin and our guilt! Yonder on Calvary’s mount outpoured, There where the blood of the Lamb was spilled. ร้องรับRefrain Grace, grace, God’s grace, Grace that will pardon and cleanse within; Grace, grace, God’s grace, Grace that is greater than all our sin.</verse2>
      <verse3>Dark is the stain that we cannot hide. What can avail to wash it away? Look! There is flowing a crimson tide, Brighter than snow you may be today.</verse3>
      <chorus>Grace, grace, God’s grace, Grace that will pardon and cleanse within; Grace, grace, God’s grace, Grace that is greater than all our sin.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
