<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ผู้เป็น</thainame>
   <englishname>He Lives</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าฯปฏิบัติพระผู้ช่วย ด้วยทรงพระชนม์เป็นอยู่ ข้าฯรู้ว่าพระองค์ทรงมี ชีวิตเป็นอยู่เรื่อยไป ข้าเห็นพระคุณพระเยซู ได้ยินเสียงหนุนน้ำใจ เมื่อข้าฯมีความทุกข์ครั้งใด พระองค์อยู่ใกล้</verse1>
      <verse2>แลไปในโลกล้อมรอบข้าฯ พระองค์ทรงคุ้มครองอยู่ แม้ข้าฯจะเหนื่อยแสนเมื่อยล้า แต่ข้าฯไม่ยอมท้อถอย ข้าฯรู้พระองค์ทรงนำหน้าตามทางชีวาน้อยใหญ่ พระเยซูจะเสด็จมา ในวันสุดท้าย</verse2>
      <verse3>ชื่นใจยินดีโอ้คริสเตียน จงเพียรร้องเพลงสรรเสริญ สรรเสริญว่า ฮาเลลูยา แด่พระเยซูผู้ไถ่ ทรงเป็นความหวังของผู้หา เมตตาแก่คนทั่วไป ไม่มีใครเหมือนพระเยซู พระผู้ยิ่งใหญ่</verse3>
      <chorus>ผู้เป็น ผู้เป็น คือองค์พระเยซูเจ้า  ทรงเดิน และตรัส สถิตกับเรา ทรงนำทางแคบชีวี ทรงเป็น ทรงพลี ประทานชีวิตนิรันดร์ ท่านถามว่า ข้าฯรู้ได้อย่างไรข้าฯรู้ เพราะอยู่ในใจ</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>I serve a risen Savior, He's in the world today;  I know that He is living, whatever men may say;  I see His hand of mercy, I hear His voice of cheer  And just the time I need Him He's always near.</verse1>
      <verse2>In all the world around me I see His loving care,  And though my heart grows weary, I never will despair  I know that He is leading, Through all the stormy blast; The day of His appearing will come at last.</verse2>
      <verse3>Rejoice, rejoice, O Christian, lift up your voice and sing,  Eternal Hallelujahs to Jesus Christ the King!  The hope of all who seek Him, the help of all who find,  None other is so loving, so good and kind.</verse3>
      <chorus>He lives, He lives, Christ Jesus lives today! He walks with me and talks with mealong life's narrow way. He lives, He lives, salvation to impart! You ask me how I know He lives? He lives within my heart.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
