<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เดี๋ยวนี้มีพระเจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>Himself</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ครั้งหนึ่งข้าฯอยากได้พร เดี๋ยวนี้ได้พระเจ้า ครั้งหนึ่งพึ่งใจตัวเอง เดี๋ยวนี้พึ่งพระธรรม ครั้งหนึ่งต้องการสิ่งของ เดี๋ยวนี้มีพระเจ้า ครั้งหนึ่งอยากแต่หายป่วย เดี๋ยวนี้ได้พระองค์  ร้องรับ เดี๋ยวนี้ข้าฯจะร้องเพลง สรรเสริญสาธุการ สารพัดที่มีอยู่ เป็นของพระองค์ประทาน</verse1>
      <verse2>ครั้งหนึ่งวางแต่โครงการ เดี๋ยวนี้อธิษฐาน ครั้งหนึ่งเป็นห่วงกังวล  เดี๋ยวนี้ทรงคุ้มครอง ครั้งหนึ่งตามอำเภอใจ เดี๋ยวนี้ตามพระองค์ ครั้งหนึ่งชอบแต่ทูลขอ เดี๋ยวนี้ขอบพระคุณ</verse2>
      <verse3>ครั้งหนึ่งข้าฯพึ่งความดี เดี๋ยวนี้พึ่งพระเจ้า ครั้งหนึ่งข้าฯใช้พระองค์ เดี๋ยวนี้ทรงใช้ข้าฯ ครั้งหนึ่งข้าฯต้องการฤทธิ์ เดี๋ยวนี้มีพระคริสต์ ครั้งหนึ่งทำเพื่อตนเอง เดี๋ยวนี้เพื่อพระเจ้า</verse3>
      <verse4>ครั้งหนึ่งมีแต่ความหวัง เดี๋ยวนี้รอดจริงจัง ครั้งหนึ่งความเชื่อจวนดับ เดี๋ยวนี้กลับแจ่มใส  ครั้งหนึ่งคอยท่าความตาย เดี๋ยวนี้มีชีวิต เดี๋ยวนี้ข้าได้รอดแน่ มั่นคงในพระคริสต์</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Once it was the blessing, Now it is the Lord; Once it was the feeling, Now it is His Word.  Once His gifts I wanted, Now the Giver own; Once I sought for healing, Now Himself alone. All in all forever, Only Christ I'll sing; Everything is in Christ, And Christ is everything.</verse1>
      <verse2>Once 'twas busy planning, Now 'tis trustful prayer  Once 'twas anxious caring, Now He has the care. Once 'twas what I wanted, Now what Jesus says;  Once 'twas constant asking, Now 'tis ceaseless praise.</verse2>
      <verse3>Once it was my working, His it hence shall be;  Once I tried to use Him, Now He uses me.  Once the power I wanted, Now the Mighty One;  Once for self I labored, Now for Him alone.</verse3>
      <verse4>Once I hoped in Jesus, Now I know He's mine;  Once my lamps were dying, Now they brightly shine  Once for death I waited, Now His coming hail;  And my hopes are anchored, Safe within the vail</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>
