<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าจะว้าเหว่ได้อย่างไร</thainame>
   <englishname>How can I be lonely</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>แม้ทางยากลำบากเพียงไรพระคริสต์ทรงไปกับข้า พระเยซูทรงช่วยประคองปกป้องอยู่ทุกเวลา ข้าจะว้าเหว่ได้อย่างไรเมื่อพระองค์ทรงอยู่ใกล้</verse1>
      <verse2>ยามเมื่อข้าหนักใจหนักกายข้าติดตามพระองค์ไป และพระเจ้าประทับอยู่ใกล้ หนุนกำลังประทังกาย ถึงจะต้องแบกไม้กางเขน ทนทุกข์ข้าก็มีชัย</verse2>
      <verse3>ชีวิตหนุ่มสาวเหมือนยามเช้าเช่นท้องฟ้ายังแจ่มใส ครั้นมัชฌิมวัยเหมือนเที่ยงบ่ายมักมีทุกข์และโรคภัย ยามชราท้องฟ้ามืดมัว ดูน่ากลัวไม่เริงใจ</verse3>
      <chorus>เมื่อพระเยซูอยู่ใกล้  ข้าเปลี่ยวเปล่าอย่างไรได้ พระองค์ทรงเป็นเพื่อนซึ่งคอยเตือนและหนุนใจ ชีวิตข้าไม่น่าเบื่อ แม้เมื่อมีทุกข์มากมาย</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>One is walking with me over life's uneven way, Constantly supporting me each moment of the day; How can I be lonely when such fellowship is mine, เป็นเพื่อนที่ดีตลอดไปWith my blessed Lord divine!</verse1>
      <verse2>Days may bring their burdens and their trials as I go, But my Lord is near me and helps them lighter grow; Life may have its crosses, or its losses, or increase, เพราะพระองค์ให้ข้าพ้นภัยJesus meets them all with peace.</verse2>
      <verse3>In life's rosy morning when the skies above are clear, In its noontide hours with many cares and problems near, Or when evening shadows fall at closing of my day แต่พระเยซูทรงอยู่ใกล้Jesus will be there always.</verse3>
      <chorus>How can I be lonely when I've Jesus only To be my companion and unfailing guide? Why should I be weary, or my path seem dreary,  เพราะพระองค์สถิตอยู่ใกล้When He's walking by my side?</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>