<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>

<thainame>พระเจ้าทรงยิ่งใหญ่</thainame>
<englishname>How Great Is Our God</englishname>
<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
<order>verse1,verse1-2,chorus,verse2,verse2-2,chorus,bridge,chorus</order>

<thai>
    <verse1>พระองค์งดงามตระการ ควรพระบารมี ให้เราร่วมกันยินดี ให้เราร่วมกันยินดี</verse1>
    <verse1-2>พระองค์เป็นความสว่าง และความมืดอันตรธาน สะท้านด้วยเสียงพระองค์ สะท้านด้วยเสียงพระองค์</verse1-2>

    <verse2>พระองค์ผู้ทรงครอบครอง และทรงเหนือกาลเวลา ทรงเป็นเบื้องต้นเบื้องปลาย ทรงเป็นเบื้องต้นเบื้องปลาย</verse2>
    <verse2-2>พระบิดา พระวิญญาณ พระเยซูพระบุตร ผู้ทรงเป็นจอมราชา ผู้ทรงเป็นจอมราชา</verse2-2>

    <bridge>พระนามเหนือนามทั้งปวง ควรคู่คำสรรเสริญ จิตใจฉันร้อง พระเจ้าทรงยิ่งใหญ่</bridge>
    <chorus>พระเจ้าทรงยิ่งใหญ่ ร้องสรรเสริญ พระเจ้าทรงยิ่งใหญ่ ร้องสรรเสริญ พระเจ้า พระเจ้า ทรงยิ่งใหญ่</chorus>
</thai>

<english>
    <verse1>The splendor of a King, clothed in majesty. Let all the earth rejoice. All the earth rejoice.</verse1>
    <verse1-2>He wraps himself in Light, and darkness tries to hide. And trembles at His voice. Trembles at His voice.</verse1-2>

    <verse2>Age to age He stands. And time is in His hands. Beginning and the end. Beginning and the end.</verse2>
    <verse2-2>The Godhead Three in One. Father Spirit Son. The Lion and the Lamb. The Lion and the Lamb.</verse2-2>

   <bridge>Name above all names. Worthy of our praise. My heart will sing. How great is our God.</bridge>
    <chorus>How great is our God, sing with me. How great is our God, and all will see. How great, how great is our God.</chorus>
</english>
    
<mienthai>
    <verse1></verse1>
    <verse2></verse2>
    <verse3></verse3>
    <verse4></verse4>
    <verse5></verse5>
    <chorus></chorus>
</mienthai>

<chord>
    <verse1>G D/ F# Em7 Cmaj7 D G D/ F# Em7 Cmaj7 D</verse1>
    <verse2>G D/ F# Em7 Cmaj7 D G D/ F# Em7 Cmaj7 D</verse2>
    <bridge>G/ D Cmaj7 D G</bridge>
    <chorus>G D/ F# Em7 Cmaj7 D G</chorus>
</chord>

</song>