<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู</thainame>
   <englishname>I am Trusting Thee</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู ผู้ประทานความรอด ข้าวางใจพระเยซูผู้รักข้าตลอด</verse1>
      <verse2>ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู ผู้อภัยบาปข้า ข้ารอดโดยพระคุณและความรักความเมตตา</verse2>
      <verse3>ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู ให้เป็นผู้นำทาง เพราะพระองค์ไม่เคยทอดทิ้ง แต่เดินเคียงข้าง</verse3>
      <verse4>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู ผู้ประทานความรอด ข้าวางใจพระเยซูผู้รักข้าตลอด  2.ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู ผู้อภัยบาปข้า ข้ารอดโดยพระคุณและความรักความเมตตา  3.ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู ให้เป็นผู้นำทาง เพราะพระองค์ไม่เคยทอดทิ้ง แต่เดินเคียงข้าง</verse4>
      <verse5>ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู ผู้คุ้มอันตราย ทรงอยู่ด้วยแม้ว่าโลกนี้จะสูญสลาย...</verse5>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>I am Trusting Thee, Lord Jesus; Trusting only Thee, Trusting Thee for full salvation,Great and free.</verse1>
      <verse2>I am trusting Thee for pardon; At Thy feet I bow, For Thy grace and tender mercy, Trusting now,</verse2>
      <verse3>I am Trusting Thee to guide me. Thou alone shalt lead; Every day and hour supplying all my need.</verse3>
      <verse4>She wrote the words at Ormont Dessons, Switzerland, and they were published in Loyal Responses in 1878. This is said to have been Havergal’s favorite hymn; it was found in her pocket Bible after her death. Music: Bullinger Ethelbert W. Bullinger, 1874 เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่  153 ข้าจะวางใจองค์พระเยซู  (I am Trusting Thee) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org I am Trusting Thee, Lord Jesus; Trusting only Thee, Trusting Thee for full salvation,Great and free. I am trusting Thee for pardon; At Thy feet I bow, For Thy grace and tender mercy, Trusting now, I am Trusting Thee to guide me. Thou alone shalt lead; Every day and hour supplying all my need.</verse4>
      <verse5>I am trusting Thee, Lord Jesus; Never let me fall. I am trusting Thee forever ,and for all.</verse5>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </chord>
</song>
