<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เราสู้ยอมตายเพื่อท่าน</thainame>
   <englishname>I Gave My Life for Thee</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>เราสู้ยอมตายเพื่อท่าน โลหิตประเสริฐหลั่งไหล เพื่อล้างชำระวิญญาณ ไถ่โทษให้เกิดใจใหม่ เราพลีชีวิตไม่คิดเสียดาย ท่านมีสิ่งใดถวาย เราพลีชีวิตไม่คิดเสียดาย ท่านมีสิ่งใดถวาย</verse1>
      <verse2>ปราสาทแห่งพระบิดา บัลลังก์รุ่งเรืองของเรา สู้ทิ้งมาสู่โลกา  รับทุกข์ลำบากเปลี่ยวเปล่า เราทิ้งยศศักดิ์ทั้งหมดสูญเปล่า ท่านทิ้งอะไรเพื่อเรา เราทิ้งยศศักดิ์ทั้งหมดสูญเปล่า ท่านทิ้งอะไรเพื่อเรา</verse2>
      <verse3>เราสู้ทนทุกข์แรงร้าย เหลือที่จะพรรณนา ทนความราวีจนตาย ให้ท่านรอดภัยนานา  เพื่อท่านเราทนความอายเหลือกล่าว ท่านทนอะไรเพื่อเรา เพื่อท่านเราทนความอายเหลือกล่าว ท่านทนอะไรเพื่อเรา</verse3>
      <verse4>เรานำของดีลงมา จากเมืองสวรรค์เบื้องบน เรานำความรักความรอด และการยกโทษโปรดชน เรานำของดีมายื่นแจกจ่าย ท่านยื่นสิ่งใดถวาย เรานำของดีมายื่นแจกจ่าย ท่านยื่นสิ่งใดถวาย.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>I gave My life for thee, My precious blood I shed, That thou might ransomed be, and raised up from the dead I gave, I gave My life for thee, what hast thou given for Me? I gave, I gave My life for thee, what hast thou given for Me?</verse1>
      <verse2>My Father’s house of light,  My glory circled throne I left for earthly night,  for wanderings sad and lone; I left, I left it all for thee, hast thou left aught for Me? I left, I left it all for thee, hast thou left aught for Me?</verse2>
      <verse3>I suffered much for thee,  more than thy tongue can tell, Of bitterest agony,  to rescue thee from hell. I’ve borne, I’ve borne it all for thee, what hast thou borne for Me? I’ve borne, I’ve borne it all for thee, what hast thou borne for Me?</verse3>
      <verse4>And I have brought to thee, down from My home above, Salvation full and free, My pardon and My love; I bring, I bring rich gifts to thee, what hast thou brought to Me? I bring, I bring rich gifts to thee, what hast thou brought to Me?</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>
