<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เต็มใจไปทุกแห่ง</thainame>
   <englishname>I’ll Go Where You Want Me to go</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>อาจไม่ใช่การปีนขึ้นยอดภูเขา หรือข้ามทะเลผ่านคลื่นใหญ่ อาจไม่ใช่ที่สนามรบแนวหน้า ซึ่งทรงต้องการให้ข้าฯไป  แต่ถ้าพระองค์ตรัสเบาๆให้ข้าฯ ไปในที่ข้าฯไม่เคยไป ข้าฯก็จะตอบว่า “พระองค์เจ้าข้าฯ ให้ไปที่ไหน ข้าฯเต็มใจไป”</verse1>
      <verse2>บางทีอาจพบคนทำบาปหลงทาง พระองค์ทรงใช้ให้นำมา โปรดเป็นผู้นำทางชีวิตของข้าฯ เพราะทางนั้นมืดมัวนักหนา ยินดีเดินตามถ้าพระองค์ทรงนำ แม้ทางนั้นลำบากยากครัน ปากข้าฯจะพูดพระธรรมตามบัญชา สั่งว่าอย่างไร จะพูดอย่างนั้น</verse2>
      <verse3>แม้โลกนี้เป็นที่กว้างใหญ่ไพศาล อาจมีงานที่ข้าฯทำได้ ข้าฯขออุทิศชีวิตทำงานเพื่อ พระเยซูผู้ถูกตรึงตาย ข้าฯวางใจในการพิทักษ์รักษา รู้ว่าพระองค์ทรงเมตตา ขอทำงานด้วยใจจริงทุกสิ่งอัน ถ้างานนั้นพระองค์ทรงบัญชา</verse3>
      <chorus>เต็มใจไปที่พระองค์ทรงใช้ให้ไป ไม่ว่าบกหรือน้ำก็ไป เต็มใจพูดถ้อยคำซึ่งพระองค์บัญชา เต็มใจกระทำตามน้ำพระทัย</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>It may not be on the mountain’s height, Or over the stormy sea; It may not be at the battle’s front My Lord will have need of me; But if by a still, small voice He calls To paths I do not know, I’ll answer, dear Lord, with my hand in Thine, I’ll go where You want me to go.</verse1>
      <verse2>Perhaps today there are loving words Which Jesus would have me speak; There may be now, in the paths of sin, Some wand’rer whom I should seek. O Savior, if Thou wilt be my guide, Tho’ dark and rugged the way, My voice shall echo the message sweet, I’ll say what You want me to say.</verse2>
      <verse3>There’s surely somewhere a lowly place In earth’s harvest fields so wide, Where I may labor thro’ life’s short day For Jesus, the Crucified. So, trusting my all unto Thy care, I know Thou lovest me! I’ll do Thy will with a heart sincere, I’ll be what You want me to be.</verse3>
      <chorus>I’ll go where You want me to go, dear Lord, O’er mountain, or plain, or sea; I’ll say what You want me to say, dear Lord, I’ll be what You want me to be.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
