<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าชอบกล่าวเรื่องประเสริฐเลิศ</thainame>
   <englishname>I Love to Tell the Story</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าชอบกล่าวเรื่องประเสริฐเลิศ ถึงสิ่งเบื้องบนสวรรค์ เล่าเรื่องของพระเยซูเจ้า ซึ่งรักอย่างอัศจรรย์ ข้าชอบเล่าเรื่องราวอันนั้น เพราะว่าเป็นเรื่องความจริง ทำให้ใจข้ามีความสุขยิ่งกว่าเรื่องอื่นทุกสิ่ง</verse1>
      <verse2>ข้าชอบกล่าวเรื่องไพเราะนั้น เป็นเรื่องเหมาะสมน่าฟัง พูดครั้งใดใจยิ่งชื่นบาน เป็นการน่าอัศจรรย์ ชอบกล่าวถึงข่าวแสนวิเศษเพราะมีหลายคนไม่รู้ คือข่าวหลุดบาปพ้นกิเลสโดยฤทธิ์ของพระเยซู</verse2>
      <verse3>ข้าชอบกล่าวเรื่องวิไลนั้นกับคนที่เคยได้ฟัง ก็ยังอยากรู้อยู่ร่ำไปเหมือนผู้ที่ไม่เคยฟัง เมื่อข้าจะเห็นพระราศี ยินดีร้องเพลงบทใหม่ แต่ยังเป็นเรื่องโบราณนั้น ซึ่งข้าได้รักมานาน</verse3>
      <chorus>ชอบกล่าวถึงข่าวประเสริฐนั้น ถึงพระเยซูผู้ศักดิ์สิทธิ์ ชอบเล่าเรื่องราวโบราณนั้น ถึงความรักแห่งพระคริสต์</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>I love to tell the story of unseen things above, Of Jesus and His glory, of Jesus and His love. I love to tell the story, because I know ’tis true; It satisfies my longings as nothing else can do.</verse1>
      <verse2>I love to tell the story; ’tis pleasant to repeat What seems, each time I tell it, more wonderfully sweet. I love to tell the story, for some have never heard The message of salvation from God’s own holy Word.</verse2>
      <verse3>I love to tell the story, for those who know it best Seem hungering and thirsting to hear it like the rest. And when, in scenes of glory, I sing the new, new song, ’Twill be the old, old story that I have loved so long.</verse3>
      <chorus>I love to tell the story, ’twill be my theme in glory, To tell the old, old story of Jesus and His love.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
