<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าขอพึ่งพระองค์เจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>I Need Thee Every Hour</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus,verse5,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าขอพึ่งพระองค์เจ้า ทุกโมงทุกยาม ไม่มีผู้ใดจะปาน ที่ข้าควรตาม</verse1>
      <verse2>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน   1.ข้าขอพึ่งพระองค์เจ้า ทุกโมงทุกยาม ไม่มีผู้ใดจะปาน ที่ข้าควรตาม  ข้าขอพึ่งองค์พระเยซู ข้าขอพึ่งทุกเวลา โปรดทรงอำนวยพระพรใหญ่ยิ่งให้แก่ข้า</verse2>
      <verse3>ข้าขอพึ่งพระองค์เจ้าคราวทุกข์หรือสุข ขอโปรดอยู่ด้วยเสมอประทานความสุข</verse3>
      <verse4>ข้าขอพึ่งพระองค์เจ้าโปรดสอนบัญญัติ เพื่อสมดังสัญญาว่าให้พ้นวิบัติ</verse4>
      <verse5>ข้าขอพึ่งพระองค์เจ้าผู้เป็นพระบุตร ขอโปรดให้ข้าติดตาม องค์บริสุทธิ์</verse5>
      <chorus>ข้าขอพึ่งองค์พระเยซู ข้าขอพึ่งทุกเวลา โปรดทรงอำนวยพระพรใหญ่ยิ่งให้แก่ข้า</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>I need Thee every hour, most gracious Lord; No tender voice like Thine can peace afford.</verse1>
      <verse2>Music: Ro­bert Low­ry เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่  183 ข้าขอพึ่งพระองค์เจ้า (I Need Thee Every Hour) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org I need Thee every hour, most gracious Lord; No tender voice like Thine can peace afford.  ร้องรับ Refrain I need Thee, O I need Thee; Every hour I need Thee; O bless me now, my Savior,I come to Thee.</verse2>
      <verse3>I need Thee every hour, in joy or pain;  Come quickly and abide, or life is in vain.</verse3>
      <verse4>I need Thee every hour; teach me Thy will; And Thy rich promises in me fulfill</verse4>
      <verse5>I need Thee every hour, most Holy One; O make me Thine indeed, Thou blessèd Son.</verse5>
      <chorus>I need Thee, O I need Thee; Every hour I need Thee; O bless me now, my Savior,I come to Thee.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>