<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ชื่อของข้าฯจดหรือยัง</thainame>
   <englishname>Is My Name Written There</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าฯไม่ห่วงใยในสมบัติเงินทองเพชรนิลจินดา แต่ข้าฯหวังของโลกภายหน้าซึ่งดำรงชั่วกัลปา ในทะเบียนแห่งเมืองแมนนั้นชื่อของข้าฯจดหรือยัง ขอพระเยซูโปรดบอกว่าชื่อของข้าฯจดหรือยัง  ชื่อของข้าฯจดหรือยัง ในสมุดอันขาวปลั่ง ในทะเบียนแห่งเมืองแมนนั้น ชื่อของข้าฯจดหรือยัง</verse1>
      <verse2>บาปของข้าฯมีมากเหลือหลาย ดังเม็ดทรายมากเหลือล้น แต่โลหิตของพระเยซูได้ช่วยข้าฯให้หลุดพ้น คำสัญญาของพระองค์มีจารึกไว้ไม่พลาดพลั้ง แม้ว่าบาปข้าฯแดงเหมือนครั่ง พระองค์ทำให้ขาวปลั่ง  ชื่อของข้าฯได้จดแล้ว ในสมุดใสดังแก้ว ในทะเบียนแห่งเมืองแมนนั้น ชื่อของข้าฯได้จดแล้ว</verse2>
      <verse3>เมืองสวรรค์เป็นเมืองงดงาม ล้วนแล้วด้วยแสงสว่าง ชาวสวรรค์มีราศีงาม เครื่องแต่งกายขาวกระจ่าง ไม่มีความชั่วมาวี่แวว บริสุทธิ์งามผ่องแผ้ว ทูตสวรรค์คอยต้อนรับข้าฯ เพราะชื่อข้าฯได้จดแล้ว ชื่อของข้าฯได้จดแล้ว ในสมุดใสดังแก้ว ในทะเบียนแห่งเมืองแมนนั้น ชื่อของข้าฯได้จดแล้ว</verse3>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Lord, I care not for riches, neither silver nor gold; I would make sure of Heaven, I would enter the fold. In the book of Thy kingdom, with its pages so fair, Tell me, Jesus, my Savior, is my name written there? Is my name written there, On the page white and fair? In the book of Thy kingdom, Is my name written there?</verse1>
      <verse2>Lord, my sins they are many, like the sands of the sea, But Thy blood, O my Savior, is sufficient for me; For Thy promise is written, in bright letters that glow,“Though your sins be as scarlet, I will make them like snow.” Is my name written there, On the page white and fair? In the book of Thy kingdom, Is my name written there?</verse2>
      <verse3>Oh! that beautiful city, with its mansions of light, With its glorified beings, in pure garments of white; Where no evil thing cometh to despoil what is fair; Where the angels are watching, yes, my name’s written there. Is my name written there, On the page white and fair? In the book of Thy kingdom, Is my name written there?</verse3>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </chord>
</song>
