<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ในคืนวันหนึ่งยามเงียบสงัด</thainame>
   <englishname>It Came upon the Midnight Clear</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ในคืนวันหนึ่งยามเงียบสงัด มีทูตสวรรค์ลงมา ร้องเพลงสรรเสริญดีดพิณทองคำ  และนำข่าวดีกล่าวว่า &quot;ความสุขจงมีแก่ชาวโลกนี้  เพราะมีกษัตริย์บังเกิด&quot; มนุษย์ทั้งหลายจงเงี่ยหูฟัง บทเพลงความสุขประเสริญ</verse1>
      <verse2>เหล่าทูตสวรรค์พากันลงมา ร้องเพลงแสดงยินดี เพื่อให้ชาวโลกซึ่งเหน็ดเหนื่อยใจ ได้รับความสุขเปรมปรีดิ์ แต่ว่ามนุษย์ยังคงดื้อดึง ไม่มีความสามัคคี คนบาปทั้งหลายจงไตร่ตรองดู รับพรจากพระเยซู</verse2>
      <verse3>ผู้ใดเป็นทุกข์หนักอกหนักใจ ต้องแบกภาระเหลือหลาย ผู้ใดรับความทุกข์ทรมาน จนเหนื่อยดูเหมือนไม่ไหว บัดนี้จงเงยหน้าดูพระเจ้า รับเอาความรอดโดยดี พระองค์จะโปรดประทานความสุข พ้นทุกข์แก่ท่านทันที</verse3>
      <verse4>วันคืนกำลังจะผ่านพ้นไป ตามคำผู้ทำนายไว้ ยุคนั้นจะมาเวลากำหนด คือยุคไม่มีวันตาย ความสุขจะแผ่ออกไปทั่วโลก เปรียบดังแสงรัศมี ชาวโลกร้องเพลงอย่างทูตสวรรค์ คือเพลงสุขสวัสดี.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>It came upon the midnight clear, That glorious song of old, From angels bending near the earth, To touch their harps of gold; &quot;Peace on the earth, good will to men,  From Heaven's all gracious King.&quot; The world in solemn stillness lay, To hear the angels sing.</verse1>
      <verse2>Still through the cloven skies they come   With peaceful wings unfurled,   And still their heavenly music floats  O'er all the weary world;  Above its sad and lowly plains,  They bend on hovering wing, And ever over its Babel sounds  The blessèd angels sing.</verse2>
      <verse3>Yet with the woes of sin and strife The world has suffered long; Beneath the angel strain have rolled Two thousand years of wrong; And man, at war with man, hears not   The love-song which they bring; O hush the noise, ye men of strife And hear the angels sing.</verse3>
      <verse4>For lo! the days are hastening on,  By prophet-bards foretold, When with the ever circling years  Comes round the age of gold;  When peace shall over all the earth Its ancient splendors fling, And the whole world send back the song Which now the angels sing.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>