<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>สง่างามเมื่อเราเดินตามพระผู้ไถ่</thainame>
   <englishname>It is glory just to walk with Him</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>สง่างามเมื่อข้าฯเดินตามพระผู้ไถ่ซึ่งล้างบาปของข้าฯ เหมือนอย่างอยู่ในเมืองสวรรค์ชั้นฟ้า แสนหรรษาเมื่อข้าฯรู้ว่าพระองค์ประทับอยู่ใกล้ตัวข้าฯ สรรเสริญขอบพระคุณและโมทนา</verse1>
      <verse2>สง่างามเมื่อมีทุกข์ข้าฯกลับสุขเพราะพระองค์ทรงอยู่ใกล้ สง่างามเมื่ออ้อนวอนด้วยวางใจ สง่างามเมื่อข้าฯเดินตาม พระผู้ประทานความสุขแจ่มใส สรรเสริญขอบพระคุณและโมทนา</verse2>
      <verse3>สง่างามเมื่อข้าฯเดินไป บนฝั่งทองคำกับพระผู้ไถ่ ไม่ต้องพรากจากพระองค์อีกต่อไป ยิ่งงามสง่าเมื่อเวลาพระองค์ ประทับด้วยช่วยชูใจ สรรเสริญขอบพระคุณและโมทนา</verse3>
      <chorus>สง่างามเมื่อเราเดินตามพระเจ้า สง่างามเมื่อเราเดินตามพระเจ้า ทรงนำเราก้าวไปไม่พลั้ง ทั้งที่ราบหรือภูเขาสูง สง่างามเมื่อเราเดินตามพระเจ้า</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>It is glory just to walk with Him Whose blood has ransomed me; It is rapture for my soul each day. It is joy divine to feel Him near where’er my path may be. Bless the Lord, it’s glory all the way!</verse1>
      <verse2>It is glory when the shadows fall to know that He is near. O what joy to simply trust and pray! It is glory to abide in Him when skies above are clear. Yes, with Him, it’s glory all the way!</verse2>
      <verse3>’Twill be glory when I walk with Him on Heaven’s golden shore, Never from His side again to stray. ’Twill be glory, wondrous glory with the Savior evermore, Everlasting glory all the way!</verse3>
      <chorus>It is glory just to walk with Him, It is glory just to walk with Him He will guide my steps aright, Through the vale and o’er the height, It is glory just to walk with Him,</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>