<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เหตุไรจึงอายพระนามเยซู</thainame>
   <englishname>Jesus, and Shall It Ever Be</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>องค์พระเยซู ทรงอยู่เป็นนิจ เหตุไรเราอาย พระนามพระคริสต์  เป็นนามศักดิ์สิทธิ์ มีเกียรตินักหนา ชาวฟ้ากราบไหว้ อยู่ทุกเวลา</verse1>
      <verse2>เหตุไรจึงอาย พระนามพระเยซู  ผู้ได้ประทาน ความรักเอ็นดู  ทรงเป็นสว่าง กระจ่างดวงใจ  เหมือนดาวดวงใหญ่ส่องอยู่ทั่วไป</verse2>
      <verse3>อายนามพระคริสต์ เป็นได้อย่างไร เพราะเรามีบาปซ่อนไว้ในใจ  พระนามเยซูงามยิ่งกว่าดาว ทรงส่องสกาว ความบาปศูนย์หาย</verse3>
      <verse4>ควรหรืออายนาม ผู้เป็นสหาย ให้ข้าฯมีหวัง รอดพ้นอบาย  เมื่ออายพระนาม นั่นน่าอดสู  เพราะขาดความรัก ขาดกตัญญู</verse4>
      <verse5>เชิดชูพระนาม ไม่เสียแรงเปล่า อวดในความตาย พระเยซูเจ้า พระองค์เป็นเกียรติ ข้าฯจึงปรีดา พระองค์ปรานีไม่ทรงอายข้าฯ.</verse5>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Jesus, and shall it ever be A  mortal  man,  ashamed  of  Thee? Ashamed of  Thee, whom angels praise,   Whose glories shine through endless  days?</verse1>
      <verse2>Ashame of Jesus! O as soon Let morning blush to own the sun! He  sheds  the  beams of light divine  O'er this benighted  soul of mine.</verse2>
      <verse3>Ashamed of Jesus! sooner far Let night disown each radiant star! 'Tis midnight with my soul, till He, Bright Morning Star, bid darkness flee.</verse3>
      <verse4>Ashamed  of  Jesus! That  dear  friend, On  whom  my  hopes  of  heav'n  depend! No! when  I  blush, be  this  my  shame,  That  I  no  more  revere  his  name.</verse4>
      <verse5>Ashamed of Jesus! empty pride! I'll boast a Savior crucified, And O may this my portion be, My Savior not ashamed of me!</verse5>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </chord>
</song>