<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>พระเยซูเจ้าของเราเท่านั้น</thainame>
   <englishname>Jesus Only is Our Message</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>พระเยซูสถิตอยู่ในใจ  พระองค์ใหญ่กว่าสิ่งทั้งหลาย ให้เราทูนพระเยซูสูงเด่น  เห็นพระเยซูเจ้าเท่านั้น  ร้องรับ  เราต้องการพระเยซูเท่านั้น            เราสรรเสริญพระองค์ทุกวัน            พระเยซูผู้ทรงชำระรักษา            จะกลับมาเป็นพระราชา</verse1>
      <verse2>พระเยซูเจ้าพระมหาไถ่  ความบาปของเราทรงแบกไว้ ความชอบธรรมนั้นโปรดประทานให้ กำลังกายใจให้ทุกวัน</verse2>
      <verse3>พระเยซูเจ้าทรงชำระให้  บริสุทธิ์ทั้งกายและใจ ได้ประทานองค์พระวิญญาณเจ้า  จนได้เต็มล้นนอกและใน</verse3>
      <verse4>พระเยซูเจ้าผู้ทรงรักษา โรคภัยไข้เจ็บที่บีฑา เพราะพระองค์ทรงคืนชีพชีวา  เราทั้งหลายจะเป็นขึ้นมา</verse4>
      <verse5>เราคอยเฝ้าพระเยซูเจ้าอยู่ คอยเอียงหูฟังเสียงแตรนั้น พระเยซูเจ้าของเราเท่านั้น ทรงพระชนม์ตลอดนิรันดร์</verse5>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Jesus only is our message, Jesus all our theme shall be; We will lift up Jesus ever, Jesus only will we see.            Jesus only, Jesus ever,            Jesus all in all we sing,     Savior, Sanctifier, and Healer,     Glorious Lord and coming King.</verse1>
      <verse2>Jesus only is our Savior, All our guilt He bore away, He, our righteousness forever, All our strength from day to day.</verse2>
      <verse3>Jesus is our Sanctifier, Saving us from self and sin, And with all His Spirit's fulness, Filling all our hearts within.</verse3>
      <verse4>Jesus only is our Healer, All our sicknesses He bare, And His risen life and fullness, All His members still may share.</verse4>
      <verse5>And for Jesus we are waiting, List'ning for the Advent Call; But 'twill still be Jesus only, Jesus ever, all in all.</verse5>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </chord>
</song>