<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วย</thainame>
   <englishname>Jesus Saves</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4>จงป่าวร้องกึกก้องโลกา พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยให้ประเทศทั้งหลายยินดี พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยผู้ที่เชื่อรับความรอดได้ ผู้ประกาศสั่งสอนเรื่อยไปร้องเพลงนี้เพราะเรามีชัย พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วย.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>เราได้ยินเสียงอันสำราญ พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยป่าวประกาศให้ทั่วทุกบ้าน พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยรีบส่งข่าวไปทุกทวีป ขึ้นภูเขาและข้ามคลื่นด้วยไปประกาศตามพระบัญชา พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยWe have heard the joyful sound: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!Spread the tidings all around: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!Bear the news to every land, Climb the mountains, cross the waves;Onward! ’tis our Lord’s command; Jesus saves! Jesus saves!</verse1>
      <verse2>กระพือข่าวทั่วทุกประเทศ พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยบอกคนบาปทั้งหลายให้รู้ พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยจงบอกข่าวชาวเกาะทั้งหลาย จงบอกไปทุกถ้ำทุกห้วยจนชาวโลกเกิดความยินดี พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยWaft it on the rolling tide: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!Tell to sinners far and wide: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!Sing, you islands of the sea; Echo back, you ocean caves;Earth shall keep her jubilee: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!</verse2>
      <verse3>บอกชาวโลกซึ่งทุกข์วุ่นวาย พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยพระเยซูชนะความตาย พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยบอกให้ผู้ที่หมดความหวัง แล้วเล้าโลมผู้ซึ่งเหน็ดเหนื่อยเรามีชัยชนะความตาย พระเยซูเป็นผู้ช่วยSing above the battle strife: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!By His death and endless life Jesus saves! Jesus saves!Shout it brightly through the gloom, When the heart for mercy craves;Sing in triumph o’er the tomb: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!</verse3>
      <verse4>Give the winds a mighty voice: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!Let the nations now rejoice: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!Shout salvation full and free; highest hills and deepest caves;This our song of victory: Jesus saves! Jesus saves!</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>