<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ความรักของพระเยซูฉุดข้าฯ</thainame>
   <englishname> Love Found a Way</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ความรักของพระเยซูฉุดข้าฯ ขึ้นมาจากบาป  ชั่วช้าเลวทรามไม่มีความดีมีแต่แช่งสาป  เมื่อความหวังแห่งชีวิตหมดไป ข้าเห็นสว่าง  ความรักพระเจ้าทรงช่วยวิญญาณ ข้าฯรอดจากตาย  ข้าฯรอดจากบาป เพราะพระเจ้ารักข้าฯ ข้าฯขาวสะอาด เพราะพระเจ้ารักข้าฯ เพราะรักอย่างนั้น ทรงยอมมรณา ข้าฯรอดจากตาย จึงได้สรรเสริญพระนาม</verse1>
      <verse2>ความรักชักนำผู้ไถ่ลงมาตายที่กางเขน  ล้างบาปล้างเวรคนชั่วอย่างข้าฯ เป็นเรื่องแปลกใจ   ความรักจึงเป็นสะพานให้ข้าม ไปถึงสวรรค์  ความรักพระเจ้าได้ทรงยกโทษ ให้พ้นอบาย</verse2>
      <verse3>ความรักได้เปิดสวรรค์กว้างขวาง ช่วยชี้หนทาง  ที่พระเยซูครองอยู่ก่อนกาล ด้วยฤทธิ์อนันต์  ความรักช่วยข้าฯให้พ้นจากเหว ตลอดกัปกัลป์  ไม่มีใครช่วยในโลกนี้ได้   เว้นแต่พระเจ้า</verse3>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Wonderful love that rescued me, sunk deep in sin,  Guilty and vile as I could be-no hope within;   When every ray of light had fled, O glorious day!   Raising my soul from out the dead, love found a way. Love found a way, to redeem my soul, Love found a way, that could make me whole. Love sent my Lord to the cross of shame, Love found a way, O praise His holy Name!</verse1>
      <verse2>Love brought my Savior here to die on Calvary,   For such a sinful wretch as I, how can it be?   Love bridged the gulf 'twixt me and heav'n, taught me to pray,   I am redeemed, set free, forgiv'n, love found a way.</verse2>
      <verse3>Love opened wide the gates of light to heav'n's domain,  Where in eternal power and might Jesus shall reign.  Love lifted me from depths of woe to endless day,  There was no help in earth below;  love found a way.</verse3>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </chord>
</song>
