<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>พระองค์เป็นสมอ</thainame>
   <englishname>My Anchor Holds</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>แม้ว่าคลื่นใหญ่จัดซัดมา มีพายุพัดโถมดวงใจ  ข้าฯสงบสุขทุกเวลา  แม้คลื่นมาแรงกล้าปานใด  พระคริสต์เจ้าทรงเป็นสมอ  ซึ่งยึดข้าฯไว้อย่างปลอดภัย</verse1>
      <verse2>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.แม้ว่าคลื่นใหญ่จัดซัดมา มีพายุพัดโถมดวงใจ  ข้าฯสงบสุขทุกเวลา  แม้คลื่นมาแรงกล้าปานใด  พระคริสต์เจ้าทรงเป็นสมอ  ซึ่งยึดข้าฯไว้อย่างปลอดภัย    เมื่อเวลาพายุพัดมา  ข้าฯไม่กลัวเพราะมีสมอ  แม้ว่าเรือลำน้อยบอบบาง  แต่พระคุณพระเจ้ามากมาย  พระองค์เป็นสมอ ยึดไว้ปลอดภัย</verse2>
      <verse3>ความลำบากเกือบท่วมวิญญาณ  ความโศกเศร้าเข้ามาเผาผลาญ ผู้ล่อลวงชวนให้หลงทาง  มีพายุบังแสงตะวัน พึ่งพระคริสต์ข้าฯไม่หวั่นไหว  เพราะทรงเป็นสมอยึดไว้</verse3>
      <chorus>เมื่อเวลาพายุพัดมา  ข้าฯไม่กลัวเพราะมีสมอ  แม้ว่าเรือลำน้อยบอบบาง  แต่พระคุณพระเจ้ามากมาย  พระองค์เป็นสมอ ยึดไว้ปลอดภัย</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Though the angry surges roll    On my tempest driven soul,  I am peaceful, for I know,  Wildly though the winds may blow  I’ve an anchor safe and sure,  That can evermore endure.</verse1>
      <verse2>Music: Daniel B. Towner เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 143 พระองค์เป็นสมอ (My Anchor Holds) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org Though the angry surges roll    On my tempest driven soul,  I am peaceful, for I know,  Wildly though the winds may blow  I’ve an anchor safe and sure,  That can evermore endure. ร้องรับRefrain      And it holds, my anchor holds: Blow your wildest, then, O gale, On my bark so small and frail;  By His grace I shall not fail,   For my anchor holds, my anchor holds.</verse2>
      <verse3>Troubles almost ’whelm the soul; Griefs like billows o’er me roll;  Tempters seek to lure astray;  Storms obscure the light of day: But in Christ I can be bold,  I’ve an anchor that shall hold.</verse3>
      <chorus>And it holds, my anchor holds: Blow your wildest, then, O gale, On my bark so small and frail;  By His grace I shall not fail,   For my anchor holds, my anchor holds.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
