<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>เฝ้าชิดสนิทพระเจ้า</thainame>
	<englishname>Nearer My God To Thee </englishname>
	<mienthainame>แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง</mienthainame>
	<order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5,verse6</order>

<thai>
    <verse1>เฝ้าชิดสนิทพระเจ้า  ยิ่งใกล้ยิ่งดี แม้ยากลำบากเพียงไร   ใจอยากอยู่ใกล้ ความทุกข์เดือดร้อนหมดไป   เพราะว่าอยู่ใกล้พระเจ้า ยิ่งใกล้พระองค์ยิ่งดี  อยู่ใกล้พระเจ้า</verse1>
    <verse2>แม้ว่าข้าได้เหินห่างจากทางพระเจ้า ดวงใจอ้างว้างเปลี่ยวเปล่า  จิตใจโศกเศร้า เมื่อนั้นใจข้าต้องการอยากใกล้ พระเจ้านานนาน ยิ่งใกล้พระองค์ยิ่งดี  อยู่ใกล้พระเจ้า</verse2>
    <verse3>ยามทุกข์ลำบากเช่นนี้  ยังโปรดปรานี เปิดทางสวรรค์ ให้มีบันไดจากฟ้า เห็นฑูตสวรรค์ลงมาเรียกข้าให้เข้าไปใกล้ ยิ่งใกล้พระองค์ยิ่งดี  อยู่ใกล้พระเจ้า</verse3>
    <verse4>แล้วข้าจึงเห็นสว่างทางของพระเจ้า ความยากลำบากบางเบาเมื่อใกล้พระองค์ ข้าจะร้องเพลงสรรเสริญ  เฝ้าใกล้พระเจ้าทุกที ยิ่งใกล้พระองค์ยิ่งดี   อยู่ใกล้พระเจ้า</verse4>
    <verse5>...</verse5>
	<verse6>...</verse6>
</thai>

<mienthai>
    <verse1>แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง, เก้า นิด ฟัด เฒี้ยว. ไม้ กุ๊น ตีง เหฒียบ หฑั่ง จ๋า เยีย หย่า ปวั๊ง เอ๋ย. เยีย หย่า อะเฮน้ย ป๋าว ฑูง, เปียะ ต้าย นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง.แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง, เก้า นิด ฟัด เฒี้ยว.</verse1>
    <verse2>ฮนั้ง ตี๋ง ล่าย เมี่ยน มี่ง เกา บะฮนอย หย่า ม้วด. ลู่ง หฮมวัง เว่ย ก๋อม เยีย หฒุ ฑ์ม หละเปย๊ย เปว๋ย. มป่า เยีย ฌ่อม เบ๋ย ปวัด แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง. แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง, เก้า นิด ฟัด เฒี้ยว.</verse2>
    <verse3>เจ๊า- คู้ บย๋าง ย่าง ทิน-ต้อง เญย เทย หิ่น ธ้วด. เหยียด ฒู้ง เฒี้ยว ฝูง เยีย วั้ว, เหว่ย เฒี้ยว ค้อ-เลี่ยน. ฟิน- เมี่ยน ฝาวๆ เหฌี่ยๆ, เยีย เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง. แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง, เก้า นิด ฟัด เฒี้ยว.</verse3>
    <verse4>เยีย เจี์ย ซิน ต้าย ฮนั้ม เถา เธง เฒี้ยว ทิน-ฮู่ง. เยีย เหลียบ เบด^เอน เหว่ย หฒุ หน่าน ฒี่ง ดุ๊ด เหฑ่ง. เยีย หฒุ ปวั้ง เญย ไฮ่ เถง, เยีย เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง. แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง, เก้า นิด ฟัด เฒี้ยว.</verse4>
    <verse5>ปวั๊ง เฮญี้ยว อะเฮน้ย ฮนั้ง ได๋ กู้ หงว่าย ลู่ง นอ. ฮนอย, หฮลา, เหฮลย, หละคุ ขูง ได๋ มี่ง ทิน-กั๊วะ. เยีย หธ่อ แอ๋ง ป๋าว ฑูง เธง, แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง. แอ๋ง เก้า นิด ฟัด ทิน-ฮู่ง, เก้า นิด ฟัด เฒี้ยว.</verse5>
	<verse6>...</verse6>
</mienthai>

    
<english>
    <verse1>Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee! E’en though it be a cross that raiseth me, Still all my song shall be, nearer, my God, to Thee. Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!</verse1>
    <verse2>Though like the wanderer, the sun gone down, Darkness be over me, my rest a stone; Yet in my dreams I’d be nearer, my God, to Thee. Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!</verse2>
    <verse3>There let the way appear, steps unto Heav’n; All that Thou sendest me, in mercy giv’n; Angels to beckon me nearer, my God, to Thee. Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!</verse3>
    <verse4>Then, with my waking thoughts bright with Thy praise, Out of my stony griefs Bethel I’ll raise; So by my woes to be nearer, my God, to Thee. Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!</verse4>
    <verse5>Or, if on joyful wing cleaving the sky, Sun, moon, and stars forgot, upward I’ll fly, Still all my song shall be, nearer, my God, to Thee. Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!</verse5>
	<verse6>There in my Father’s home, safe and at rest, There in my Savior’s love, perfectly blest; Age after age to be nearer, my God, to Thee. Nearer, my God, to Thee, nearer to Thee!</verse6>
</english>

<chord>
    <verse1>G   C G     D G     C G    D7     G G     C      G G   C   D7 G      C   G   D7    G</verse1>
    <verse2>G   C G     D G     C G    D7     G G     C      G G   C   D7 G      C   G   D7    G</verse2>
    <verse3>G   C G     D G     C G    D7     G G     C      G G   C   D7 G      C   G   D7    G</verse3>
    <verse4>G   C G     D G     C G    D7     G G     C      G G   C   D7 G      C   G   D7    G</verse4>
    <verse5>G   C G     D G     C G    D7     G G     C      G G   C   D7 G      C   G   D7    G</verse5>
	<verse6>G   C G     D G     C G    D7     G G     C      G G   C   D7 G      C   G   D7    G</verse6>
</chord>


</song>
