<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ความรักพระองค์มัดแน่นหนา</thainame>
   <englishname>O Love that Wilt Not Let Me Go</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ขออย่าให้พระคริสต์ทอดทิ้งข้า ให้ความรักพระองค์มัดแน่นหนา ข้าขอถวายทั้งใจวาจา ขอให้ความรักหลั่งไหลลงมา ให้มากยิ่งกว่าแต่ก่อน</verse1>
      <verse2>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ขออย่าให้พระคริสต์ทอดทิ้งข้า ให้ความรักพระองค์มัดแน่นหนา ข้าขอถวายทั้งใจวาจา ขอให้ความรักหลั่งไหลลงมา ให้มากยิ่งกว่าแต่ก่อน</verse2>
      <verse3>ให้ความยินดีของพระเยซู ขับไล่ความทุกข์ป่วยไข้สูญหาย เป็นพรลงมาเหมือนฝนโปรยปราย ข้ายินดีเพราะพระองค์สัญญา ข้ายิ้มได้ทั้งน้ำตา</verse3>
      <verse4>ข้ารู้จักกางเขนพระเยซู เป็นที่ลี้ภัยมั่นคงช่วยชู แม้ว่าร่างกายกลายเป็นดินทราย พระองค์ประทานให้มีชีพใหม่ สู่ชีวิตไม่รู้ตาย...</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>O Love that Will Not Let Me Go I rest my weary soul in Thee; I give Thee back the life I owe, That in thine ocean depths its flow   May richer, fuller be.</verse1>
      <verse2>Music: St. Mar­garet (Peace), Al­bert L. Peace, 1884 . Alternate tunes:  • Hampstead (Davies), H. Wal­ford Da­vies, in In hoc Sig­no, 1915, num­ber 31  • Wyke, Les­lie H. Hew­ard (1897-1943). Hew­ard is said have writ­ten the tune while a choir boy at Man­ches­ter Ca­thed­ral. เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 126 ความรักพระองค์มัดแน่นหนา (O Love that Wilt Not Let Me Go) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org O Love that Will Not Let Me Go I rest my weary soul in Thee; I give Thee back the life I owe, That in thine ocean depths its flow   May richer, fuller be.</verse2>
      <verse3>O joy that seekest me through pain, I cannot close my heart to Thee; I trace the rainbow through the rain, And feel the promise is not vain   That morn shall tearless be.</verse3>
      <verse4>O Cross that liftest up my head, I dare not ask to fly from Thee; I lay in dust life’s glory dead, And from the ground there blossoms red. Life that shall endless be.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>
