<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เหล่าทหารของพระคริสต์</thainame>
   <englishname>Onward, Christian Soldiers</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>เหล่าทหารของพระคริสต์ ต้องทำศึกกับมาร พระเยซูทรงนำหน้า เข้ารบประจัญบาน พระคริสต์เจ้าแม่ทัพใหญ่ พาไปรบศัตรู เวลารบต้องคอยดู ธงกางเขนโบกอยู่</verse1>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3>ยศศักดิ์สง่าราศี ของโลกนี้สูญหาย</verse3>
      <verse4>ร้องสรรเสริญพระบารมี แด่องค์พระเยซูทูตสวรรค์และชาวโลก สดุดีเชิดชู</verse4>
      <chorus>เหล่าทหารของพระคริสต์ ต้องทำศึกกับมารจงตามองค์พระเยซู เราชนะซาตาน</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Onward, Christian soldiers, marching as to war,With the cross of Jesus going on before. Christ, the royal Master,leads against the foe; Forward into battle see His banners go!</verse1>
      <verse2>เหมือนกองทัพอันเกรียงไกร ศิษย์พระคริสต์นับล้านทำสงครามกับมารร้าย คล้ายกับศิษย์โบราณLike a mighty army moves the church of God;Brothers, we are treading where the saints have trod. เราไม่แตกแยกจากกัน แต่มีใจกลมเกลียวความเชื่อ ความหวัง ความรัก เรามีหลักอย่างเดียวWe are not divided, all one body we,One in hope and doctrine, one in charity.</verse2>
      <verse3>ความรอดในพระเยซู ไม่มีที่สุดปลายCrowns and thrones may perish, kingdoms rise and wane,But the church of Jesus constant will remain. พญามารคอยกีดกั้น แต่ยิ่งแผ่ไพศาลเชื่อสัญญาของพระคริสต์ เรามีชัยแก่มารGates of hell can never gainst that church prevail;We have Christ’s own promise,and that cannot fail.</verse3>
      <verse4>จงก้าวหน้าเดินต่อไป รวมกับศิษย์ทั้งหลายร่วมประสานเสียงบรรเลง เป็นบทเพลงถวายOnward then, ye people, join our happy throng,Blend with ours your voices in the triumph song. Glory, laud and honor unto Christ the King,This through countless ages men and angels sing.</verse4>
      <chorus>Onward, Christian soldiers, marching as to war,With the cross of Jesus going on before.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
