<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ขอเปิดดวงตาให้ข้าฯแลเห็น</thainame>
   <englishname>Open My Eyes That I may See</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ขอเปิดดวงตาให้ข้าฯแลเห็น  สัตย์จริงเที่ยงธรรมให้เห็นชัดเจน  โปรดช่วยปลดปล่อยพ้นฤทธิ์ของซาตาน  ให้ข้าฯเป็นไทมีชัยเหนือมาร   โดยใจสงบ ข้าฯคอยพระองค์  พร้อมที่จะทำตามพระประสงค์  โปรดเปิดดวงตาให้ข้าฯแลเห็น  โอพระวิญญาณ</verse1>
      <verse2>ขอเปิดหูข้าฯ เพื่อฟังคำตรัส เมื่อยินสำเนียงพระองค์ถนัด ขอให้เสียงอื่นได้อันตรธาน แต่เสียงพระองค์ยังคงกังวาน   โดยใจสงบ ข้าฯคอยพระองค์  พร้อมที่จะทำตามพระประสงค์  โปรดเปิดหูข้าฯให้ได้ยินเสียง  โอพระวิญญาณ</verse2>
      <verse3>ขอให้วาจาข้าฯเป็นพยาน ประกาศความรักซึ่งได้ประทาน ขอเปิดใจข้าฯเพื่อเป็นคนกล้าหาญ สำแดงความรักทั่วโลกชื่นบาน   โดยใจสงบ ข้าฯคอยพระองค์  พร้อมที่จะทำตามพระประสงค์  ขอให้วาจาข้าฯเป็นพยาน  โอพระวิญญาณ</verse3>
      <verse4>ขอเปิดดวงใจให้อ่านพระธรรม  เข้าใจความรักมากขึ้นทุกวัน  ขอเปิดทางเดินเพื่อไม่ตกใจกลัว  ขอความสว่างส่องแสงอยู่ทั่ว  โดยใจสงบ ข้าฯคอยพระองค์  พร้อมที่จะทำตามพระประสงค์  โปรดเปิดดวงใจให้เห็นสว่าง  โอพระวิญญาณ</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Open my eyes, that I may see  glimpses of truth thou hast for me;  place in my hands the wonderful key that shall unclasp and set me free.  Silently now I wait for thee, ready, my God, thy will to see. Open my eyes, illumine me, Spirit divine!</verse1>
      <verse2>Open my ears, that I may hear voices of truth thou sendest clear;  and while the wavenotes fall on my ear,  everything false will disappear.  Silently now I wait for thee, ready, my God, thy will to see.  Open my ears, illumine me, Spirit divine!</verse2>
      <verse3>Open my mouth, and let me bear  gladly the warm truth everywhere;  open my heart and let me prepare  love with thy children thus to share.  Silently now I wait for thee, ready, my God, thy will to see.  Open my heart, illumine me, Spirit divine!</verse3>
      <verse4>Open my mind that I may read More of Thy love in word and deed; What shall I fear while yet Thou dost lead? Only for light from Thee I plead. Silently now I wait for thee,  ready, my God, thy will to see. Open my mind, illumine me, Spirit divine!</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>
