<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>พระวาทะคือพระเป็นเจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>O Word of God Incarnate</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>พระวาทะคือพระเป็นเจ้า  พระปัญญาจากเบื้องฟ้า เป็นความจริงที่ไม่เปลี่ยนแปลง  ส่องแสงสว่างแจ่มหล้า    เราสรรเสริญเพราะรังสี  ส่องในวิถีทางเดิน เป็นโคมสว่างนำมรรคา  อยู่ทุกสมัยจำเริญ</verse1>
      <verse2>คริสตจักรได้รับพระธรรมนี้  คือองค์พระเยซูคริสต์ จึงยกพระธรรมนั้นขึ้นชี้  ส่องให้โลกเห็นชีวิต    เปรียบดังหีบทองอันมีค่า  เก็บเพชรเม็ดงามยิ่งไว้ เหมือนภาพองค์พระเยซูเจ้า  ผู้ทรงเป็นชีวิตไซร้</verse2>
      <verse3>ขอพระผู้ช่วยทรงบันดาล ส่องแสงสว่างตลอดกาล ส่องไปทั่วทุกทวีป                                                                                                 ขอทรงนำผู้ที่หลงทาง ด้วยแสงสว่างสุกใส จนเมฆหมอกมืดมัวกระจ่าง จะเห็นพระพักตร์วิไล อาเมน.</verse3>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>O Word of God Incarnate ,  O wisdom from on high. O Truth unchanged , unchanging , O Light of our dark sky. We praise thee for the radiance  that from the hallowed page. A lantern to our footstep, Shines on from age to age.</verse1>
      <verse2>The Church from her dear  Master received the gift divine. And still that light she lifteth  O'er all the earth to shine. It is the golden caset ,  Where gems of truth are stored. It is the heaven-drawn picture of Christ,  the living word.</verse2>
      <verse3>O make your Church, dear Savior,  คริสตจักรให้เป็นประทีป                                                                                          a lamp of purest gold,  To bear before the nations   Your true light as of old.  O teach your wandering pilgrims   by this their path to trace,  Till, clouds and darkness ended,   they see You face to face.</verse3>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </chord>
</song>
