<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ขอเชิญไหว้กษัตริย์</thainame>
   <englishname>O Worship the King</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ขอเชิญไหว้กษัตริย์ ทรงรัศมีเมืองบน สรรเสริญปฏิบัติ ด้วยโสมนัสเหล่าชน พระเจ้าเป็นโล่ของข้าฯ เป็นป้อมแต่โบราณ สถิตป้องกันรักษา ข้าฯจึงพ้นภัยมาร</verse1>
      <verse2>สรรเสริญฤทธิ์พระองค์ ถวายผู้เมตตา ทรงรังสีมั่นคง ส่องไปทั่วเวหา เมื่อทรงพิโรธชนใด ดังหมอกใหญ่มืดมัว โดยเดชาอันเกรียงไกร ข้าฯจึงได้เกรงกลัว</verse2>
      <verse3>โลกนี้ของพระองค์ เต็มด้วยอัศจรรย์ สร้างตามพระประสงค์ โดยฤทธิ์ใหญ่อนันต์  ทรงตั้งแผ่นดินโลกไว้ ให้ เหล่าชนอาศัย  และสร้างน้ำสมุทรให้ ล้อมรอบโลกกว้างใหญ่</verse3>
      <verse4>ข้าฯเกิดมาในโลก เต็มด้วยบาปหยาบหลง  แต่พระเจ้าปรานี เมื่อวางใจ พระองค์ ทรงเมตตาค้ำชูข้าฯ แน่นหนาจนสุดปลาย พระผู้สร้าง ผู้รักษา ผู้ช่วย และสหาย.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>O  Worship  the  king , All  glorious  a  bove And  gratefully   sing  His pow'r  and  his  love. Our  shield  and  defender  the ancient  of   days . Pavilioned  in  splendor ,  and  girded  with  praise.</verse1>
      <verse2>O  tell  of his might ,  O sing  of  his  grace, Whose  robe  is the  light,  whose  can-o-py  space, His  chariots  of  wrath  the deep  thunder  clouds  form. And  dark  is  His path  on  the wings  of  the  storm.</verse2>
      <verse3>The earth with its store of wonders untold, Almighty, Thy power hath founded of old; Established it fast by a changeless decree, And round it hath cast, like a mantle, the sea.</verse3>
      <verse4>Frail  children  of dust, and feeble  as frail, In  Thee  do we trust, nor  find Thee  to fail. Thy  mercies  how tender, how  firm to  the  end, Our  Marker, Defender, Redeemer  and  Friend.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>