<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ความสุขมีหรือ</thainame>
   <englishname>Peace, Perfect  Peace</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5,verse6</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อโลกนี้ถูกแช่งสาป พระโลหิตของพระคริสต์ทำลายความบาป</verse1>
      <verse2>ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อต้องทำงานวุ่นวาย แต่ตามพระทัยพระเจ้าความทุกข์สูญหาย</verse2>
      <verse3>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อโลกนี้ถูกแช่งสาป พระโลหิตของพระคริสต์ทำลายความบาป  2.ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อต้องทำงานวุ่นวาย แต่ตามพระทัยพระเจ้าความทุกข์สูญหาย</verse3>
      <verse4>ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อคนรักอยู่ห่างไกล พระเยซูคุ้มครองเราปลอดภัยทุกฝ่าย</verse4>
      <verse5>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อโลกนี้ถูกแช่งสาป พระโลหิตของพระคริสต์ทำลายความบาป  2.ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อต้องทำงานวุ่นวาย แต่ตามพระทัยพระเจ้าความทุกข์สูญหาย  3.ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อความทุกข์บีบรอบกาย เมื่อยามอยู่ชิดพระคริสต์ใจเงียบสบาย  4.ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อคนรักอยู่ห่างไกล พระเยซูคุ้มครองเราปลอดภัยทุกฝ่าย</verse5>
      <verse6>ความสุขมีหรือเมื่อถึงวันมรณา พระองค์ผู้ทรงชัยจะโปรดนำพา.</verse6>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Peace, perfect peace, in this dark world of sin? The blood of Jesus whispers peace within.</verse1>
      <verse2>Peace, perfect peace, by thronging duties pressed? To do the will of Jesus, this is rest.</verse2>
      <verse3>He wrote down these lyr­ics, just as they ap­pear today, and read them to the man: per­haps the last thing he heard before Jesus called him “to Hea­ven’s per­fect peace.” Music: Pax Te­cum, George T. Cald­beck &amp; Charles J. Vin­cent, 1876 เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่  160 ความสุขมีหรือ (Peace, Perfect  Peace) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org Peace, perfect peace, in this dark world of sin? The blood of Jesus whispers peace within. Peace, perfect peace, by thronging duties pressed? To do the will of Jesus, this is rest.</verse3>
      <verse4>Peace, perfect peace, with loved ones far away? In Jesus’ keeping we are safe, and they.</verse4>
      <verse5>Bick­er­steth was va­ca­tion­ing in Har­ro­gate, England, where he heard a ser­mon on Isaiah 26:3 by Canon Gibbon. The min­is­ter re­lat­ed that the He­brew text used the word peace twice to in­di­cate ab­so­lute per­fect­ion. The idea was still on Bick­er­steth’s mind when he vis­it­ed a dy­ing rel­a­tive that af­ter­noon. To soothe the man’s emo­tion­al tur­moil, Bick­er­steth opened his Bible to read from Isaiah 26:3. He wrote down these lyr­ics, just as they ap­pear today, and read them to the man: per­haps the last thing he heard before Jesus called him “to Hea­ven’s per­fect peace.” Music: Pax Te­cum, George T. Cald­beck &amp; Charles J. Vin­cent, 1876 เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่  160 ความสุขมีหรือ (Peace, Perfect  Peace) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org Peace, perfect peace, in this dark world of sin? The blood of Jesus whispers peace within. Peace, perfect peace, by thronging duties pressed? To do the will of Jesus, this is rest. Peace, perfect peace, with sorrows surging round? On Jesus’ bosom naught but calm is found. Peace, perfect peace, with loved ones far away? In Jesus’ keeping we are safe, and they.</verse5>
      <verse6>Peace, perfect peace, death shadowing us and ours? Jesus has vanquished death and all its powers.</verse6>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <verse6/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <verse6/>
   </chord>
</song>
