<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>สรรเสริญ สรรเสริญ</thainame>
   <englishname>Praise Him! Praise Him!</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>สรรเสริญ สรรเสริญ พระเยซูเป็นผู้ไถ่ดีเลิศ ชาวชนโห่ร้อง ขอบพระคุณองค์พระบุตร ทูตสวรรค์ร้อง พร้อมกันสรรเสริญยกย่องชูเชิด เราถวายเกียรติ แด่องค์ผู้บริสุทธิ์ พระองค์ทรงเป็นผู้เลี้ยงอันดีที่นำทาง คนอ่อนแอทรงช่วยประคองไว้ไม่วาง</verse1>
      <verse2>สรรเสริญ สรรเสริญ พระเยซูเป็นผู้ไถ่ดีเลิศ  พระองค์วายชนม์ เพื่อให้ข้าฯพ้นอบาย  ทรงเป็นความรอด เป็นความหวังมั่นคงดั่งศิลา จงถวายเกียรติ แด่ผู้ทรงถูกตรึงตาย เปล่งเสียงยกย่อง ผู้แบกภาระของเราไป นี่คือความรัก อัศจรรย์อันยิ่งใหญ่</verse2>
      <verse3>สรรเสริญ  สรรเสริญ พระเยซูเป็นผู้ไถ่ดีเลิศ ร้องโฮซันนา ก้องสนั่นทั่วท้องฟ้า องค์พระเยซูทรงฤทธิ์ครอบครองเป็นนิจสืบไป ราชาทั้งหลายนำมงกุฎมาถวาย พระเยซูทรงครอบครองโลกอย่างผู้มีชัย ทรงมีอำนาจ ประกอบด้วยฤทธิ์ยิ่งใหญ่</verse3>
      <chorus>สรรเสริญ สรรเสริญ ประกาศพระคุณของพระเยซู สรรเสริญ  สรรเสริญ ด้วยบทเพลงสดุดี</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Praise Him! praise Him! Jesus, our blessed Redeemer! Sing, O earth, His wonderful love proclaim!  Hail Him! Hail Him! highest archangels in glory, Strength and honor give to His holy name!  Like a shepherd, Jesus will guard His children; In His arms He carries them all day long.</verse1>
      <verse2>Praise Him! praise Him! Jesus, our blessed Redeemer! For our sins He suffered and bled and died;  He our Rock, our hope of eternal salvation, Hail Him! hail Him! Jesus the crucified. Sound His praises! Jesus who bore our sorrows, Love unbounded, wonderful, deep, and strong!</verse2>
      <verse3>Praise Him! praise Him! Jesus, our blessed Redeemer! Heavenly portals loud with hosannas ring!  Jesus, Savior, reigneth forever and ever;  Crown Him! Crown Him! Prophet and Priest and King!  Christ is coming,over the world victorious;  Power and glory unto the Lord belong!</verse3>
      <chorus>Praise Him! Praise Him! Tell of His excellent greatness!  Praise Him! Praise Him! Ever in joyful song!</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
