<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ช่วยให้พ้นอันตราย</thainame>
   <englishname>Rescue the Perishing</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ช่วยคนกำลังทำบาป ให้รอดจากความตาย ช่วยฉุดออกมาให้หลุดพ้นจากความบาป จงเมตตาผู้หลงทางและผู้พลั้งพลาดไป  บอกว่าพระเยซูทรงช่วยให้รอดได้</verse1>
      <verse2>หากว่าดูหมิ่นพระเจ้า แต่ทรงอดทนได้  ทรงคอยคนบาปให้สำนึกผิดกลับใจ จงร้อนใจชักชวนเขา สั่งสอนด้วยเมตตา ผู้ใดยอมเชื่อพระองค์ ทรงยกโทษได้</verse2>
      <verse3>หากว่ามารมารบกวน ชักชวนให้หลงใหล คนบาปรอดได้เพราะพระเจ้ากรุณา ปลอบใจเขาด้วยความรักชักนำให้กลับใจ จิตอันฟกช้ำต้องการ ผู้ช่วยเมตตา</verse3>
      <verse4>ช่วยให้พ้นอันตราย ด้วยใจอันขวนขวาย ทรงให้ท่านมีกำลังสู้พญามาร นำเข้าในทางชอบธรรม ช่วยเขาด้วยเมตตา บอกว่าพระองค์เป็นผู้ตายไถ่ประชา</verse4>
      <chorus>ช่วยให้พ้นอันตราย ให้รอดจากความตาย พระเยซูทรงเมตตา ทรงกรุณา</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Rescue the perishing, care for the dying, Snatch them in pity from sin and the grave;  Weep o’er the erring one, lift up the fallen,  Tell them of Jesus, the mighty to save.</verse1>
      <verse2>Though they are slighting Him, still He is waiting, Waiting the penitent child to receive;  Plead with them earnestly, plead with them gently;   He will forgive if they only believe.</verse2>
      <verse3>Down in the human heart, crushed by the tempter,   Feelings lie buried that grace can restore; Touched by a loving heart, wakened by kindness, Chords that were broken will vibrate once more.</verse3>
      <verse4>Rescue the perishing, duty demands it; Strength for thy labor  the Lord will provide;  Back to the narrow way patiently win them; Tell the poor wand’rer a Savior has died.</verse4>
      <chorus>Rescue the perishing, care for the dying,  Jesus is merciful, Jesus will save.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
