<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ขอองค์พระเจ้าฟื้นใจ</thainame>
   <englishname>Revive Thy Work, O Lord</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus,verse5,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ขอองค์พระเจ้าฟื้นใจ ทรงสำแดงพระฤทธา ให้ปรากฏแก่คริสตจักรทั้งหลาย ให้ทุกคนยอมกลับใจ</verse1>
      <verse2>โปรดฟื้นการของพระองค์ โปรดทรงดลจิตดลใจ ขอโปรดประทานไฟลุกรุ่งเรือง เหมือนวันเพ็นเทคอสเต</verse2>
      <verse3>โปรดฟื้นการของพระองค์ โปรดทรงให้ความชื่นใจ โปรดให้ความรักของเราผ่องใส จนความชั่วหมดสูญไป</verse3>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <chorus>โปรดฟื้นการของพระองค์ ทรงตอบคำอธิษฐาน ขอพระวิญญาณทรงโปรดเข้ามา ให้ความรอดแก่ประชา</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Revive Thy work,O Lord! Now to Thy saints appear!Oh, speak with power to every soul, And let Thy people hear!</verse1>
      <verse2>Revive Thy work,O Lord! And every soul inspire;Oh, kindle in each heart, we pray,The Pentecostal fire!</verse2>
      <verse3>Revive Thy work, O Lord! Exalt Thy precious name!And may Thy love in every heart Be kindled to a flame!</verse3>
      <verse4>โปรดฟื้นการของพระองค์ โปรดทรงให้ศิษย์กล้าหาญให้ทุกคนรู้ว่ามีบาปหนา เหมือนเวลาครั้งโบราณRevive Thy work, O Lord! And bless to all Thy Word!And may its pure and sacred truth In living faith be heard!</verse4>
      <verse5>โปรดฟื้นการของพระองค์ ทรงให้ตามพระสัญญาขอทรงสำแดงการงานยิ่งใหญ่ให้เป็นพระเกียรติพระองค์Revive Thy work, O Lord! And make Thy servants bold;Convict of sin and work once more As in the days of old.</verse5>
      <chorus>Revive Thy work, O Lord! While here to Thee we bow;Descend, O gracious Lord, descend! Oh, come, and bless us now!</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
