<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>จงชื่นใจยินดี</thainame>
   <englishname>Revive Us Again</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>จงชื่นใจยินดี ที่พระคริสต์เสด็จมา รางหญ้า ไม้กางเขน และอุโมงค์ประจักษ์ตา  ร้องรับ สรรเสริญ จงเทิดพระเกียรติไว้ อาเลลูยา อาเมน สรรเสริญ จงเทิดพระเกียรติไว้ ขอให้ฟื้นใจใหม่</verse1>
      <verse2>จงชื่นใจยินดี เพราะพระวิญญาณนำเรา ทรงเป็นแสงสว่าง ให้เห็นพระเยซูเจ้า</verse2>
      <verse3>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.จงชื่นใจยินดี ที่พระคริสต์เสด็จมา รางหญ้า ไม้กางเขน และอุโมงค์ประจักษ์ตา  ร้องรับ สรรเสริญ จงเทิดพระเกียรติไว้ อาเลลูยา อาเมน สรรเสริญ จงเทิดพระเกียรติไว้ ขอให้ฟื้นใจใหม่  2.จงชื่นใจยินดี เพราะพระวิญญาณนำเรา ทรงเป็นแสงสว่าง ให้เห็นพระเยซูเจ้า</verse3>
      <verse4>จงชื่นใจยินดีที่พระองค์รักทุกคน ทรงให้ทุกคนร้อนรนด้วยไฟจากเบื้องบน</verse4>
      <verse5>จงชื่นใจยินดีที่พระองค์สัญญาว่า เราจะกลับมารับท่านในวันหนึ่งข้างหน้า</verse5>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>We praise Thee, O God! For the Son of Thy love, For Jesus who died, And is now gone above. Hallelujah! Thine the glory.Hallelujah! Amen. Hallelujah! Thine the glory. Revive us again.</verse1>
      <verse2>We praise Thee, O God!For Thy Spirit of light, Who hath shown us our Savior, And scattered our night.</verse2>
      <verse3>Music : John J. Husband, 1815 เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 201 จงชื่นใจยินดี  (Revive Us Again) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org We praise Thee, O God! For the Son of Thy love, For Jesus who died, And is now gone above. Hallelujah! Thine the glory.Hallelujah! Amen. Hallelujah! Thine the glory. Revive us again. We praise Thee, O God!For Thy Spirit of light, Who hath shown us our Savior, And scattered our night.</verse3>
      <verse4>All glory and praise To the God of all grace, Who hast bought us, and sought us,And guided our ways.</verse4>
      <verse5>Revive us again; Fill each heart with Thy love; May each soul be rekindled With fire from above.</verse5>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </chord>
</song>
