<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>รอดอยู่ในหัตถ์พระเยซู</thainame>
   <englishname>Safe in the arms of Jesus</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>รอดอยู่ในหัตถ์พระเยซู   ใจข้าหยุดพักหมดห่วง ที่นั่นร่มเย็นด้วยความรัก    มีทูตสวรรค์บรรเลงเพลง   ต้อนรับข้าเข้าสวรรค์ ให้ข้าพักอยู่ที่เมืองนั้น   มีความสุขอยู่นิรันดร์</verse1>
      <verse2>รอดอยู่ในหัตถ์พระเยซู   รอดพ้นจากความรำคาญพ้นจากการล่อลวงของมาร   บาปไม่ทำร้ายรังควาน พ้นจากความทุกข์เศร้าโศก พ้นจากศัตรูคอยรบกวน   พ้นการทดลองของโลก</verse2>
      <verse3>รอดอยู่ในหัตถ์พระเยซู   ข้าฯรอดพ้นจากอบายอยู่ในพระทรวงพระเยซู   ใจข้าฯหยุดพักสบาย และวายพระชนม์เพื่อข้าฯเป็นเหมือนศิลาอันถาวร  ข้าฯไว้ใจทุกเวลา</verse3>
      <chorus>รอดอยู่ในหัตถ์พระเยซู   ใจข้าหยุดพักหมดห่วงที่นั่นร่มเย็นด้วยความรัก   รอดอยู่ภายในพระทรวง</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>รอดอยู่ภายในพระทรวงSafe in the arms of Jesus,safe on His gentle breast,There by His love o’ershaded,sweetly my soul shall rest. Hark! ’tis the voice of angels, borne in a song to me.Over the fields of glory, over the jasper sea.</verse1>
      <verse2>Safe in the arms of Jesus, safe from corroding care,Safe from the world’s temptations, sin cannot harm me there.พ้นจากสงสัยและความกลัว   Free from the blight of sorrow, free from my doubts and fears;Only a few more trials, only a few more tears!</verse2>
      <verse3>Jesus, my heart’s dear Refuge, Jesus has died for me;Firm on the Rock of Ages, ever my trust shall be.ทรงเป็นที่พึ่งให้ข้าฯรอด   Here let me wait with patience, wait till the night is over;Wait till I see the morning break on the golden shore.</verse3>
      <chorus>Safe in the arms of Jesus, safe on His gentle breastThere by His love o’ershaded, sweetly my soul shall rest.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
