<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ขอพระบิดาโปรดตรวจจิตใจข้า</thainame>
   <englishname>Search Me, O God</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ขอพระบิดา โปรดตรวจจิตใจของข้า ขอตรวจถ้วนถี่ พิสูจน์ความคิดในใจ ล้างให้สะอาด ทรงฟอกภายนอกภายใน ขอทรงนำข้าไป ตามทางนิรันดร</verse1>
      <verse2>ไม่ทรงเปลี่ยนแปลง ทั้งวันนี้และวันหน้า ขอประทับอยู่  ภายในดวงใจของข้า ขอทรงฟอกล้าง รอยด่างรอยชั่วนานา ขอทรงนำข้าไป  ตามทางนิรันดร</verse2>
      <verse3>โปรดดลใจข้า รักแต่พระเจ้าเท่านั้น ผู้ทรงพระชนม์ เป็นอยู่ไม่รู้แปรผัน ผูกใจข้ามั่น สนิทกับชาวสวรรค์ ขอทรงนำข้าไป ตามทางนิรันดร</verse3>
      <verse4>ให้งานของข้า ทนทานต่อการลองใจ ไม่เหมือนหญ้าแห้ง ถูกไฟก็ไหม้สลาย ทรงสร้างบ้านข้า อยู่บนศิลามั่นคง ขอทรงนำข้าไป ตามทางนิรันดร...</verse4>
      <chorus>ขอโปรดนำข้า ทรงนำข้าสู่ชีวิตนิรันดร ขอช่วยรั้งใจข้าเลิกรักสิ่งอนิจจัง โปรดประทานสิ่งบริสุทธิ์ซึ่งไม่สูญหาย ขอทรงนำข้าไปตามทางนิรันดร</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Search me, O God, search me and know my heart; Try me and prove me in the hidden part; Cleanse me and make me holy, as Thou art, And lead me in the way everlasting.</verse1>
      <verse2>Thou art the same today and yesterday; Oh, make Thy life in me the same alway; Take from my heart the things that pass away; Lead, lead me in the way everlasting.</verse2>
      <verse3>Take my poor heart and only let me love The things that always shall abiding prove; Bind all my heartstrings to the world above, And lead me in the way everlasting.</verse3>
      <verse4>Oh, let my work abide the testing day That shall consume the stubble and the hay; Oh, build my house upon the rock, I pray, And lead me in the way everlasting.</verse4>
      <chorus>Lead me, lead me, lead me in the way everlasting; Keep me from the things that wither and decay; Give to me the things that cannot pass away, And lead me in the way everlasting.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
