<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>องค์พระเยซูเกิดอยู่บ้านเบธเลเฮม</thainame>
   <englishname>Seeking for Me</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>องค์พระเยซูเกิดอยู่บ้านเบธเลเฮ็ม นอนในรางหญ้าต่างบัลลังก์สุขเกษม น่าประหลาดนักซึ่งทรงรักเรามากมาย รักเรามากมาย มากมาย รักเรามากมาย มากมาย รักเรามากมาย มากมาย น่าประหลาดนักซึ่งทรงรักเรามากมาย รักเรามากมาย มากมาย</verse1>
      <verse2>องค์พระเยซูประทับอยู่ในรางหญ้า อยู่กับวัวควายช่างน่าอายยิ่งนักหนา ลดพระเกียรติลงเพื่อทรงช่วยชาวโลกา ทรงมาไถ่บาป ไถ่บาป ทรงมาไถ่บาป ไถ่บาป ทรงมาไถ่บาป ไถ่บาป ลดพระเกียรติลงเพื่อทรงช่วยชาวโลกา ทรงมาไถ่บาป ไถ่บาป</verse2>
      <verse3>องค์พระเยซูถูกตรึงที่ไม้กางเขน รับโทษแทนเราให้พ้นจากบาปทุกข์เข็ญ พระกรุณานี้หาเปรียบไม่เทียบเท่า วายชนม์เพื่อเรา เพื่อเรา วายชนม์เพื่อเรา เพื่อเรา วายชนม์เพื่อเรา เพื่อเรา พระกรุณานี้หาเปรียบไม่เทียบเท่า วายชนม์เพื่อเรา เพื่อเรา</verse3>
      <verse4>องค์พระเยซูจะเสด็จกลับลงมา คำที่สัญญาคงสำเร็จในไม่ช้า ตาเราจะเห็นพระองค์ลงมาจากฟ้า กลับมารับเรา รับเรา กลับมารับเรา รับเรา กลับมารับเรา รับเรา ตาเราจะเห็นพระองค์ลงมาจากฟ้า กลับมารับเรา รับเรา...</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Jesus, my Savior, to Bethlehem came, Laid in a manger to sorrow and shame; Oh, it was wonderful, blest be His Name, Seeking for me, for me: Seeking for me, seeking for me, Seeking for me, seeking for me, Oh, it was wonderful, blest be His Name, Seeking for me, for me.</verse1>
      <verse2>Jesus, my Savior, in mercy and love, Came from the mansions of Heaven above, Tenderly pleading with sinners like me, Pleading for me, for me: Pleading for me, pleading for me, Pleading for me, pleading for me, Tenderly pleading for sinners like me, Pleading for me, for me.</verse2>
      <verse3>Jesus, my Savior, the same as of old, While I did wander afar from the fold, Gently and long He hath pled with my soul, Calling for me, for me: Calling for me, calling for me, Calling for me, calling for me, Gently and long He hath pled with my soul, Calling for me, for me.</verse3>
      <verse4>Jesus, my Savior, will come from on high, Sweet is the promise as weary years fly; Oh, I shall see Him descending the sky, Coming for me, for me: Coming for me, coming for me, Coming for me, coming for me, Oh, I shall see Him descending the sky, Coming for me, for me.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>
