<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ทหารของพระเยซูเจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>Stand Up,Stand Up for Jesus</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ทหารของพระเยซูเจ้า  จงเตรียมตัวไว้ให้พร้อม จงยืนต่อสู้หมู่มารร้าย  ร่างกายวายปราณก็ยอม ทำลายความชั่วให้ศูนย์ไป ด้วยฤทธิ์ของพระเยซู ออกรบชนะทุกครั้งไป   เพราะมีพระคริสต์ช่วยสู้</verse1>
      <verse2>ทหารของพระเยซูเจ้า จงเชื่อฟังพระวิญญาณ จงให้พระองค์ทรงนำทาง เหมือนแตรซึ่งเป็นสัญญาณ เมื่อเราต้องออกทำสงคราม  กับความเลวร้ายวุ่นวาย เราก็มีชัยไม่ต้องกลัว ความชั่วต้องถูกทำลาย</verse2>
      <verse3>ทหารของพระเยซูเจ้า ขอแรงจากพระบิดา เรี่ยวแรงมนุษย์ช่วยไม่ได้ อย่าหวังพึ่งในตนเอง อาศัยอำนาจพระดำรัส ตรัสแล้วใครเชื่อมีชัย จงทูลขอด้วยความแน่ใจ เพื่อให้สมน้ำพระทัย</verse3>
      <verse4>ทหารของพระเยซูเจ้า สงครามสงบเร็วไว วันนี้เสียงรบยังกึกก้อง รุ่งขึ้นเสียงร้องมีชัย ถ้าใครชนะแก่มารร้าย จะได้มงกุฎชีวิต แล้วอยู่กับพระเยซูเจ้า  ครอบครองสวรรค์เป็นนิจ อาเมน.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Stand up, stand up for Jesus, Ye soldiers of the cross; Lift high His royal banner, It must not suffer loss. From victory unto victory His army shall He lead; Till every foe is vanquished, And Christ is Lord indeed.</verse1>
      <verse2>Stand up, stand up for Jesus, The trumpet call obey; Forth to the mighty conflict, In this His glorious day. Ye that are brave now serve him  Against unnumbered foes; Let courage rise with danger,   And strength to strength oppose.</verse2>
      <verse3>Stand up, stand up for Jesus, Stand in His strength alone; The arm of flesh will fail you,   Ye dare not trust your own. Put on the gospel armor, Each piece put on with prayer; Where duty calls, or danger, Be never wanting there.</verse3>
      <verse4>Stand up, stand up for Jesus,  The strife will not be long; This day, the noise of battle, The next, the victor's song. To him who overcometh,  A crown of life shall be; He, with the King of Glory, Shall reign eternally.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>
