<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>งามขึ้นทุกเวลา</thainame>
   <englishname>Still Sweeter Every Day</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>พระเยซูทรงชักจูงดวงใจของข้าฯให้เข้ามาใกล้ พระองค์ทรงงามยิ่งกว่าท้องฟ้าเวลาอรุโณทัย แม้ภาพนั้นงามเพียงไรก็ตามพระองค์ยังทรงงามกว่า พระองค์ทรงงามมากขึ้นนักหนายิ่งงามขึ้นทุกเวลา</verse1>
      <verse2>พระรัศมีรุ่งเรืองของพระเยซูข้าฯเห็นแต่ไกล พระองค์งามกว่าดอกไม้และงามกว่าดาวรุ่งที่สุกใส ทรงบันดาลใจข้าฯให้อิ่มหนำสำราญเหลือพรรณนา พระองค์ทรงงามมากขึ้นนักหนายิ่งงามขึ้นทุกเวลา</verse2>
      <verse3>บางครั้งจิตใจชอกช้ำแต่พระเยซูทรงให้ทุเลา ทรงอุ้มตัวข้าฯแนบชิดไว้กับพระทรวงจนหายโศกเศร้า ข้าฯรักพระเยซูคริสต์เพราะทรงเป็นมิตรรับบาปของข้าฯ</verse3>
      <chorus>ไม่อาจบอกให้หมดความหมาย  ว่างามนักสักเพียงไร ยิ่งงามกว่านั้น เมื่อเราขึ้นไปถึงสวรรค์เมืองวิไล</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>To Jesus every day I find my heart is closer drawn, He’s fairer than the glory of the gold and purple dawn; He’s all my fancy pictures in its fairest dreams, and more, Each day He grows still sweeter than He was the day before.</verse1>
      <verse2>His glory broke upon me when I saw Him from afar, He’s fairer than the lily, brighter than the morning star; He fills and satisfies my longing spirit o’er and o’er, Each day He grows still sweeter than He was the day before.</verse2>
      <verse3>My heart is sometimes heavy, but He comes with sweet relief, He folds me to His bosom when I droop with blighting grief; I love the Christ Who all my burdens in His body bore,พระองค์ทรงงามมากขึ้นนักหนายิ่งงามขึ้นทุกเวลา Each day He grows still sweeter than He was the day before.</verse3>
      <chorus>The half cannot be fancied This side the golden shore; O there He’ll be still sweeter than He ever was before.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>