<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เมื่ออธิษฐาน</thainame>
   <englishname>Sweet Hour of Prayer</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>เมื่ออธิษฐานนมัสการ อัญเชิญพระองค์ทรงเป็นประธาน แม้ต้องอดอยากก็จงทูลขอ สิ่งที่จำเป็นประทานเพียงพอ  ถ้าถูกข่มเหงหรือมีโศกทุกข์ จิตใจบรรเทาได้รับความสุข  ถ้าถูกทดลองจิตใจเหนื่อยอ่อน  จะได้บรรเทาเมื่อเฝ้าอ้อนวอน</verse1>
      <verse2>เมื่ออธิษฐานเราแสนยินดี  คำทูลขึ้นถึงสวรรค์ทันที  พระเยซูคอยรับคำอ้อนวอน  ประทานพระพรแก่ผู้เหนื่อยอ่อน  เชิญเราเข้าเฝ้าต่อองค์พระเจ้า  เชื่อคำสัญญาที่ให้แก่เรา  ถวายความกลัวทุกข์ร้อนการงาน  พระองค์ทรงรับเมื่ออธิษฐาน</verse2>
      <verse3>เมื่ออธิษฐานเห็นอัศจรรย์  ได้การปลอบโยนเหมือนอยู่สวรรค์  เปรียบเหมือนขึ้นไปยอดเขาเกษม  เห็นบ้านของข้าน่าอยู่ปรีดิ์เปรม  อยากรีบเร่งไปเมืองสุขสำราญ  ไปเฝ้าพระองค์ผู้อภิบาล  ถวายสรรเสริญและรับพระพร  เมื่อนั้นก็เสร็จสิ้นการอ้อนวอน.</verse3>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Sweet hour of prayer! sweet hour of prayer!  that calls me from a world of care,  and bids me at my Father's throne make all my wants and wishes known. In seasons of distress and grief,  My soul has often found relief  And oft escaped the tempter's snare, by thy return, sweet hour of prayer!</verse1>
      <verse2>Sweet hour of prayer! sweet hour of prayer! Thy wings shall my petition bear To Him whose truth and faithfulness Engage the waiting soul to bless. And since He bids me seek His face, Believe His Word and trust His grace, I’ll cast on Him my every care, And wait for thee, sweet hour of prayer!</verse2>
      <verse3>Sweet hour of prayer! sweet hour of prayer! May I thy consolation share, Till, from Mount Pisgah’s lofty height, I view my home and take my flight: This robe of flesh I’ll drop and rise To seize the everlasting prize; And shout, while passing through the air, “Farewell, farewell, sweet hour of prayer!”</verse3>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </chord>
</song>
