<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ชีวิตข้าขอมอบถวาย</thainame>
   <englishname>Take My Life, And Let It Be</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ชีวิตข้าขอมอบถวาย สุดแต่พระเจ้าทรงนำไป วันเวลาที่ข้ามีอยู่ ข้ามอบไว้กับพระเยซู ข้ามอบไว้กับพระเยซู</verse1>
      <verse2>เท้าของข้าพระองค์ทรงสร้าง  ขอเดินตามที่ทรงชี้ทาง มือของข้าขอมอบไว้ให้ พระเจ้าโปรดใช้ตามพระทัย พระเจ้าโปรดใช้ตามพระทัย</verse2>
      <verse3>ให้ปากข้ารับพระดำรัส  กล้าประกาศเรื่องความรอดบาป ขอมอบเสียงร้องโมทนา แด่พระองค์ผู้เป็นราชา แด่พระองค์ผู้เป็นราชา</verse3>
      <verse4>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ชีวิตข้าขอมอบถวาย สุดแต่พระเจ้าทรงนำไป วันเวลาที่ข้ามีอยู่ ข้ามอบไว้กับพระเยซู ข้ามอบไว้กับพระเยซู  2.เท้าของข้าพระองค์ทรงสร้าง  ขอเดินตามที่ทรงชี้ทาง มือของข้าขอมอบไว้ให้ พระเจ้าโปรดใช้ตามพระทัย พระเจ้าโปรดใช้ตามพระทัย  3.ให้ปากข้ารับพระดำรัส  กล้าประกาศเรื่องความรอดบาป ขอมอบเสียงร้องโมทนา แด่พระองค์ผู้เป็นราชา แด่พระองค์ผู้เป็นราชา</verse4>
      <verse5>น้ำใจข้าขอมอบถวาย ข้าอยากตามแต่น้ำพระทัย ข้าถวายจิตวิญญาณกาย ขอมอบไว้จนชีพวางวาย ขอมอบไว้จนชีพวางวาย...</verse5>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Take my life and let it be consecrated, Lord, to thee. Take my moments and my days;  let them flow in endless praise, let them flow in endless praise.</verse1>
      <verse2>Take my hands and let them move at the impulse of thy love. Take my feet and let them be,  swift and beautiful for Thee, swift and beautiful for Thee.</verse2>
      <verse3>Take my voice, and let me sing Always, only, for my King; Take my lips, and let them be,  Filled with messages from Thee, Filled with messages from Thee.</verse3>
      <verse4>Music: Messiah, Lou­is J. Hér­old, 1830; ar­ranged by George Kings­ley, 1838 เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 230 ชีวิตข้าขอมอบถวาย (Take My Life, And Let It Be) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org Take my life and let it be consecrated, Lord, to thee. Take my moments and my days;  let them flow in endless praise, let them flow in endless praise. Take my hands and let them move at the impulse of thy love. Take my feet and let them be,  swift and beautiful for Thee, swift and beautiful for Thee. Take my voice, and let me sing Always, only, for my King; Take my lips, and let them be,  Filled with messages from Thee, Filled with messages from Thee.</verse4>
      <verse5>Take my will, and make it Thine; It shall be no longer mine. Take my heart; it is Thine own;  It shall be Thy royal throne, It shall be Thy royal throne.</verse5>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </chord>
</song>
