<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>รากฐานของคริสตจักรแท้</thainame>
   <englishname>The Church's One Foundation</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>รากฐานของคริสตจักรแท้คือ พระเยซูเจ้าพระบุตร พระองค์ทรงมารับคริสตจักร ให้เป็นเจ้าสาววิสุทธิ์ คำตรัสและน้ำพระทัยได้ แต่งตั้งคริสตจักรนั้นไว้ พระองค์ทรงสิ้นพระชนม์และ ยอมพลีโลหิตเพื่อไถ่</verse1>
      <verse2>ทรงเลือกชนจากทุกชาติตั้ง ให้เป็นคริสตจักรอันเดียว หลักความรอดของคริสตจักรนั้น คือเชื่อพระเจ้าองค์เดียว มีความหวังในพระคุณนั้น แซ่ซ้องสรรเสริญพระนาม ร่วมศีลสนิทบังเกิดใหม่ เปลี่ยนใจผ่องแผ้วแวววาม</verse2>
      <verse3>ทนทุกข์ลำบากความยากเข็ญ จำเป็นเข้าสู่สงคราม แล้วคริสตจักรรับความสุขแท้ เมื่อแพร่ความรอดทุกบ้าน จนกว่าบังเกิดความชื่นใจ แลเห็นชัดด้วยตาว่า คริสตจักรได้ชัยชนะแล้ว ผ่องแผ้วหยุดพักกายา</verse3>
      <verse4>เมื่อคริสตจักรอยู่ในโลกนี้ ก็รักพระองค์มากมาย ร่วมใจกับพระผู้ช่วยไถ่ ร่วมกับผู้เชื่อทั้งหลาย ที่ล่วงผ่านไปก่อนนานแล้ว ผ่องแผ้วอยู่ในวิมาน ขอพระองค์เทพระพรให้ จะไปอยู่ด้วยไม่นาน อาเมน.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>The church's one foundation is Jesus Christ her Lord;  she is His new creation by water and the Word.  From heaven He came and sought her to be His holy bride;  with His own blood he bought her, and for her life He died.</verse1>
      <verse2>Elect from every nation, yet one o'er all the earth;  her charter of salvation, one Lord, one faith, one birth;  one holy name she blesses, partakes one holy food,  and to one hope she presses, with every grace endued.</verse2>
      <verse3>’Mid toil and tribulation,And tumult of her war, She waits the consummation Of peace forevermore; Till, with the vision glorious,Her longing eyes are blest, And the great Church victorious Shall be the Church at rest.</verse3>
      <verse4>Yet she on earth hath union With God the Three in One, And mystic sweet communion With those whose rest is won, With all her sons and daughters Who, by the Master’s hand Led through the deathly waters, Repose in Eden land.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>