<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ผู้รับใช้พระเยซู</thainame>
   <englishname>The King’s Business</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าฯเป็นคนต่างเมืองมา บ้านข้าฯอยู่แคว้นแดนไกล  เขาเรียกว่าเมืองสวรรค์ เมืองนั้นไม่มีคนตาย   และเดี๋ยวนี้ตัวของข้าฯ เป็นทูตพระเยโฮวาห์  เป็นผู้รับใช้พระเยซูคริสต์</verse1>
      <verse2>เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่ 242 ผู้รับใช้พระเยซู  จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.ข้าฯเป็นคนต่างเมืองมา บ้านข้าฯอยู่แคว้นแดนไกล  เขาเรียกว่าเมืองสวรรค์ เมืองนั้นไม่มีคนตาย   และเดี๋ยวนี้ตัวของข้าฯ เป็นทูตพระเยโฮวาห์  เป็นผู้รับใช้พระเยซูคริสต์   ข่าวประเสริฐนี้ ข้าฯชอบประกาศ  เป็นข่าวความรอดให้คนพ้นบาป ให้คนทั้งหลายกลับใจ คืนดีกับองค์พระเจ้า พระคริสต์ตรัสว่า “จงมาหาเรา”</verse2>
      <verse3>บ้านในสวรรค์ก็มีสุขยิ่งกว่าในโลกนี้  ไร้ทุกข์และไร้ความโศกมีสุขตลอดเวลา  เหตุนี้พระองค์บัญชาให้ข้าฯมาป่าวประกาศ  ให้คนทุกชาติรู้ข่าวประเสริฐ</verse3>
      <chorus>ข่าวประเสริฐนี้ ข้าฯชอบประกาศ  เป็นข่าวความรอดให้คนพ้นบาป ให้คนทั้งหลายกลับใจ คืนดีกับองค์พระเจ้า พระคริสต์ตรัสว่า “จงมาหาเรา”</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>I am a stranger here, within a foreign land; My home is far away, upon a golden strand;  Ambassador to be of  realms beyond the sea, I’m here on business for my king.</verse1>
      <verse2>Music : Flora H. Cassel (The King’s Business) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org I am a stranger here, within a foreign land; My home is far away, upon a golden strand;  Ambassador to be of  realms beyond the sea, I’m here on business for my king. ร้องรับRefrain This is the message that I bring, A message angels fain would sing: Oh, be ye reconciled,Thus saith my Lord and king, Oh, be ye reconciled to God.</verse2>
      <verse3>My home is brighter far than Sharon’s rosy plain, Eternal life and joy throughout its vast domain; My sovereign bids me tell how mortals there may dwell, And that’s my business for my king.</verse3>
      <chorus>This is the message that I bring, A message angels fain would sing: Oh, be ye reconciled,Thus saith my Lord and king, Oh, be ye reconciled to God.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>