<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>พระนามเยซูเป็นที่ชูเชิด</thainame>
   <englishname>The  name  of  Jesus  Is  So  Sweet</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>พระนามเยซูเป็นที่ชูเชิด ข้าฯรักพระองค์ผู้ทรงล้ำเลิศ ซึ่งทำให้ข้าฯมีความสุขอยู่ พระนามประเสริฐพระเยซู</verse1>
      <verse2>ข้าฯรักพระนามพระองค์ทรงทราบ รับทุกข์ของข้าฯและยอมรับบาป   และทรงขับไล่ความกลัวทั้งหลาย ข้าฯรักพระนามพระเยซู</verse2>
      <verse3>ข้าฯรักพระองค์และยอมเชื่อฟัง พระองค์ปลอบโยนไม่ให้ผิดพลั้ง สรรเสริญพระนามพระเยซู</verse3>
      <verse4>ไม่มีแสงอาทิตย์ส่องอยู่ในเมืองสวรรค์ สว่างแห่งโลกคือพระเยซู พระองค์เป็นสว่างเมืองบนที่งามครัน   สว่างแห่งโลกคือพระเยซู</verse4>
      <chorus>พระนามพระเยซูประเสริฐ พระนามของพระองค์ล้ำเลิศ พระนามพระผู้บริสุทธิ์  สรรเสริญพระนามผู้สูงสุด</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>The  name  of  Jesus  is  so  sweet, I  love  its  music  to  repeat; It  makes  my  joys  full  and  complete,  The  precious  name  of  Jesus.</verse1>
      <verse2>I  love  the  name  of  Him  whose heart  Knows  all my  griefs and bears a part; Who  bids all anxious  fears depart, I  love  the name  of  Jesus.</verse2>
      <verse3>That  name  I  fondly  love  to  hear, It  never  fails  my  heart  to  cheer, ให้ข้าฯชื่นใจชีวิตผ่องใสn    Its  music  dries  the  falling  tear, Exalt  the  name  of  Jesus.</verse3>
      <verse4>No  word  of  man  can  ever  tell  How sweet  the  name  I  love so well, Oh,  let  its  praises  ever  swell,  Oh,  praise  the  name  of  Jesus.</verse4>
      <chorus>Jesus!  oh, how  sweet  the name. Jesus! every  day  the  same; Jesus! let  all saints  proclaim  Its  worthy  praise forever.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>