<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ไม้กางเขนโบราณ</thainame>
   <englishname>The Old Rugged Cross</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>บนภูเขาซึ่งอยู่ไกล ได้แลเห็นไม้กางเขน  เป็นรอยแห่งความทุกข์และความอาย แต่ใจข้าฯรักกางเขน ที่พระคริสต์ถูกตรึงตาย ไถ่คนบาปให้รอดพ้นจากอบาย</verse1>
      <verse2>ไม้กางเขนโบราณนั้น ชาวโลกพากันดูหมิ่น แต่ข้าฯรักกางเขนยิ่งนักหนา เพราะพระเยซูคริสตเจ้า สละเนาในเมืองฟ้า เสด็จมาเพื่อยอมตายบนกางเขน</verse2>
      <verse3>ที่กางเขนโบราณนั้น ข้าฯได้เห็นรัศมี พระโลหิตพระองค์ได้หลั่งไหล เพื่อจะได้ชำระบาป  ในตัวข้าฯให้สะอาด นั่นแหละคือไม้กางเขนโบราณนั้น</verse3>
      <verse4>ไม้กางเขนโบราณนั้น ยึดมั่นไว้จนวันตาย หากใครติเตียน ข้าฯไม่ละอาย เมื่อวันหนึ่งถึงเวลา พระองค์มารับข้าฯไป สู่สวรรค์อยู่ที่นั่นสำราญใจ</verse4>
      <chorus>:  โดยเหตุนี้ข้าฯจึงรักไม้กางเขน เพราะว่าเป็นที่จะวางภาระลง ข้าฯก็คงยึดกางเขนไว้ให้มั่น แล้ววันหนึ่งจะแลกเอามงกุฎงาม</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>On a hill far away stood an old rugged cross,  The emblem of suffering and shame;     And I love that old cross   where the dearest and best  For a world of lost sinners was slain.</verse1>
      <verse2>Oh, that old rugged cross,   so despised by the world, Has a wondrous attraction for me;     For the dear Lamb of God   left His glory above To bear it to dark Calvary.</verse2>
      <verse3>In the old rugged cross,  stained with blood so divine, A wondrous beauty I see,      For 'twas on that old cross   Jesus suffered and died  To pardon and sanctify me.</verse3>
      <verse4>To the old rugged cross  I will ever be true,  Its shame and reproach gladly bear;     Then He'll call me some day   to my home far away, Where His glory forever I'll share.</verse4>
      <chorus>So I'll cherish the old rugged cross,  Till my trophies at last I lay down; I will cling to the old rugged cross, And exchange it some day for a crown.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
