<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>แกะเก้าสิบเก้าตัว</thainame>
   <englishname>There Were Ninety and Nine </englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>แกะเก้าสิบเก้าตัวนอนสบาย ในคอกพ้นอันตราย แต่ตัวหนึ่งหลงหายไปจากฝูง อยู่ไกล ไม่รู้แห่งใด หลงทางอยู่ห่างพระเยซูเจ้า หลงจากผู้เลี้ยงผู้ทรงเมตตา หลงจากผู้เลี้ยงผู้ทรงเมตตา</verse1>
      <verse2>นับดูว่าเก้าสิบเก้าตัวมี แต่ไม่ทรงพอพระทัย ผู้ยังไม่หลง ก็คงไม่รู้ พระองค์ทรงรักเพียงไร พระองค์ติดตามมืดค่ำไม่ว่า ถ้าไม่ทรงช่วย แกะคงจะตาย ถ้าไม่ทรงช่วย แกะคงจะตาย</verse2>
      <verse3>ตามรอยพระบาทนั้นมีอะไร ซึ่งเห็นที่เนินภูเขา เป็นรอยโลหิตของพระผู้ไถ่ ซึ่งไหลไถ่บาปของเรา ทำไมพระหัตถ์จึงบวมและช้ำ เพราะถูกหนามตำ เมื่อตามแกะไป เพราะถูกหนามตำ เมื่อตามแกะไป</verse3>
      <verse4>ทั่วบรรพตชั้น มีเสียงฟ้าลั่น ทรงร้องบอกบนภูเขา ว่าดีพระทัย พบแกะตัวนั้น กลับมาสู่คอกดังเก่า ฝ่ายทูตสวรรค์ร้องเพลงยินดี เพราะแกะที่หายไปกลับมาแล้ว เพราะแกะที่หายไปกลับมาแล้ว.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>There were ninety and nine that safely lay in the shelter of the fold.  But one was out on the hills away, far off from the gates of gold. Away on the mountains wild and bare. Away from the tender Shepherd's care.  Away from the tender Shepherd's care.</verse1>
      <verse2>&quot;Lord, thou hast here thy ninety and nine; are they not enough for thee?&quot;  But the Shepherd made answer: “This of mine has wandered away from me;  and although the road be rough and steep,  I go to the desert to find my sheep,  I go to the desert to find my sheep.&quot;</verse2>
      <verse3>&quot;Lord, whence are those blood-drops all the way, That mark out the mountain's track?&quot; &quot;They were shed for one who had gone astray Ere the Shepherd could bring him back.&quot; &quot;Lord, whence are Thy hands so rent and torn?&quot; &quot;They're pierced tonight by many a thorn.&quot; &quot;They're pierced tonight by many a thorn.&quot;</verse3>
      <verse4>But all through the mountains, thunder riven  and up from the rocky steep,  there arose a cry to the gate of heaven,  &quot;Rejoice! I have found My sheep!&quot;  and the angels echoed around the throne,  &quot;Rejoice, for the Lord brings back His own!  rejoice, for the Lord brings back His own!&quot;</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>