<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
         <!--Edited-->

   <thainame>ไม่มีหว่างเขามืดเมื่อพระเยซูมา</thainame>
   <englishname>There’ll be no dark valley</englishname>
   <mienthainame>เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย ต๋อง หฮมวัง.</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus,verse5,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ไม่มีหว่างเขามืดเมื่อพระเยซูมา ไม่มีหว่างเขามืดเมื่อพระเยซูมา แต่เป็นวันรุ่งเรืองเมื่อพระเยซูมา จะรวมเราไปสวรรค์</verse1>
      <verse2>ไม่มีทุกข์โศกเศร้าเมื่อพระเยซูมา  ไม่มีทุกข์โศกเศร้าเมื่อพระเยซูมา แต่เป็นวันชมชื่นเมื่อพระเยซูมา จะรวมเราไปสวรรค์</verse2>
      <verse3>ไม่มีการร้องไห้เมื่อพระเยซูมา ไม่มีการร้องไห้เมื่อพระเยซูมา แต่จะรับพระพรเมื่อพระเยซูมา จะรวมเราไปสวรรค์</verse3>
      <verse4>ไม่มีความป่วยไข้เมื่อพระเยซูมา ไม่มีความป่วยไข้เมื่อพระเยซูมา แต่จะรับความสุขเมื่อพระเยซูมา จะรวมเราไปสวรรค์</verse4>
      <verse5>จะมีเพลงต้อนรับเมื่อพระเยซูมา จะมีเพลงต้อนรับเมื่อพระเยซูมา  และประชุมรื่นเริงเมื่อพระเยซูมา จะรวมเราไปสวรรค์</verse5>
      <chorus>จะรวมเราไปสวรรค์ จะรวมเราไปสวรรค์  ไม่มีหว่างเขามืดเมื่อพระเยซูมาจะรวมเราไปสวรรค์</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>There’ll be no dark valley when Jesus comes, There’ll be no dark valley when Jesus comes; There’ll be no dark valley when Jesus comes To gather His loved ones home.</verse1>
      <verse2>There’ll be no more sorrow when Jesus comes, There’ll be no more sorrow when Jesus comes; But a glorious morrow when Jesus comes To gather His loved ones home.</verse2>
      <verse3>There’ll be no more weeping when Jesus comes, There’ll be no more weeping when Jesus comes; But a blessèd reaping when Jesus comes To gather His loved ones home.</verse3>
      <verse4>There’ll be no more hurting when Jesus comes, There’ll be no more hurting when Jesus comes; But a blessèd reaping when Jesus comes To gather His loved ones home.</verse4>
      <verse5>There’ll be songs of greeting when Jesus comes, There’ll be songs of greeting when Jesus comes; And a joyful meeting when Jesus comes To gather His loved ones home.</verse5>
      <chorus>To gather His loved ones home, To gather His loved ones home; There’ll be no dark valley when Jesus comes To gather His loved ones home.</chorus>
   </english>
<mienthai>
    <verse1>เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย ต๋อง หฮมวัง. เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย ต๋อง หฮมวัง. เก้ง ฌัง-หล่าง เจี๋ย เญย ฮนอย, เฒี้ยว เย^ซู ต้าย. เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง.</verse1>
    <verse2>เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย โยว-เฑ่า. เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย โยว-เฑ่า. หฒะเก้ง ออน-เหลาะ, เฌียน-โย่ว, เฒี้ยว เย^ซู ต้าย, เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง.</verse2>
    <verse3>เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ หฒุ เหลาะ เหลว่ย. เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่. ไม้ หฒุ เหลาะ เหลว่ย. เย^ซู หฒอย เหฌี่ย ป้าม เกน ต้าย เหธย เอน ปุน, เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง.</verse3>
    <verse4>เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย เหฒะ หน่าน. เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย เหฒะ หน่าน. เย^ซู อ๋อย หฒ่อ หลง เหฑ่ง เยีย บัว เญย แป่ง, เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง.</verse4>
    <verse5>เยีย บัว ปวัด เฒี้ยว เย^ซู, ฯฒฯ ป๋าว ฑูง เธง. เยีย บัว ปวัด เฒี้ยว เย^ซู, ฯฒฯ ป๋าว ฑูง เธง. ทิน- ต้อง เหน่า หญิด เฌียน-โย่ว เหว่ย เฒี้ยว เญย เอน, เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง.</verse5>
    <chorus>เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง, เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง. เย^ซู หฒอย ต้าย เฒี่ยง โห่, ไม้ ม่าย ต๋อง หฮมวัง, เยีย บัว ตุ๊ ฝาว ทิน-ต้อง.</chorus>
</mienthai>

<chord>
    <verse1>D   D    G   D    D    D   A    A    D    D    G    G   D    A   D</verse1>
    <verse2>D   D    G   D    D    D   A    A    D    D    G    G   D    A   D</verse2>
    <verse3>D   D    G   D    D    D   A    A    D    D    G    G   D    A   D</verse3>
    <verse4>D   D    G   D    D    D   A    A    D    D    G    G   D    A   D</verse4>
    <verse5>D   D    G   D    D    D   A    A    D    D    G    G   D    A   D</verse5>
    <chorus>D   D   D     A   D   D   D   G   G  D  A   D</chorus>
</chord>
</song>