<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ลุกช่วงโชติในใจข้า</thainame>
   <englishname>'Tis Burning in My Soul</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>พระเจ้าทรงโปรดประทาน อำนาจฤทธิ์เดชลงมา เพื่อทรงพิทักษ์รักษา พระคุณทรงโปรดให้ข้าฯ เมื่อพระวิญญาณลงมา เพื่อทรงเป็นผู้บัญชา ความรักรุ่งเรืองนักหนา ลุกช่วงโชติในใจข้าฯ</verse1>
      <verse2>ยืนอยู่ตรงหน้ากางเขน วางลงบนแท่นบูชา  ยอมสักการบูชา ทุกสิ่งในชีวิตข้าฯ พระองค์ทรงใช้หนี้ข้าฯ เรียกชื่อไพเราะนักหนา พระเพลิงสวรรค์ลงมา บนเครื่องถวายบูชา</verse2>
      <verse3>ไม่ใช่ความดีของข้าฯ แต่เป็นตามพระสัญญา ยอมรับองค์พระบุตรา รอดโดยพระคุณนั้นนา ถวายบทเพลงสรรเสริญ ร้องว่าอาเลลูยา ความรักแผ่ทุกทิศ พระเพลิงลุกในใจข้าฯ</verse3>
      <chorus>ลุกช่วงโชติในใจข้าฯ ลุกช่วงโชติในใจข้าฯ พระเพลิงแห่งฟ้าสวรรค์ ลุกช่วงโชติในใจข้าฯ เมื่อพระวิญญาณลงมา ทุกคนสรรเสริญวันทา พระเพลิงแห่งฟ้าสวรรค์ ลุกช่วงโชติในใจข้าฯ</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>God sent His mighty pow'r  To this poor, sinful heart, To keep me ev'ry hour, And needful grace impart; And since His Spirit came, To take supreme control, The love enkindled flame  Is burning in my soul.</verse1>
      <verse2>Before the cross I bow,  Upon the altar lay A willing off'ring now, My all from day to day. My Savior paid the price, My name He sweetly calls;  Upon the sacrifice The fire from Heaven falls.</verse2>
      <verse3>No good that I have done,  His promise I embrace; Accepted in the Son,  He saves me by His grace. All glory be to God!  Let hallelujahs roll; His love is shed abroad, The fire is in my soul.</verse3>
      <chorus>'Tis burning in my soul, 'Tis burning in my soul; The fire of heav'nly love is burning in my soul, The Holy Spirit came,  All glory to His name! The fire of heav'nly love is burning in my soul.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>