<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าฯขอติดตามพระเยซูดีกว่า</thainame>
   <englishname>‘Tis Better Far to Follow Jesus</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าฯขอติดตามพระเยซูดีกว่า  ไม่ว่านำทางไหนข้าฯจะตาม  โลกนี้มีความสุขซึ่งอาจสูญได้  แต่ข้าฯกระหายสิ่งซึ่งไม่ตาย  พระเจ้าสร้างเราเพื่อเกียรติพระองค์เอง  และทรงยินดีไม่มีเสื่อมคลาย  ติดตามพระเยซูชื่นชูดวงใจ  เพราะว่าทรงทำให้ข้าอิ่มใจ</verse1>
      <verse2>มาตรแม้นขวากหนามมีอยู่ในทางเดิน  หรือต้องเผชิญทุกข์โศกมืดมัว  ข้าฯไม่กลัวเพราะพระองค์อยู่เคียงข้าง   นำไปถึงปลายทางโดยปลอดภัย  ทรงทนอับอายขายหน้าเพื่อตัวข้าฯ   ยอมพลีโลหิตไถ่ข้าฯจนตาย  ชื่นใจเพราะว่าข้าฯได้ร่วมลำบาก   เหนื่อยยากเพียงไรพระองค์อยู่ใกล้</verse2>
      <verse3>ข้าฯตามพระเยซูด้วยความเต็มใจ ทุกข์ร้อนเพียงไหนข้าฯก็ไม่กลัว มืดมัวปวดร้าวดวงใจก็ยอมทน เพราะว่าเหล่าทูตสวรรค์ปลอบโยน แม้ว่าจะขมจะขื่นข้าฯกลืนได้ เพราะว่าภายหลังกลายเป็นชมชื่น จะทนความทุกข์ความเจ็บแม้ความตาย ไม่ช้าข้าฯไปสวรรค์สบาย...</verse3>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>'Tis better far to follow Jesus  No matter where His hand may lead;  Than with the world's vain fleeting pleasures Our souls’ immortal longings feed; For He has made us for His glory  And His are joys that never die;  'Tis sweeter far to follow Jesus,  For He alone can satisfy.</verse1>
      <verse2>What matter if  the way be thorny,  Or if dark waves of sorrow roll? Beside me walks my loving Saviour And I shall safely reach the goal; For me He bore the thorns and scoffing, It was for me He bled and died;  'Tis sweet that I may share His sorrow And walk forever at His side.</verse2>
      <verse3>What matter if I stand at Calvery And lay my life down for the lost?  'Twas only what He did before me, I’ll follow Him at any cost;  Then from the pain,and shame and dying, In glorious power I’ll rise again To share the glory of His kingdom And evermore with Jesus reign</verse3>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
   </chord>
</song>