<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>แสนชื่นใจที่เชื่อพระเยซู</thainame>
   <englishname>Tis So Sweet to Trust in Jesus</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>แสนชื่นใจที่เชื่อพระเยซู คือรักษาพระธรรมพระองค์ และไว้ใจในพระสัญญานั้น ซึ่งพระองค์ตรัสแล้วมั่นคง   ***ผู้ช่วย ผู้ช่วย คือพระเยซู ข้าฯไว้ใจผู้ทรงปราณี ผู้ช่วย ผู้ช่วย องค์พระเยซู โปรดประทานความเชื่อทวี</verse1>
      <verse2>จัดทำขึ้นเพื่อจะเป็นประโยชน์ให้กับพี่น้องคริสเตียนทุกท่าน  ในการฝึกร้องเพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน  1.แสนชื่นใจที่เชื่อพระเยซู คือรักษาพระธรรมพระองค์ และไว้ใจในพระสัญญานั้น ซึ่งพระองค์ตรัสแล้วมั่นคง   ***ผู้ช่วย ผู้ช่วย คือพระเยซู ข้าฯไว้ใจผู้ทรงปราณี ผู้ช่วย ผู้ช่วย องค์พระเยซู โปรดประทานความเชื่อทวี</verse2>
      <verse3>แสนหรรษาเมื่อเชื่อพระเยซู ได้ทิ้งบาปถวายใจกาย รับชีวิตจากองค์พระเยซู ได้พักผ่อนใจสุขสบาย</verse3>
      <verse4>ข้าฯยินดีวางใจพระเยซู พระผู้ช่วยประเสริฐเหลือหลาย ข้าฯเชื่อว่าพระองค์สถิตอยู่ และทรงอยู่ด้วยจนสุดปลาย</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>'Tis so sweet to trust in Jesus, Just to take Him at His word; Just to rest upon His promise; Just to know&quot;Thus saith the Lord.&quot; Jesus, Jesus, how I trust Him! How I've proved Him o'er and o'er! Jesus, Jesus, precious Jesus! O for grace to trust Him more!</verse1>
      <verse2>Stead is said to have written these words after witnessing her husband drown. Music: William J. Kirkpatrick เพลงชีวิตคริสเตียน บทที่  148 แสนชื่นใจที่เชื่อพระเยซู  (Tis So Sweet to Trust in Jesus) ผลิตโดย คริสตจักรตรัง www.trangchurch.org 'Tis so sweet to trust in Jesus, Just to take Him at His word; Just to rest upon His promise; Just to know&quot;Thus saith the Lord.&quot; Jesus, Jesus, how I trust Him! How I've proved Him o'er and o'er! Jesus, Jesus, precious Jesus! O for grace to trust Him more!</verse2>
      <verse3>Yes, 'tis sweet to trust in Jesus, Just from sin and self to cease; Just from Jesus simply taking Life and rest, and joy and peace.</verse3>
      <verse4>I'm so glad I learned to trust Thee, Precious Jesus, Saviour, Friend; And I know that Thou art with me, Wilt be with me to the end.</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>