<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>สรรเสริญแด่พระเจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>To God Be the Glory</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าฯขอถวายเกียรติแด่พระเจ้าผู้ยิ่งใหญ่ พระองค์ได้ประทาน พระบุตรเพื่อเป็นค่าไถ่ โดยยอมพลีพระชนม์ ไถ่บาปเราที่กางเขน เพื่อให้เราทุกคนทุกชาติหมดบาปหมดเวร</verse1>
      <verse2>ความรอดอันสมบูรณ์  เราได้เพราะโลหิตไถ่  ผู้ใดเชื่อพระสัญญา จะรับชีวิตใหม่ คนบาปจะเลวร้าย สักเท่าใดก็รอดได้ พระเยซูประทานความรอดแก่ผู้วางใจ</verse2>
      <verse3>พระองค์สอนถึงสิ่งใหญ่ซึ่งได้ทรงกระทำ ยินดีที่พระเยซูพระบุตรเป็นผู้นำ ประหลาดใจนักหนาเมื่อเราเห็นพระเยซู เป็นผู้บริสุทธิ์ยิ่งใหญ่ซึ่งเราเฝ้าดู</verse3>
      <chorus>สรรเสริญ สรรเสริญ  แด่พระเจ้าด้วยยินดี สรรเสริญแด่พระเจ้า จงให้ชาวโลกยินดี เชิญมาเฝ้าพระเจ้าโดยพระนามพระเยซู ถวายเกียรติพระองค์ผู้ทรงเมตตาเอ็นดู</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>To God be the glory,great things He has done;  So loved He the world that He gave us His Son, Who yielded His life an atonement for sin, And opened the life gate that all may go in.</verse1>
      <verse2>O perfect redemption,the purchase of blood, To every believer the promise of God;  The vilest offender who truly believes, That moment from Jesus a pardon receives.</verse2>
      <verse3>Great things He has taught us, great things He has done,    And great our rejoicing through Jesus the Son; But purer, and higher, and greater will be Our wonder, our transport, when Jesus we see.</verse3>
      <chorus>Praise the Lord, praise the Lord,  Let the earth hear His voice! Praise the Lord, praise the Lord, Let the people rejoice! O come to the Father through Jesus the Son, And give Him the glory, great things He has done.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>