<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เราเป็นคนทำงานของพระเจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>To  the  Harvest  Field</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>เราเป็นคนทำงานของพระเจ้า พระองค์ยินดีร่วมงานกับเรา ช่วยนำวิญญาณที่หิวกระหาย ไปช่วยคนให้รอดพ้นอบาย วิญญาณดวงเดียวมีค่าล้ำเลิศ นำมาถวายแด่ผู้ประเสริฐ คือพระบิดาผู้ได้ประทาน พระบุตรไถ่โทษให้พ้นจากมาร</verse1>
      <verse2>เรานำวิญญาณไม่ยอมท้อถอย ทำตามบัญชาไม่ต้องรอคอย ไม่ย่อท้อแต่สัตย์ซื่ออดทน เพราะพวกเรามีอยู่แต่น้อยคน ธงไม้กางเขนโบกปลิวไสว ช่วยกู้วิญญาณให้รอดจากตาย พระสุรเสียงตรัสสั่งบอกชี้ ว่าให้เราไปทำงานวันนี้</verse2>
      <verse3>วันคืนเดือนปีไม่รอคอยท่า ไม่รู้เมื่อไรจะสิ้นชีวา จงรีบแบกเคียวไปทำการเกี่ยว เสร็จแล้วรับมงกุฎแน่ทีเดียว ทำไมจึงรอหลบหลีกอยู่ช้า คนกำลังตายทุกวันเวลา ไปเฝ้าพระเจ้าด้วยมือเปล่าหรือ ไม่นำวิญญาณอื่นถวายหรือ</verse3>
      <chorus>ไปเถอะไปยังโลกกว้างใหญ่ เพราะพระองค์ทรงเรียกใช้ ไปทำการทุกคนวันนี้ ถ้าช้าเวลาไม่มี วันและคืนไม่คอยใครเลย  เดือนและปีล่วงไปอย่าเฉย รีบไป รีบไป รีบไปนำวิญญาณ</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>A band of faithful reapers we, Who gather for eternity The golden sheaves of ripened grain From ev’ry valley, hill and plain: Our song is one the reapers sing, In honor of the Lord and King— The Master of the harvest wide, Who for a world of sinners died.</verse1>
      <verse2>We are a faithful gleaning band, And labor at our Lord’s command, Unyielding, loyal, tried and true, For lo! the reapers are but few: Behold the waving harvest-field Abundant with a golden yield; And hear the Lord of harvest say To all, “Go reap for Me today.”</verse2>
      <verse3>The golden hours like moments fly, And harvest days are passing by; Then take thy rusty sickle down, And labor for a fadeless crown: Why will you idly stand and wait? Behold, the hour is growing late! Can you to judgment bring but leaves, While here are waiting golden sheaves?</verse3>
      <chorus>To the harvest field away, For the Master calleth; There is work for all today, Ere the darkness falleth. Swiftly do the moments fly, Harvest days are going by, Going, going, going, going by.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
