<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เชื่อและฟังคำ</thainame>
   <englishname>Trust and Obey</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ถ้าเราเดินตามพระเจ้า พระเยซูทรงนำเรา และประทานรัศมีให้อิ่มหนำ เมื่อเราทำตามพระทัย พระองค์สถิตในใจ ของทุกคนที่ยอมเชื่อและฟังคำ</verse1>
      <verse2>ไม่มีทุกข์เกิดขึ้นได้ ไม่มีมืดในจิตใจ เพราะอำนาจของพระคริสต์ขับไล่ไป  ไม่ต้องกลัวหรือสงสัย ไม่มีโศกเศร้าร้องไห้ มาแผ้วพานเมื่อเราเชื่อและฟังคำ</verse2>
      <verse3>ถ้าเรามีความลำบาก หรือถ้ามีความทุกข์ยาก พระเยซูทรงช่วยให้พ้นมารร้าย  หากมีความทุกข์เหลือหลาย ไม่ต้องยากซ้ำช้ำใจ พระองค์ช่วยผู้ที่เชื่อและฟังคำ</verse3>
      <verse4>ความสัมพันธ์อันชื่นใจ จะนั่งใกล้พระบาทไท้ เราจะเดินอยู่เคียงข้างพระผู้ไถ่  ให้ไปไหนเต็มใจไป ยินดีทำตามพระทัย ไม่ต้องกลัวแต่จงเชื่อและฟังคำ</verse4>
      <chorus>เชื่อและฟังคำ ไม่มีทางอื่นเที่ยงธรรม พระเยซูโปรดให้ความสุข แก่ผู้เชื่อและฟังคำ</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>When we walk with the Lord,  In the light of His Word, What a glory He sheds on our way!  While we do His good will, He abides with us still, And with all who will trust and obey.</verse1>
      <verse2>Not a shadow can rise, Not a cloud in the skies,  But His smile quickly drives it away;  Not a doubt nor a fear, Not a sigh nor a tear, Can abide while we trust and obey.</verse2>
      <verse3>Not a burden we bear, Not a sorrow we share, But our toil He doth richly repay;  Not a grief or a loss, Not a frown or a cross, But is blest if we trust and obey.</verse3>
      <verse4>Then in fellowship sweet We will sit at His feet, Or we'll walk by His side in the way;  What He says we will do, Where He sends we will go Never fear, only trust and obey!</verse4>
      <chorus>Trust and obey! For there's no other way To be happy in Jesus, But to trust and obey.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
