<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าฯยินดีที่วันนั้นทรงเมตตา</thainame>
   <englishname>’Twas a Glad Day</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3>ยินดีเมื่อได้พบสหายที่คอยท่าในวิมานของพระบิดาซึ่งอยู่เมืองฟ้าเราจะสนทนาถึงเรื่องพระเมตตาที่พระองค์พลีพระชนม์เพื่อข้าฯ</verse3>
      <chorus/>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>เมื่อพระคริสต์พบข้าฯกำลังทำบาปหนาเมื่อพระองค์ช่วยให้รอด ข้าฯก็โมทนาความสนุกของโลกนี้ผูกมัดข้าฯไว้แต่ทรงช่วยให้พ้นบาป พ้นอายI was lost in sin when Jesus found me,But He rescued me, all glory to His name!And the cords of worldly pleasure bound me,Till He saved me from sin and shame.</verse1>
      <verse2>จากสวรรค์ข้าฯได้ยินเสียงระฆังดังและได้ยินเสียงนั้นด้วยหูแห่งจิตวิญญาณพระเยซูทรงให้ใจข้าฯมีเพลงชัยคือวันที่บาปหลุดพ้นจากใจO the bells of Heaven now are ringing,For I hear their tones within my ransomed soul;And my heart is filled with joyful singingSince the Savior has made me whole.</verse2>
      <verse3>O the joy when we shall meet in glory,In the mansions of my Father’s home above;And through endless ages tell the storyOf the Savior’s redeeming love.</verse3>
      <chorus>ข้าฯยินดีที่วันนั้นทรงเมตตาเมื่อได้ทรงยื่นพระหัตถ์ออกรับข้าฯในทะเลใหญ่เอาความบาปของข้าฯทิ้งไว้ใจข้าฯเปี่ยมล้นด้วยความยินดีเพราะมีชัยข้าฯยินดีร้องเพลงอาเลลูยารับข้าฯเป็นบุตรตามพระสัญญาข้าฯจะร้องเพลงอาเลลูยาในเมืองฟ้าตรงพระที่นั่งอันทรงสง่า’Twas a glad day when Jesus found me,When His strong arms were thrown around me;When my sins He buried in the deepest sea,And my soul He filled with joy and victory.’Twas a glad day, O hallelujah!’Twas a glad day He claimed His own.I will shout a glad hosanna in gloryWhen I see Him upon His throne.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
