<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>

<thainame>มีสหายเลิศคือพระเยซู</thainame>
<englishname>What a Friend we have in Jesus</englishname>
<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
<order>verse1,verse2,verse3</order>

<thai>
    <verse1>มีสหายเลิศคือพระเยซู ผู้ได้แบกบาปทุกข์ของเรา มีอะไรรบกวนให้โศกเศร้า จงรีบเร่งนำมาเข้าเฝ้า เหตุไฉนเราลืมพระเจ้าบ่อย ใจเป็นทุกข์โดยไม่มีเหตุ เพราะการไหว้วอนเราได้ท้อถอย ไม่ได้ทูลผู้ทรงฤทธิ์เดช</verse1>
    <verse2>เราเป็นทุกข์เพราะถูกล่อลวงหรือ เคยเดือนร้อนลำบากหรือเปล่า ไม่ควรย่อท้อหรือใจห่อเหี่ยว แต่เร่งนำทุกสิ่งเข้าเฝ้า เราจะหาสหายที่วางใจ แก้ความทุกข์ลำบากเราได้ เพราะพระเยซูทราบความทุกข์นั้น จงทูลทุกสิ่งต่อพระองค์</verse2>
    <verse3>เมื่อเหน็ดเหนื่อยเพราะแบกภาระหนัก เหลือกำลังและเราหมดแรง ผู้ประเสริฐทรงช่วยศิษย์ที่รัก ให้เราอ้อนวอนต่อพระองค์ ถ้าสหายดูหมิ่นเกลียดชังท่าน จงเร่งนำทุกสิ่งเข้าเฝ้า แล้วทรงยื่นพระหัตถ์รับท่านไว้ ท่านจึงได้รับความบรรเทา</verse3>

</thai>

<english>
    <verse1>What a Friend we have in Jesus, All our sins and griefs to bear. What a privilege to carry. Everything to God in prayer. O what peace we often forfeit, O what needless pain we bear, All because we do not carry. Everything to God in prayer.</verse1>
    <verse2>Have we trials and temptations. Is there trouble anywhere. We should never be discouraged, Take it to the Lord in prayer. Can we find a friend so faithful. Who will all our sorrows share. Jesus knows our every weakness, Take it to the Lord in prayer.</verse2>
    <verse3>Are we weak and heavy-laden, Cumbered with a load of care. Precious Savior, still our refuge. Take it to the Lord in prayer; Do thy friends despise, forsake thee. Take it to the Lord in prayer; In His arms He’ll take and shield thee, Thou wilt find a solace there.</verse3>

</english>
    
<mienthai>
    <verse1></verse1>
    <verse2></verse2>
    <verse3></verse3>

</mienthai>

<chord>
    <verse1>D G D Bm Em-A D G Abdim D A D A D D7 G F#m Em- A D G Abdim D A D</verse1>
    <verse2>D G D Bm Em-A D G Abdim D A D A D D7 G F#m Em- A D G Abdim D A D</verse2>
    <verse3>D G D Bm Em-A D G Abdim D A D A D D7 G F#m Em- A D G Abdim D A D</verse3>

</chord>

</song>