<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา</thainame>
   <englishname>What a wonderful Savior!</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus,verse5,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>พระคริสต์ทรงช่วยเราพ้นความบาป อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา</verse1>
      <verse2>ประทานพระโลหิตอันประเสริฐ อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา</verse2>
      <verse3>พระองค์ทรงช่วยให้เราพ้นภัย อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา</verse3>
      <verse4>ทรงโปรดประทานให้พระวิญญาณ อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา</verse4>
      <verse5>เรามอบจิตใจถวายพระองค์ อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา เต็มใจเดินตามและเชื่อมั่นคง อัศจรรย์พระผู้ช่วยเรา</verse5>
      <chorus>อัศจรรย์พระเยซู เป็นผู้ช่วยอัศจรรย์</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Christ has for sin atonement made  What a wonderful Savior! ทรงไถ่เราไว้ ทรงชำระบาป We are redeemed, the price is paid  What a wonderful Savior!</verse1>
      <verse2>I praise Him for the cleansing blood, What a wonderful Savior! เราเป็นมิตรกับผู้ช่วยดีเลิศ That reconciled my soul to God. What a wonderful Savior!</verse2>
      <verse3>He cleansed my heart from all its sin What a wonderful Savior! เดี๋ยวนี้พระองค์ประทานในใจ And now He reigns and rules therein; What a wonderful Savior!</verse3>
      <verse4>He gives me overcoming power What a wonderful Savior! ทรงช่วยให้พ้นอำนาจของมาร He gives me overcoming power What a wonderful Savior!</verse4>
      <verse5>To Him I've given all my heart: What a wonderful Savior! The world shall never share a part: What a wonderful Savior!</verse5>
      <chorus>What a wonderful Savior is Jesus, my Jesus!               What a wonderful Savior is Jesus, my Lord!</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
