<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>

<thainame>ถ้าพระเยซูเสด็จมาวันนี้</thainame>
<englishname>What If It Were Today?</englishname>
<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
<order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>

<thai>
    <verse1>ถ้าพระเยซูเสด็จมาวันนี้ พวกเราจะว่าอย่างไร ถ้าพระเยซูกลับมาด้วยราศี พวกเราจะว่าอย่างไร รับคริสเตียนที่ได้ทรงเลือกไว้ คือสิทธชนสะอาดสดใส มีอยู่ทั่วไปในโลกกว้างใหญ่ พระองค์อาจมาวันนี้</verse1>
    <verse2>แล้วอาณาจักรมารต้องถูกทำลาย เราอยากให้เป็นวันนี้ เราอยากให้เป็นวันนี้ ผู้ตายในพระเยซูฟื้นชีพ เข้าสู่สง่าราศียิ่งใหญ่ เมื่อไหร่จะเห็นเหตุการณ์อย่างนี้ ถ้าเป็นวันนี้จะดี</verse2>
    <verse3>พระองค์ทรงเห็นเราสัตย์ซื่อหรือเปล่า ถ้าพระองค์มาวันนี้ ไม่ต้องกลัวเมื่อเรายังคอยเฝ้าอยู่ พระองค์อาจมาวันนี้ เครื่องหมายหลายอย่างบอกเหตุการณ์นี้ คือพระเยซูเสด็จกลับมา จงเฝ้าคอยท่าพระองค์จะมา ถ้าเป็นวันนี้จะดี</verse3>
    <chorus>ชื่นใจยินดี ใจเราชื่นชมยินดี ชื่นใจยินดี สรรเสริญพระบารมี ชื่นใจยินดี ถวายพระเกียรติราศี ชื่นใจยินดี พระองค์อาจมาวันนี้</chorus>
</thai>

<english>
    <verse1>Jesus is coming to earth again. What if it were today? Coming in power and love to reign. What if it were today? Coming to claim His chosen Bride, All the redeemed and purified, Over this whole earth scattered wide. What if it were today?</verse1>
    <verse2>Satan's dominion will then be o'er. O that it were today! Sorrow and sighing shall be no more. O that it were today! Then shall the dead in Christ arise, Caught up to meet Him in the skies; When shall these glories meet our eyes? What if it were today?</verse2>
    <verse3>Faithful and true would He find us here. If He should come today? Watching in gladness and not in fear, If He should come today? Signs of His coming multiply, Morning light breaks in eastern sky; Watch, for the time is drawing nigh. What if it were today?</verse3>
    <chorus>Glory, glory! Joy to my heart 'twill bring; Glory, glory! When we shall crown Him King. Glory, glory! Haste to prepare the way; Glory, glory! Jesus will come someday.</chorus>
</english>
    
<mienthai> 
</mienthai>

<chord>
    <verse1>C G7 G7 C C F Dm C G F G7 C</verse1>
    <verse2>C G7 G7 C C F Dm C G F G7 C</verse2>
    <verse3>C G7 G7 C C F Dm C G F G7 C</verse3>
    <chorus>C G/B Am Em C Dm G7 C C G/B Am Em F C Dm Em F D/F# G7 C</chorus>
</chord>

</song>