<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ครั้นเรียกชื่อที่เมืองเกษมสุข</thainame>
   <englishname>When the roll is called up yonder</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ครั้นเมื่อเป่าแตรของพระเจ้าเวลาของโลกก็ถึงที่สุด และพระเยซูกลับมารับเราไปสวรรค์ สานุศิษย์ผู้รอดชีวิตในโลกพระเจ้าทรงรับเป็นบุตร ครั้นตรวจชื่อเบื้องบน ชื่อข้าฯก็อยู่ที่นั่น</verse1>
      <verse2>เวลานั้นศิษย์ของพระองค์ ผู้ตายไปแล้วจะคืนชีวี และจะเข้าในรัศมีบนเมืองสวรรค์ คนเหล่านั้นที่ทรงเลือกสรรในเมืองสวรรค์จะมีราศี ครั้นตรวจชื่อเบื้องบน ชื่อข้าฯก็อยู่ที่นั่น</verse2>
      <verse3>ให้เร่งทำการของพระเยซูตั้งแต่เวลาเช้าจนค่ำ และกล่าวถึงความรักพระองค์จนสิ้นชีวัน เมื่อสำเร็จงานของพระคริสต์ในโลกทั้งสิ้นที่เราควรทำ ครั้นตรวจชื่อเบื้องบน ชื่อข้าฯก็อยู่ที่นั่น</verse3>
      <chorus>ครั้นเรียกชื่อที่เมืองเกษมสุข ครั้นเรียกชื่อที่เมืองเกษมสุข ครั้นเรียกชื่อที่เมืองเกษมสุข ครั้นเรียกชื่อเบื้องบน ชื่อข้าฯก็อยู่ที่นั่น</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>When the trumpet of the Lord shall sound, and time shall be no more,And the morning breaks, eternal, bright and fair;When the saved of earth shall gather over on the other shore,And the roll is called up yonder, I’ll be there.</verse1>
      <verse2>On that bright and cloudless morning when the dead in Christ shall rise,And the glory of His resurrection share;When His chosen ones shall gather to their home beyond the skies,And the roll is called up yonder, I’ll be there.</verse2>
      <verse3>Let us labor for the Master from the dawn till setting sun,Let us talk of all His wondrous love and care;Then when all of life is over, and our work on earth is done,And the roll is called up yonder, I’ll be there.</verse3>
      <chorus>When the roll, is called up yon-der,When the roll, is called up yon-der,When the roll, is called up yon-der,When the roll is called up yonder I’ll be there.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>