<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ข้าจะแบกกางเขนแล้วเดินตาม</thainame>
   <englishname>Where He Leads Me </englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus,verse4,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข้าฯได้ยินพระเยซูเรียกข้าฯ โดยความรักพระองค์ทรงเรียกข้าฯ โดยพระธรรมโอวาททรงเรียกข้าฯ แบกกางเขนและตามเรา ตามเรามา</verse1>
      <verse2>แม้ว่าทางมืดมัว ทรงนำหน้า เมื่อจิตใจโศกเศร้า มีน้ำตา  แต่วิญญาณชุ่มชื่นทุกเวลา ข้าฯจะตามไป ตามไปทั่วทุกทาง</verse2>
      <verse3>ขอพระองค์เสด็จนำหน้าข้าฯ โปรดประทานสว่างฤทธิ์เดชมา  แม้ใจข้าฯอ่อนเพลียโปรดรักษา ข้าฯจะตามไป ตามไปทั่วทุกทาง</verse3>
      <verse4>แม้ว่าทางคดเคี้ยวทรงนำหน้า โปรดประทานอาหารสวรรค์มา เมื่อชีวิตวางวายทรงนำพา เพราะข้าฯตามไป ตามไปทั่วทุกทาง</verse4>
      <chorus>ข้าฯจะแบกกางเขน แล้วเดินตาม ข้าฯจะแบกกางเขน แล้วเดินตาม ข้าฯจะแบกกางเขน แล้วเดินตาม แล้วจะตามไป ตามไปทั่วทุกทาง</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>I can hear my Savior calling,  I can hear my Savior calling, I can hear my Savior calling,  &quot;Take thy cross and follow, follow me.&quot;</verse1>
      <verse2>I'll go with Him through the garden, I'll go with Him through the garden,  I'll go with Him through the garden, I'll go with Him, with Him all the way.</verse2>
      <verse3>I'll go with Him through the judgment, I'll go with Him through the judgment,  I'll go with Him through the judgment, I'll go with Him, with Him all the way.</verse3>
      <verse4>He will give me grace and glory,  He will give me grace and glory,  He will give me grace and glory,  and go with me, with me all the way.</verse4>
      <chorus>Where He leads me I will follow,  where He leads me I will follow, where He leads me I will follow; I'll go with Him, with Him all the way.</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>
