<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>เมื่อพวกเลี้ยงแกะเฝ้าแกะกลางคืน</thainame>
   <englishname>While Shepherds Watched Their Flocks</englishname>
   <mienthai>none</mienthai>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>เมื่อพวกเลี้ยงแกะเฝ้าแกะกลางคืน นั่งอยู่พื้นดินกลางนา มีทูตสวรรค์องค์หนึ่งลงมา มีแสงประจักษ์กับตา มีแสงประจักษ์กับตา</verse1>
      <verse2>พวกเลี้ยงแกะนั้นตกใจนักหนา แต่ทูตนั้นว่าอย่ากลัว เพราะเรานำข่าวดีมาประกาศ ชาวโลกชื่นใจยินดี ชาวโลกชื่นใจยินดี</verse2>
      <verse3>เหตุว่าวันนี้ที่เมืองดาวิด พระคริสต์ผู้ไถ่ประสูติ  ทรงรับร่างกายอย่างคนทั่วไป ในรางหญ้าผ้าพันกาย ในรางหญ้าผ้าพันกาย</verse3>
      <verse4>เมื่อทูตองค์นั้นเสร็จการบรรยาย มีชาวสวรรค์มากมาย ปรากฏแก่พวกเลี้ยงแกะทั้งหลาย ร้องเพลงสรรเสริญพระเจ้า  ร้องเพลงสรรเสริญพระเจ้า</verse4>
      <verse5>รัศมีจงมีแด่พระเป็นเจ้า  ความสุขมีแก่เหล่าชน  บนแผ่นดินโลกเกษมสำราญ อยู่ตลอดนิรันดร์กาล  อยู่ตลอดนิรันดร์กาล.</verse5>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>While shepherds watched their flocks by night, All seated on the ground;  The angel of the Lord came down, And glory shone around, And glory shone around.</verse1>
      <verse2>&quot;Fear not!&quot; said he, for mighty dread Had seized their troubled mind.  &quot;Glad tidings of great joy I bring To all of humankind, to all of humankind.&quot;</verse2>
      <verse3>&quot;To you, in David's town, this day Is born of David's line   A Savior, who is Christ the Lord, And this shall be the sign, and this shall be the sign:&quot;</verse3>
      <verse4>Thus spake the seraph and forthwith Appeared a shining throng Of angels praising God on high, Who thus addressed their song, Who thus addressed their song</verse4>
      <verse5>&quot;All glory be to God on high, And to the earth be peace;   Good will henceforth from heaven to earth Begin and never cease, Begin and never cease!&quot;</verse5>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
      <verse5/>
   </chord>
</song>
