<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>ใครสมัครอยู่ฝ่ายพระเจ้า</thainame>
   <englishname>Who Is on the Lord’s Side?</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ใครอาสาพระผู้ไถ่คอยรับใช้ค่ำเช้า ใครจะช่วยนำวิญญาณ ใครอยู่ฝ่ายพระเจ้า ใครยอมทิ้งสิ่งโลกีย์ ใครไม่หนีศัตรู ใครสมัครอยู่ฝ่ายพระเจ้าผู้ทรงเป็นอยู่ ทรงเรียกเราด้วยเมตตา โดยความกรุณา เราสมัครฝ่ายพระองค์ ยอมรับใช้พระเจ้า</verse1>
      <verse2>ไม่ต้องการเกียรติอย่างใด ไม่ต้องการศักดา แต่เพราะรักพระเยซู เราพลีตัวบูชา เราอยู่เพื่อพระผู้ไถ่ซึ่งได้ตายแทนข้าฯ ใครอยู่ฝ่ายพระเจ้าผู้นั้นรอดตลอดไป ความรักพระองค์ผูกไว้ โดยความกรุณา เราสมัครฝ่ายพระองค์ ยอมรับใช้พระเจ้า</verse2>
      <verse3>ทรงซื้อไว้ด้วยโลหิตสัมฤทธิ์กว่าเงินทอง ทรงพลีโลหิตหมายปอง เพื่อเข้าครองใจข้าฯ ทรงสร้างตัวเราทุกคนให้มีสิทธิ์เสรี รับความรอดจากพระเยซู ด้วยใจยินดี โดยพระคุณเรารอดบาป โดยความกรุณา เราสมัครฝ่ายพระองค์ ยอมรับใช้พระเจ้า</verse3>
      <verse4>ความโหดร้ายอาจต้านทานมารร้ายอาจขัดขวาง แต่พระเจ้าทรงคุ้มครองคอยปกป้องไม่ห่าง พระเยซูอยู่เคียงข้าง ทรงช่วยโดยไม่วาง เพราะพระองค์ทรงเป็นความจริง และไม่ปรวนแปร โดยความเชื่อมั่นคงอยู่ โดยความกรุณา เราสมัครฝ่ายพระองค์ยอมรับใช้พระเจ้า.</verse4>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>Who is on the Lord’s side? Who will serve the King?  Who will be His helpers, other lives to bring? Who will leave the world’s side? Who will face the foe?  Who is on the Lord’s side? Who for Him will go?  By Thy call of mercy, by Thy grace divine, We are on the Lord’s side Savior, we are Thine!</verse1>
      <verse2>Not for weight of glory, nor for crown and palm, Enter we the army, raise the warrior psalm; But for love that claimeth lives for whom He died: He whom Jesus nameth must be on His side  By Thy love constraining, by Thy grace divine,  We are on the Lord’s side Savior, we are Thine!</verse2>
      <verse3>Jesus, Thou hast bought us, not with gold or gem, But with Thine own life blood, for Thy diadem; With Thy blessing filling each who comes to Thee, Thou hast made us willing,Thou hast made us free.  By Thy grand redemption, by Thy grace divine,  We are on the Lord’s side Savior, we are Thine!</verse3>
      <verse4>Fierce may be the conflict, strong may be the foe, But the King’s own army none can overthrow;  ’Round His standard ranging, victory is secure, For His truth unchanging makes the triumph sure. Joyfully enlisting By Thy grace divine, We are on the Lord’s side Savior, we are Thine!</verse4>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <verse4/>
   </chord>
</song>