<?xml version="1.0" ?><song>
   <!--Generated from Trang Church Youtube-->
   <thainame>วานนี้และวันนี้และสืบไป</thainame>
   <englishname>Yesterday, Today, Forever</englishname>
   <mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
   <order>verse1,chorus,verse2,chorus,verse3,chorus</order>
   <thai>
      <verse1>ข่าวประเสริฐขององค์พระเยซูผู้ช่วยไถ่ให้รอด วานนี้และวันนี้และสืบไป ทรงช่วยได้ตลอด  ทรงเมตตารักษาคนป่วยคนบาปให้หายจากโรค หากผู้ใดจิตใจชอกช้ำทรงทำให้คลายความโศก</verse1>
      <verse2>ทรงเป็นเพื่อนกับคนทั้งหลาย ช่วยให้กลับใจเลิกบาป เชิญผู้สำนึกตัวละทิ้งความชั่วยอมสารภาพ เคยตรัสว่า &quot;จงไปเถิด อย่าทำผิดบาปต่อไปเลย&quot;  เช่นเดียวกันยังตรัสวันนี้ ขอท่านอย่าได้เพิกเฉย</verse2>
      <verse3>เหมือนดำเนินกับศิษย์ทั้งสอง นั้นไปบ้านเอมมาอูส   อย่างเดียวกันพระองค์ดำเนินกับเราและประทับอยู่ ในไม่ช้าพระเยซูเจ้าจะได้เสด็จกลับมา แล้วพระองค์รับเราทั้งหลายผู้เชื่อขึ้นไปเมืองฟ้า</verse3>
      <chorus>องค์พระเยซูผู้ไม่รู้แปรผัน อยู่ตลอดกาล ของทั้งหลายในโลกหันเหียนเปลี่ยนไปตามวันเวลา แต่องค์พระเยซู ผู้ไม่รู้เปลี่ยนแปลง สารพัดในโลกต้องเสื่อมสูญ แต่พระคริสต์ยั่งยืน</chorus>
   </thai>
   <english>
      <verse1>O how sweet the glorious message simple faith may  claim. Yesterday, Today, Forever Jesus is the same. Still  He  loves  to save the sinful, heal the sick and lame. Cheer the  mourner still  the tempest, Glory to His  name!</verse1>
      <verse2>He, who was the Friend of sinners, seeks the lost one now Sinner come, and at His footstool penitently bow He who said &quot;I'll not condemn thee, go and sin no more,&quot; Speaks to thee that word of pardon as in days of yore.</verse2>
      <verse3>As of old He walked to Emmaus, with them to abide So through all life's way He walketh ever near our side Soon again shall we behold Him, Hasten Lord the day But 'twill still be this same Jesus As he went away.</verse3>
      <chorus>Yesterday, today, forever Jesus is the same,  All may change, but Jesus never! Glory to His name! Glory to His name! Glory to His name! All may change, but Jesus never! Glory to His name!</chorus>
   </english>
   <mienthai>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </mienthai>
   <chord>
      <verse1/>
      <verse2/>
      <verse3/>
      <chorus/>
   </chord>
</song>