<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>มีธารน้ำพุเต็มด้วยโลหิต</thainame>
	<englishname>There Is a Fountain</englishname>
	<mienthainame>ม่าย ฒี้ง ปวั๊ง เหฑ่ง เย^ซู ปู๊-ฑย้าม</mienthainame>
	<order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5</order>
	<thai>
		<verse1>1.มีธารน้ำพุเต็มด้วยโลหิตซึ่งมาจากพระเยซู ถ้าใครทำบาปดำลงให้มิด จะหายบาปที่มีอยู่ จะหายบาปที่มีอยู่ จะหายบาปที่มีอยู่ ถ้าใครทำบาปดำลงให้มิดจะหายบาปที่มีอยู่</verse1>
		<verse2>2.โจรบนกางเขนผู้นั้นยินดีได้เห็นฤทธิ์โลหิตนั้น แม้ข้าจะชั่วกว่าโจรผู้นั้นบาปก็จะหลุดเหมือนกัน บาปก็จะหลุดเหมือนกันบาปก็จะหลุดเหมือนกัน แม้ข้าจะชั่วกว่าโจรผู้นั้นบาปก็จะหลุดเหมือนกัน</verse2>
		<verse3>3.โลหิตประเสริฐแห่งพระผู้ไถ่จะไม่หมดไปซึ่งฤทธิ์ จนทุกคนที่พระองค์ไถ่นั้นจะพ้นอำนาจความผิด จะพ้นอำนาจความผิดจะพ้นอำนาจความผิด จนทุกคนที่พระองค์ไถ่นั้นจะพ้นอำนาจความผิด</verse3>
		<verse4>4.ตั้งแต่ข้าเชื่อได้เห็นโลหิตซึ่งไหลมาจากกางเขน ข้าขอถวายสรรเสริญพระคริสต์เพราะข้าพ้นบาปหมดเวร เพราะข้าพ้นบาปหมดเวรเพราะข้าพ้นบาปหมดเวร ข้าขอถวายสรรเสริญพระคริสต์เพราะข้าพ้นบาปหมดเวร</verse4>
		<verse5>...</verse5>
	</thai>
<english>
    <verse1>There is a fountain filled with blood Drawn from Immanuel’s veins; And sinners, plunged beneath that flood, Lose all their guilty stains: Lose all their guilty stains, Lose all their guilty stains; And sinners, plunged beneath that flood, Lose all their guilty stains.</verse1>
    <verse2>The dying thief rejoiced to see That fountain in his day; And there may I, though vile as he, Wash all my sins away: Wash all my sins away, Wash all my sins away; And there may I, though vile as he, Wash all my sins away.</verse2>
    <verse3>Dear dying Lamb, Thy precious blood Shall never lose its power, Till all the ransomed ones of God Be saved, to sin no more: Be saved, to sin no more, Be saved, to sin no more; Till all the ransomed ones of God, Be saved to sin no more.</verse3>
    <verse4>E’er since by faith I saw the stream Thy flowing wounds supply, Redeeming love has been my theme, And shall be till I die: And shall be till I die, And shall be till I die; Redeeming love has been my theme, And shall be till I die.</verse4>
    <verse5>When this poor lisping, stammering tongue Lies silent in the grave, Then in a nobler, sweeter song, I’ll sing Thy power to save: I’ll sing Thy power to save, I’ll sing Thy power to save; Then in a nobler, sweeter song, I’ll sing Thy power to save.</verse5>
</english>
    
<mienthai>
    <verse1>ม่าย ฒี้ง ปวั๊ง เหฑ่ง เย^ซู ปู๊-ฑย้าม, เยียม เฒี้ยว เย^ซู เหลี่ยว ธ้วด. หาย เต้า ต่อง ฒุ์ย โซ้ว เจี๊ยน เหญี่ยม ฒุ์ย, นิ่น ม่าย เญย ฒุ์ย เหมียด เหฑ่ง. นิ่น ม่าย เญย ฒุ์ย เหมียด เหฑ่ง. นิ่น ม่าย เญย ฒุ์ย เหมียด เหฑ่ง. หาย เต้า ต่อง ฒุ์ย โซ้ว เจี๊ยน เหญี่ยม ฒุ์ย, นิ่น ม่าย เญย ฒุ์ย หฑาว เหฑ่ง.</verse1>
    <verse2>เยียม เหฒียบ หฑั่ง จ๋า วั้ว เต้า จั๋น-หฒะ, อะเฮน้ย เขา เฒี้ยว เญย ชะ. เยีย เก้า หว่าย เจี๋ย วั้ว เต้า จั๋น-หฒะ, เย^ซู หย่า ไฮ่ หฑาว เหฑ่ง. เย^ซู หย่า ไฮ่ หฑาว เหฑ่ง. เย^ซู หย่า ไฮ่ หฑาว เหฑ่ง. เยีย เก้า หว่าย เจี๋ย วั้ว เต้า จั๋น-หฒะ, เย^ซู หย่า ไฮ่ หฑาว เหฑ่ง.</verse2>
    <verse3>จ๋าย เญย ปู๊-ฑย้าม เสีย ธ้วด ฒุ์ย-เมี่ยน, เหยียด ลิ์ว ฒู้ง ไม้ เหฑ่ง ชะ. เยียม เฒี้ยว เสีย ธ้วด เหยียด ฒู้ง เญย เมี่ยน, เล่ย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เญย หัด ม์า. เล่ย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เญย หัด ม์า. เล่ย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เญย หัด ม์า. เยียม เฒี้ยว เสีย ธ้วด เหยียด ฒู้ง เญย เมี่ยน, เล่ย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เญย หัด ม์า.</verse3>
    <verse4>เยีย เสียน วั้ว หฒั่น ฮิ้ว ตุ๊ ปู๊-ฑย้าม, เยียม เหฒียบ หฑั่ง จ๋า เหลี่ยว ต้าย. เยีย โท้ ฝ่ง ห่อ เธง เฒี้ยว กี^ตู่, สา เยีย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เหฑ่ง วิน. สา เยีย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เหฑ่ง วิน. สา เยีย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เหฑ่ง วิน. เยีย โท้ ฝ่ง ห่อ เธง เฒี้ยว กี^ตู่, สา เยีย ดุ๊ด ฒุ์ย เหฑ่ง วิน.</verse4>
    <verse5>หาย เต้า ก๊อย เฮญี้ยว แล์ง โหฒว ธีง-เหฑ่ง, ไฮ่ ตุ๊ สีง ลี่ง เปียะ ต้าย. ตะฟ่าน เหยียด ฒู้ง ฝูง เหฑ่ง ปุน เฒี้ยว, เย^ซู อะเฮน้ย เหฌียว นิ่น. เย^ซู อะเฮน้ย เหฌียว นิ่น. เย^ซู อะเฮน้ย เหฌียว นิ่น. ตะฟ่าน เหยียด ฒู้ง ฝูง เหฑ่ง ปุน เฒี้ยว, เย^ซู อะเฮน้ย เหฌียว นิ่น.</verse5>
</mienthai>

<chord>
    <verse1>G      C      G        D Em          C          G     C    G         D      G G         C        G        C  D  G Em         C       G         D      G</verse1>
    <verse2>G      C      G        D Em          C          G     C    G         D      G G         C        G        C  D  G Em         C       G         D      G</verse2>
    <verse3>G      C      G        D Em          C          G     C    G         D      G G         C        G        C  D  G Em         C       G         D      G</verse3>
    <verse4>G      C      G        D Em          C          G     C    G         D      G G         C        G        C  D  G Em         C       G         D      G</verse4>
    <verse5>G      C      G        D Em          C          G     C    G         D      G G         C        G        C  D  G Em         C       G         D      G</verse5>
</chord>


</song>
