<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>

<thainame>อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอน</thainame>
<englishname>Don't Stop Praying</englishname>
<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
<order>verse1,verse2,verse3,verse4,verse5,verse6</order>

<thai>
    <verse1>อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอน พระเจ้าอยู่ใกล้ อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอน พระเจ้าโปรดได้ อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอน พระองค์สัญญา ทูลขอสิ่งใดประทานให้มา</verse1>
    <verse2>อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอนทูลขอทุกอย่าง อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนพระองค์ทรงฟัง คำร้องทูลขอสำคัญนักหนา อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนพระพรจะมา</verse2>
    <verse3>อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอนเมื่อถูกล่อลวง อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนจะหลุดจากบ่วง พระเจ้ารู้แจ้งความภายในใจ อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนจะทรงโปรดให้</verse3>
    <verse4>อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอนเมื่อทุกข์หนักใจ อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนเมื่อร้อนภายใน ความทุกข์เหล่านั้นทรงทราบประจักษ์ อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนคงสมความรัก</verse4>
    <verse5>อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอนทำตามพระทัย อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนร่ำร้องทูลไป ความเชื่อจะดับความกังวลใจ อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนต้องตามพระทัย</verse5>
    <verse6>อย่าหยุดอ้อนวอนเพื่อคนทั้งหลาย อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนจะสายเกินไป ความเชื่อชนะจิตใจศัตรู อย่าเว้นอ้อนวอนอย่างพระเยซู</verse6>
</thai>

<english>
    <verse1>Don't stop praying! The Lord is nigh; Don't stop praying! He'll hear your cry; God has promised, and He is true; Don't stop praying; He'll answer you.</verse1>
    <verse2>Don't stop praying! For ev’ry need; Don't stop praying! The Lord will heed; No petition to Him is small; Don't stop praying! He'll hold your hand.</verse2>
    <verse3>Don’t stop praying when led to sin; Don’t stop praying! That good may win; Christ was tempted and understands; Don’t stop praying! He’ll hold your hands.</verse3>
    <verse4>Don't stop praying! When bow’d with grief; Don't stop praying! You'll get relief; Troubles never escape God's sight; Don't stop praying! He'll make it right.</verse4>
    <verse5>Don't stop praying! But have more trust; Don't stop praying! For pray we must; Faith will banish a mount of care; Don't stop praying! God answers prayer.</verse5>
    <verse6>Pray always! Though your eyes grow dim, Go with your troubles straight to Him; Pray always for God understands; Have faith, leaving all in His hands.</verse6>
</english>
    
<mienthai>
</mienthai>

<chord>
    <verse1></verse1>
    <verse2></verse2>
    <verse3></verse3>
    <verse4></verse4>
    <verse5></verse5>
    <chorus></chorus>
</chord>

</song>