<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>1974 </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>We were young, And none of us know quite what to say, But the feeling moved. Among us in silence anyway. Slowly we had made. Quite a change--. Somewhere we had crossed a big line. Down upon our knees, We had tasted holy wine, And no one could sway us. In a life time.</segment1>
		<segment2>Purer than the sky, Behind the rain. Falling down all around us, Calling out from a boundless love. Love had lit a fire;. We were the flame. Burning into the darkness, Shining out from inside us.</segment2>
		<segment3>Not a word. And no one had to say we were changed. Nothing else we lived through. Would ever be same the same, Knowing the truth. That we had gained.</segment3>
		<segment4>Purer than the sky, Behind the rain. Falling down all around us, Calling out from a boundless love. Love had lit a fire;. We were the flame. Burning into the darkness, Shining out from inside us.</segment4>
		<segment5>Stay with me. Make it ever new, So time will not undo, As the years go by, How I need to see. That's still me.</segment5>
		<segment6>Falling down all around us, Calling out from a boundless love.</segment6>
		<segment7>Yeah..</segment7>
		<segment8>Burning into the darkness, Shining out from inside us.</segment8>
		<segment9>Purer than the sky, Behind the rain. Falling down all around us, Calling out from a boundless love. Love has lit a fire;. I am the flame. Burning into the darkness, Shining out from inside us.</segment9>
		<segment10>Purer than the sky, Behind the rain. Falling down all around us, Calling out from a boundless love. (ohh..). Love has lit a fire;. I am the flame. Burning into the darkness, Shining out from inside us.</segment10>
		<segment11>Purer than the sky, Behind the rain. Falling down all around us, Calling out from a boundless love.    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
