<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>7x70 </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Ive been living in this house here. Since the day that I was born. These walls have seen me happy. But most of all theyve seen me torn. Theyve heard the screaming matches. That made a family fall apart. Theyve had a front row seat. To the breaking of my heart</segment1>
		<segment2>7 times 70 times. Ill do what it takes to make it right. I thought the pain was here to stay. But forgiveness made a way. 7 times 70 times. Theres healing in the air tonight. Im reaching up to pull it down. Gonna wrap it all around</segment2>
		<segment3>I remember running down the hallway. Playing hide-and-seek. I didnt know that I was searching. For someone to notice me. I felt alone and undiscovered. And old enough to understand. Just when Im sposed to be learning to love you. Let me doubt again</segment3>
		<segment4>7 times 70 times. Ill do what it takes to make it right. I thought the pain was here to stay. But forgiveness made a way. 7 times 70 times. Theres healing in the air tonight. Im reaching up to pull it down. Gonna wrap it all around</segment4>
		<segment5>I lost count of the ways you let me down. But no matter how many times you werent around. Im all right now</segment5>
		<segment6>God picked up my heart and helped me through. And shined a light on the one thing left to do. And thats forgive you. I forgive you</segment6>
		<segment7>7 times 70 times. If thats the cost Ill pay the price. 7 times 70 times. Ill do what it takes to make it right. I thought the pain was here to stay. But forgiveness made a way</segment7>
		<segment8>7 times 70 times. Theres healing in this house tonight. Im reaching up to pull it down. Gonna wrap it all around. Yeah. Im gonna wrap it all around</segment8>
		<segment9>Ive been living in this house here. Since the day that I was born     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
