<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Acoustic Set: Rose Colored Stained Glass Windows/Road to Zion/More ... </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Acoustic Set Featuring Greg Volz</segment1>
		<segment2>Another sleepy Sunday safe within the walls. Outside a dying world in desperation calls. But noone hears the cries or knows what they're about. The doors are locked within, or is it from without </segment2>
		<segment3>Looking through rose-colored stained glass windows. Never allowing the world to come in. Seeing no evil and feeling no pain. And making the light as it comes from within. So dim..So dim</segment3>
		<segment4>There is a way that leads to life. The few that find it never die. Past mountain peaks graced white with snow. The way grows brighter as it goes </segment4>
		<segment5>There is a road inside of you. Inside of me there is one too. No stumbling pilgrim in the dark. The road to Zion's in your heart. The road to Zion's in your heart. The road to Zion's in your heart</segment5>
		<segment6>You say you've been feeling weaker, weaker by the day. You say you can't make the joy of your salvation stay. But good things come to them that wait. Not to those who hesitate. So hurry up and wait upon the Lord </segment6>
		<segment7>More power to ya. When you're standing on His word. When you're trusting with your whole heart in the message you have heard. More power to ya. When we're all in one accord. They that wait upon the Lord, they shall renew, they shall renew their strength</segment7>
		<segment8>No one ever noticed Annie weeping. People all around, but she was all alone. Mama's got her meetings, Daddy's got his job. and no one's got the time so Annie's on her own</segment8>
		<segment9>And it's not too late for Annie, she could be next to you. Don't miss the chance to tell her before her life is through. We gotta tell her Jesus loves her, tell her Jesus cares. Tell her He can free her and her burdens bear. Tell her Jesus loves her, tell her Jesus cares. Tell her He can free her and her burdens bear. It's not too late</segment9>
		<segment10>There are times when you feel like you can't go on. There are times when you feel like giving in. And there are times when you feel like you can't try anymore. There are times of trouble in believing. This test of your faith will last. As long as it takes to pass. Till you have no more doubt you'll endure. And your faith will emerge true and pure </segment10>
		<segment11>No doubt it'll be alright. With God it'll work together for good. No doubt in the end it will be understood. No doubt it'll all work out. With faith He can move any mountain for us. No doubt in the power of Jesus. And after all is done we find out. All we really need to have is no doubt</segment11>
		<segment12>Red is the color of the blood that flowed. Down the face of Someone Who loved us so. He's the perfect man, He's the Lord's own son, He's the Lamb of God, He's the only one. That can give us life, that can make us grow, That can make our sins as white as snow </segment12>
		<segment13>That can give us life, that can make us grow. That can turn our mornings into gold. That can give us life, that can make us grow. That can keep our hearts from growing cold. That can give us life, that can make us grow. That can make the love between us flow.</segment13>
		<segment14>Love is patient, love is kind. No eyes of envy, true love is blind. Love is humble, it knows no pride. No selfish motive hidden inside. Love is gentle, makes no demands. Despite all wrong, true love still stands. Love is holy, love is pure. It lasts forever, it will endure </segment14>
		<segment15>Love knows when to let go. Love knows when to say no. Love grows in the light of the Son. And love shows the world that the Son of Love has come.    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
