<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>A Day Late </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>So let me get this straight. Say now you love me all along. What made you hesitate. To tell me in words what you really feel. I can see it in your eyes. You mean all of what you say. I remember so long ago. See, I felt the same way</segment1>
		<segment2>Now we both have spearate lives and lovers (and lovers). Insignificantly enough we both have significant others. Only time will tell. Time will turn and tell</segment2>
		<segment3>We are who we were then. Could of been lovers. But at least your still my day late friend. We are who, We are who we were then. Who knew what we knew now. Could of been more. But at least your still my day late friend. We are who, We are who we were then</segment3>
		<segment4>But thoughts may change. And times they rearange. I don't know who you are anymore. But thoughts come and go. And this I know. I'm not who you recall anymore. But I must confess. You're so much more than I remember. Can't help but entertain this thought. Thoughts of us together</segment4>
		<segment5>We are who we were then. Could of been lovers. But at least your still my day late friend. We are who, We are who we were then. Who knew what we knew now. Could of been more. But atleast your still my day late friend. We are who, We are who we were then. My day late friend</segment5>
		<segment6>So let me get this straight. All these years and you were nowhere to be found. And now you want me for your own. But you're a day late and my love's just still renown</segment6>
		<segment7>We are who we were then. Could of been lovers. But at least your still my day late friend. We are who, We are who we were then. Who knew what we knew now. Could of been more. But at least your still my day late friend. We are who, We are who we were then    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
