<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>After The Music Fades </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Lord, take me. From this place. Into a world that has no time. No hurries, no worries, Gladly I leave them all behind. Down here; I'm letting go and drawing near.</segment1>
		<segment2>I wanna sing. I wanna fly. I wanna see from Your side of the sky. I wanna love. I wanna stay, Wanna be close to You. Long after the music fades.</segment2>
		<segment3>Lord, I come. To give You. Much more than just a melody. Please take me and break me;. Right now God, I don't want to leave. Unchanged; I never wanna be the same.</segment3>
		<segment4>I wanna sing. I wanna fly. I wanna see from Your side of the sky. I wanna love. I wanna stay, Wanna be close to You. Long after,</segment4>
		<segment5>'Cause Lord You are. Mighty, Awesome, Righteous, Gracious, Knowing, In me overflowing. Father, Teacher, Master, Leader. Jealous, Loving, You are.</segment5>
		<segment6>And you make me wanna sing. I wanna fly. I wanna see from Your side of the sky. I wanna love. I wanna stay, Wanna be close to You. Long after, And I wanna sing. I wanna fly. I wanna see from Your side of the sky. And I wanna love. I wanna stay, Wanna be close to You. Long after, Wanna be close to you. Forever after, Wanna be close to you, Long after the music fades, Long after the music fades.</segment6>
		<segment7>You are life. You are love. You are everything that I'm needing. You are life. You are love. You are everything that I'm needing. You are life. (I wanna be.). You are love. (I wanna be.). You are everything that I'm needing. (I wanna be closer.). You are life. (I wanna be.). You are love. (I wanna be.). You are everything that I'm needing. (I wanna be closer.). You are life. (You are.). (I wanna be.). You are love. (You are.). (I wanna be.). You are everything that I'm needing. (You are.). (I wanna be closer.). You are life. (You are.). (I wanna be.). You are love. (You are.). (I wanna be.). You are everything that I'm needing. (You are.). (I wanna be closer.). You are life. (You are.). (I wanna be.). You are love. (You are.). (I wanna be.). You are everything that I'm needing. (You are.). (I wanna be closer.)     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
