<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>A.K.A. Public School </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Counting the days to get away. to pack your bags up on a plane. But see Bob run yeah! See Bob play. why not talk to Bob today. If you wanna save the lost. you don't have to travel South. You don't have to pay the cost. just run your mouth </segment1>
		<segment2>School is the place to be. when you're young and fancy free. 'Cause you got what? Mmm half a day. to give your life away. In Uncle Sam's soul salvation program. government funded paid in full. A.K.A. your public school. They pay to put you in the classes. it's your chance to reach the masses </segment2>
		<segment3>This ain't no trip to a foreign land. this ain't no trip to a foreign land. but you can take a stand. in your Public school </segment3>
		<segment4>This may Mexico, Columbia or France. you want to go to Africa well now you got a chance. Talk to your friends before the fun ends. you can take 'em by surprise when you open their eyes </segment4>
		<segment5>School is the place to be. when you're young and fancy free. 'Cause you got what? Mmm half a day. to give your life away. In Uncle Sam's soul salvation program. government funded paid in full. A.K.A. your public school. They pay to put you in the classes. it's your chance to reach the masses </segment5>
		<segment6>This ain't no trip to a foreign land. this ain't no trip to a foreign land. but you can take a stand. in your Public school </segment6>
		<segment7>This ain't no trip. This ain't no trip. This ain't no trip to a foreign land. This ain't no trip to a foreign land. This ain't no trip to a foreign land. No passport of any sort this ain't no trip. This ain't no trip to a foreign land. This ain't no trip to a foreign land. </segment7>
		<segment8>It's your own school home town its where you should be livin'. This ain't no trip. This ain't no trip. It's your own school home town its where you should be givin' </segment8>
		<segment9>This ain't no trip to a foreign land.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
