<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Alarm the Alarm </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>If I'm the first to go, then make it quick (then make it quick). We're so young, so naive. If I'm the first to go, then make it quick. We're so young, we're so young, so naive. It's all for nothing, nothing at all</segment1>
		<segment2>Liars can't be martyrs, don't you know. Let me give it to you plain and simple, You walk a fine line, you walk a fine line. You speak of truth, you speak of progress, Well I'll believe it when I see it for myself. Let me spell it out a little more clearly, You walk a fine line, you walk a fine line.</segment2>
		<segment3>Can't you see the irony, in what you do to me?. You get so close, so close, And make me feel so terribly alone. Can't you see the irony, in what you do to me?. You get so close, so close, And make me feel so terribly alone.</segment3>
		<segment4>If I'm the first to go, then make it quick (then make it quick). We're so young, so naive. If I'm the first to go, then make it quick. We're so young, we're so young, so naive.</segment4>
		<segment5>It's safe to say that we're heading to the crossroads. We are the galleries of the centuries. If you knew the truth, it really would've killed you. If you knew the truth, if you only knew.</segment5>
		<segment6>We've been caught up in the moment, And our beds are crowded where we sleep. I hate to say it but we're never making progress. I hate to say it, I hate to say it.</segment6>
		<segment7>Can't you see the irony, in what you do to me?. You get so close, so close, And make me feel so terribly alone. Can't you see the irony, in what you do to me?. You get so close, so close, And make me feel so terribly alone.</segment7>
		<segment8>There's no other name by which I am saved, I will not be afraid to trust in you.</segment8>
		<segment9>This is a race to a lost cause. This is a race to a lost cause. This is a race to the skies. This is a race to the skies.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
