<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>All Right </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Looking out. To the hills, to the setting sun, I feel a cold wind. Bound to come;. Another change, Another end I cannot see, But your faithfulness to me</segment1>
		<segment2>Is making it all right. I fall down on my knees;. Tell me that it's all right. You give me what I need. Years of knockin' on heaven's door. Have taught me this, if nothing more, That it's all right, what may come.</segment2>
		<segment3>I've heard it said, When the river's running high, You get to higher ground or you die. Well, muddy waves of pain. Washed over me, And it only made me see,</segment3>
		<segment4>It's gonna be all right. I, I fall down on my knees;. Tell me that it's all right. You give me what I need. Years of knockin' on heaven's door. Have taught me this, if nothing more, That it's all right, what may come.</segment4>
		<segment5>When will I learn there're no guarantees?. What strengthens hope, my eyes have never seen, But it won't be long. Till the faith will be sight, And the heavens will say,</segment5>
		<segment6>It's all right. (all right.). (all right.). (all right.)</segment6>
		<segment7>All right, I fall down on my knees;. Tell me that it's all right. You give me what I need. Years of knockin'..heaven's door, Have taught me this, if nothing more, And it's all right. Whatever comes.</segment7>
		<segment8>All right, Fall on my knees, Tell me that it's all right. You give me what I need. (after all these) years of knockin' on heaven's door, (years of knockin' on heavens' door,). (it's gonna be) all right. (oooooh, yeah.) all right. I fall down on my knees, Tell me that it's all right, 'cause you give me what I need, (after all these years of knockin' on heaven's door,). Years of knockin' on heaven's door, (it's gonna be) all right. Whatever comes, yes sir, All right. I fall down on my knees. All right.    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
