<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>All The Memories </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I can't stop killing the songs you like. You look at me with eyes. That could beat the sunrise in a contest. No question. Well, talk to all the others. And bring me back to earth. I'm thankful for your mother for what it's worth</segment1>
		<segment2>Oh, all the memories we had. Framed in our minds like photographs. Take a second, take a second. And make this last. Here where the future meets the past. I can never fall in love again. I can never fall in love again</segment2>
		<segment3>I can't stop moving cause I'll feel dead. Give me a second and I'll turn into a year you won't forget. We'll make read our stories. And we'll make them eat their words. We'll make their lives seem boring for what it's worth</segment3>
		<segment4>Oh, all the memories we had. Framed in like photographs. Take a second, take a second. And make this last. Here where the future meets the past. I can never fall in love again. I can never fall in love again</segment4>
		<segment5>I drink your poison and say. I'm still not going away. I'll swallow all your bombs and grenades. And love you like a tsunami wave. Wave, wave</segment5>
		<segment6>Oh, all the memories we had. Framed in like photographs. Take a second, take a second. And make this last. Here where the future meets the past. I can never fall in love again. I can never fall in love again</segment6>
		<segment7>Oh, all the memories. Framed in our minds. Take a second, take a second. And make this last, here for a while. I can never fall in love again. I can never fall in love again</segment7>
		<segment8>Oh, all the memories. Framed in our minds. Take a second, take a second. And make this last, here for a while. I can never fall in love again. I can never fall in love again. Again    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
