<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>All That Matters </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Look at what I've gained, I've earned. Since I've been here on this earth. I've collected everything that was of value and of worth!. But there was always something missing inside of me.. (Always something missing.. Always something..)</segment1>
		<segment2>People that could give to me, I always held in high esteem. And I would stab you in the back to gain popularity. And then You came into my life and I realized. (You came into my life.. You came into..)</segment2>
		<segment3>Everything I have is trash. Compared to knowing who You are!. Everything is trash compared to knowing You!. (All that matters is You)</segment3>
		<segment4>Since you came along, I've had to re-evaluate my heart.. Then I realized that I was blind from the very start!. Because without You there is nothing worth anything. (There is nothing.. There Is..)</segment4>
		<segment5>Everything I have is trash. Compared to knowing who You are!. Everything is trash compared to knowing You!. (All that matters is You)</segment5>
		<segment6>So take my heart and take my soul (Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!). Instill in me what matters most (Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!). All that matters is You. All that matters is You. All that matters is You. All that matters is.. You!</segment6>
		<segment7>Everything I have is trash. Compared to knowing who You are!. Everything is trash compared to knowing You!. (All that matters is You)</segment7>
		<segment8>Everything I have is trash. Compared to knowing who You are! (Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!). Everything is trash compared to knowing You!. (All that matters is You)</segment8>
		<segment9>Compared to knowing You (All that matters is You). Everything is trash (All that matters is You). Compared to knowing You (All that matters is You). All that matters is You..     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
