<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Always There </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I Have Run But I Can't Lose You, I Built Up Walls But You Just Break Through. I'm Trying To Escape Trying To Escape, But Your Keeping Up The Chase Keeping Up The Chase</segment1>
		<segment2>. I Break Your Heart But You Just Come Back. You've Open Arms And I Know. I Can't Ever Make You Leave Never Gonna Leave. Love Is Holding Me Love Is Holding Me</segment2>
		<segment3>. I Can Never Walk Anywhere Without You. Try To Turn My Back But Still I Find You. Everywhere I Go Everywhere I Know Your Always There Always There</segment3>
		<segment4>. There Are Days I Want To Turn Back. Sometimes Its So Tough To Trust That. You Gotta Plan For Me, Gotta Plan For Me. But Its Hard For Me To See, Hard For Me To See</segment4>
		<segment5>. There's One Thing With Which I'm Sure. No High No Depth No Fear Of Failure. But Can Pull Me From Your Grace, Can Pull Me From Your Grace</segment5>
		<segment6>. I Can Never Walk Anywhere Without You. Try To Turn My Back But Still I Find You. Everywhere I Go. Everywhere I Know Your Always There, Always There</segment6>
		<segment7>. When I'm Walking In The Light And Faith Comes Easy. When I'm Drowning In My Doubt Not Believing. Every Step I Take With Me All The Way. Your Always There, Always There</segment7>
		<segment8>. And I Won't Ever Be Alone (i Won't Ever Be Alone). No I Won't Ever Be Alone (i Won't Ever Be Alone)</segment8>
		<segment9>. I Can Never Walk Anywhere Without You. Try To Turn My Back But Still I Find You. Everywhere I Go, Everywhere I Know Your Always There, Always There</segment9>
		<segment10>. When I'm Walking In The Light Faith Comes Easy. When I'm Drowning In My Doubt Not Believing. Every Step I Take With Me All The Way. Your Always There, Always There. Your Always There, Always There    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
