<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>America's Next Freak </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>This song's for the emo kids. With the punk rock, rock 'n' roll, screamo lids. And the crunk, rock, hip hop, metal queens. Who still don't know what the 'heck that means </segment1>
		<segment2>Let's cheer for the real MC's. All the East, West, 'Derrty South', straight O.G.'s. With the hippy rock, hard core, alt. country's. With the techno industrial magazines </segment2>
		<segment3>I don't know where I fit in, But every time that record spins. I know the way it makes me feel. I never tried to be your trend. Never asked to be everyone's friend. I'm just who I am. And that's life for real. And every time you try to just remember </segment3>
		<segment4>That I won't be. America's next freak. I will not lay down. Every time you speak. And if all you see. Is America's next freak. Take me home, take me home, take me home </segment4>
		<segment5>This one's for America's teens. And the beach boys rockin' in the Phillipines. With the twist top, X-Box strategies. All speakin' French, Spanish and Portuguese </segment5>
		<segment6>And one time for the After Life. And the super low, low ride Macstyle. And the man with the plan in the Corderois. Who just brought back the backstreet boys </segment6>
		<segment7>I don't know where I fit in. But every time that record spins. I know the way it makes me feel. I never tried to be your trend. Never asked to be everyone's friend. I'm just who I am. And that's life for real. And every time you try to just remember </segment7>
		<segment8>That I won't be. America's next freak. I will not lay down. Every time you speak. And if all you see. Is America's next freak. Take me home, take me home, take me home </segment8>
		<segment9>i dont see anything around me. i wont be, i wont be. i dont see anything around me. i wont be, i wont be. if you dont see, then skip my trial. i wont see, i wont see. it makes me sick, it makes me smile. cause i wont be, i wont be </segment9>
		<segment10>I won't be. America's next freak. I will not lay down. Every time you speak. And if all you see. Is America's next freak. Take me home, take me home, take me home.     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
