<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Amy's Song </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Amy's gone. And time rolls on. How far? how fast? how long?</segment1>
		<segment2>The last time we saw Amy. She was headed for the shore. Fighting off the volatile gray skies</segment2>
		<segment3>She said now begins forever. And that no one knows their time. We bid farewell not knowing. That might be our last good-bye</segment3>
		<segment4>Amy was a fighter. She cut like Casius Clay. She burned like a fire. Despite these rains</segment4>
		<segment5>Where time was a question. She only knew one song. She's singing, &quot;how far, how fast, how long?&quot;</segment5>
		<segment6>Salvation is a fire. In the midnight of the soul. It lights up like a can of gasoline</segment6>
		<segment7>Yeah, she's a freedom fighter. She's a stand up kind of girl. She's out to start a fire. In a bar code plastic world</segment7>
		<segment8>Amy was a fighter. She cut like Casius Clay. She burned like a fire. Despite these rains</segment8>
		<segment9>Where time was a question. She only knew one song. She's singing, &quot;how far, how fast, how long?&quot;</segment9>
		<segment10>When everything stops moving. And I stop to catch my breath. And ride my train of thought. All the way around</segment10>
		<segment11>My thoughts return to Amy. And the fire she's begun. She came when we were freezing. And left us burning up</segment11>
		<segment12>Amy was a fighter. She cut like Casius Clay. She burned like a fire. Despite these rains</segment12>
		<segment13>Where time was a question. She only knew one song. She's singing, &quot;how far, how fast, how long?&quot;. How long, how long, how long?</segment13>
		<segment14>The last time we saw Amy. The last time we saw Amy. Yeah, the last time we saw Amy. The last time we saw Amy. Yeah, the last time we saw Amy    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
