<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Are You Online? </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>and if you dont know what to do get back online. and if you dont know the truth get back online. now hit the button reboot get back online. get back online get back online</segment1>
		<segment2>when I first got the friend request. I was like now whos this who be sending this. I went online hit ya profile but then I guess. I was wild as a child w/ my senselessness. couldnt vibe when you said I should then repent. hit deny then relied then I sent it back. time to time you would try but I must regret. had you on block with all your friend attempts. you had me on top 8 saw your pics and vids. I went and walked my way like you didnt exist. I read your blogs and Id comment on your sentences. I was wrong till I found out what you went and did. you broke my walls right down and my defensiveness. I watched it fall right now since I been convinced. ever since you got added this has been commenced. you went and changed my status to what its been just since </segment2>
		<segment3>. my whole life I tried to hurry through. I was hurting dude stressed out read the current mood. I didnt want to turn to you. I set the profile to private is what I learned to do this is true. foul mouth full of attitude until I heard of you. you added me before I added you. I cant express all my gratitude you let them murder you. you went offline but came out the tomb. I ran a search then I brought ya name up. and now the whole profile changed up. straight up you didnt care how my face looked. you invaded myspace w/ your facebook. now I was straight shook but you was online. and now I read your word line on line. youre profile is like all mine. and every email back is always on time </segment3>
		<segment4>now anyplace now that I go. that if I find that I start to sync just like my iphone. mind blown off the hook like a dial tone. in any timezone I know that Im home. and when I roam peace flows like a river. I follow you like a tweets from a twitter. and I can see and remember and I see and consider. now every need for me you deliver. if I could load it all to youtube. and they could see the very death right now just that you knew. how they beat you buried you bruised you. how many views on the page now would you do. would they choose you would it make em mad. would they ignore it like a banner ad. or would I be just another fad. downloaded like a torrent that you grab.     </segment4>
	</english>
</song>
