<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Around The Clock </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Dance until we just can't. Clapping our hands to the songs. And get dancing around to the joyful sound that the band plays. As his smiling face just shines away its making things as big as a train. April, May, June and July we'll hang outside. August and February all the time. Talking are way through March. Hanging out always till this starts. Over and over again you promise that it won't end. So I will try to find the right way to begin and</segment1>
		<segment2>How I, I am not into the idea of living without you. And I, I am not into the idea of being without you. And no this won't be a sad song. And it's gonna be classic singing along. Cuz this song's about now well that would just feel wrong</segment2>
		<segment3>Beautiful colors that came for you. So this ones goes out to the reds and yellows and blues. And of course I cant forget all the beautiful colors on the day that we first met. So I will never know the right way to say thanks. for all the nights and days you spent hanging out. That's what this is about</segment3>
		<segment4>How I, I am not into the idea of living without you. And I, I am not into the idea of being without you. And no this won't be a sad song. And it's gonna be classic singing along</segment4>
		<segment5>Cuz you there when you talk and your there not to stop and you leave me</segment5>
		<segment6>Around the clock you are you are. Around the clock you are you are. Around the clock</segment6>
		<segment7>Just so you know everyone else is not so I, I am not into the idea of living without you. And I, I am not into the idea. And no this won't be a sad song. And it's gonna be classic singing along. Cuz you there when you talk and your there not to stop and with me around the clock    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
