<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>A Stick, a Carrot &amp; String </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>the horse's hay beneath his head. our Lord was born to a manger bed. that all whose wells run dry. could drink of his supply</segment1>
		<segment2>to keep him warm, the sheep drew near. so grateful for His coming here. come with news of grace. come to take my place. the donkey whispered in his ear. &quot;child, in 30-some-odd years. you'll ride someone who looks like me. untriumphantly&quot;</segment2>
		<segment3>the cardinals warbled a joyful song. he'll make right what man made wrong. bringing low the hills. that the valleys might be filled</segment3>
		<segment4>then &quot;child&quot;, asked the birds. &quot;well, aren't they lovely words we sing?&quot;. the tiny baby layed there. without saying anything</segment4>
		<segment5>at a distance stood a mangy goat. with the crooked teeth and a matted coat. weary eyes and worn. chipped and twisted horns</segment5>
		<segment6>thinking &quot;maybe I'll make friends someday. with the cows and the hens in the rambouillet. but for now, I'll keep away. I've got nothing smart to say&quot;</segment6>
		<segment7>there's a sign on the barn. in the cabbage town. &quot;when the rain picks up. and the sun goes down. sinners, come inside. with no money, come and buy</segment7>
		<segment8>no clever talk, nor a gift to bring. requires our lowly, lovely king. come now empty handed, you don't need anything&quot;</segment8>
		<segment9>and the night was cool. and clear as glass. with the sneaking snake in the garden grass. deep cried out to deep. the disciples fast asleep</segment9>
		<segment10>and the snake perked up. when he heard You ask. &quot;if you're willing that. this cup might pass. we could find our way back home. maybe start a family all our own&quot;</segment10>
		<segment11>&quot;but does not the Father guide the Son?. not my will, but yours be done. what else here to do?. what else me, but You?&quot;</segment11>
		<segment12>and the snake who'd held the world. a stick, a carrot and a string. was crushed beneath the foot. of your not wanting anything     </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
