<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Audrey, Start The Revolution! </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Maybe tonight we'll get back together. Sound the alarms and break all the levers. These streets are ours, our anthem rings. You'd know the truth if these walls could sing.</segment1>
		<segment2>Amateur youth, sling down those signs. Gather the masses, friends of mine. I've got your back if you've got my hand. This isn't over, it just began.</segment2>
		<segment3>If this isn't love, (If this isn't love). This is the closest I've ever been. Do you think we have a chance?. Tonight at streetlights, sing on Audrey's song.</segment3>
		<segment4>If this isn't love, (If this isn't love). This is the closest I've ever been. Do you think we have a chance?. Tonight at streetlights, sing on Audrey's song.</segment4>
		<segment5>Remind your parents, We're tomorrow. Lead with morals and we'll follow. When they wake up they'll see. That youth fades and glory days deceive.</segment5>
		<segment6>What are you waiting for? Let's move on this. Time is of essence like your kiss. So say you're in. With cards down and guns drawn; this is it!</segment6>
		<segment7>If this isn't love, (If this isn't love). This is the closest I've ever been. Do you think we have a chance?. Tonight at streetlights, sing on Audrey's song.</segment7>
		<segment8>If this isn't love, (If this isn't love). This is the closest I've ever been. Do you think we have a chance?. Tonight at streetlights, sing on Audrey's song.</segment8>
		<segment9>But now it stops at this. We could take it all if only we were rich. You can be what you can conceive. Red letters, kill your disbelief.</segment9>
		<segment10>We all make mistakes sometimes. We all fail, but we stand tonight. Look past them and move on. We're all here; you're not the only one.</segment10>
		<segment11>If this isn't love, (If this isn't love). This is the closest I've ever been. Do you think we have a chance?. Tonight at streetlights, sing on Audrey's song.    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
