<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Away In Silence </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>You walked away in silence. You walked away to breathe. Stopped and turned around to say goodbye to me. I'm pleading as your leaving I'm begging you stay. I'm not the man I used to be, I've changed. I'm not the man I used to be, I've changed</segment1>
		<segment2>Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. If my life is the price, then my life it will cost. Now that I'm picking up the pieces see the pain that I have caused. It's hard to believe in someone you thought was lost. Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. Don't you walk away in silence.. </segment2>
		<segment3>In tears you counted reasons. Tears covered you it seemed. Face down screaming &quot;God help me please&quot;. I'm pleading as your leaving; I'm begging you to stay. I'm not the man I used to be, I've changed. I'm not the man I used to be, I've changed</segment3>
		<segment4>Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. If my life is the price, then my life it will cost. It will cost my life. Now that I'm picking up the pieces see the pain that I have caused. It's hard to believe in someone you thought was lost. Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. Don't you walk away in silence. Please come back to me. Don't you walk away in silence. I'm not the man I used to be! </segment4>
		<segment5>Well I pray that tomorrow you'll be home. We can rebuild and forever we can go on. Go on, and go on. We can go on, well I pray that tomorrow you'll be home. Look at horizons and let the light bring you home, bring you home</segment5>
		<segment6>Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. If my life is the price, then my life it will cost. Now that I'm picking up the pieces see the pain that I have caused. It's hard to believe in someone you thought was lost. Don't give up on us, don't give up on love. Don't walk away in silence. Please don't walk away. Don't you walk away in silence. I'm not the man I used to be!    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
