<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Beautiful King </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Beautiful King, has anybody seen. Your glory unfold?. You walk up to me. with sparks in Your eyes, You brighten my world </segment1>
		<segment2>And You'll always be my only One. You're the only God I'll ever love. because.. </segment2>
		<segment3>Every word that you say. wields the beauty of angels. Every smile is arrayed. with a joy like wedding bells. It's my heart you hold. Of your mystery I sing. I will stand and behold. my Beautiful King </segment3>
		<segment4>Love of my soul, with power untold, who is like you?. Lamb that was slain, my God, You reign. in victory and truth. </segment4>
		<segment5>And I'll follow You all my days. And I'll give to You every single thing. I hand everything over.. </segment5>
		<segment6>Every word that You say. wields the beauty of angels. Every smile is arrayed. with a joy like wedding bells. It's my heart You hold. Of your mystery i sing. I will stand and behold. my Beautiful King. </segment6>
		<segment7>And time flies by. We're not standing alone. Every word that You say, Father, let it be known. I fall so fast. without You by my side. Let Your beauty be seen </segment7>
		<segment8>Let Your glory unfold. Let Your glory unfold. Let Your glory unfold. Let Your glory unfold </segment8>
		<segment9>Every word that You say. wields the beauty of angels. 'Cause every smile is arrayed. with a joy like wedding bells. It's my heart You hold. Of Your mystery i sing. I will stand and behold. my Beautiful King!!! </segment9>
		<segment10>'Cause every word that you say. wields the beauty of angels. 'Cause every smile is arrayed. with a joy like wedding bells. It's my heart You hold. Of your mystery i sing. I will stand and behold. my Beautiful King    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
