<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Beauty Mark </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>What do You see when You look at me?. Ten dollar words and philosophies. How would You choose to define me. Cares for others or just cares what others think? </segment1>
		<segment2>But there is more to me than just what meets the eye. It's time to be the change inside </segment2>
		<segment3>I wanna' look like love. I wanna' look like, live like faith. I wanna' let this life in me show on my face. I wanna' look like hope. I wanna' look, live like grace. And I know just where to start. I'll let you be my beauty mark </segment3>
		<segment4>Lookin' the part just to play the game. Cookie cutter faith that looks the same. Religious rock stars making a name. So churchified it is a crying shame. But I'll put the finger on nobody else but me. (Nobody else but me). It's time to be the change we need </segment4>
		<segment5>I wanna' look like love. I wanna' look like, live like faith. I wanna' let this life in me show on my face. I wanna' look like hope. I wanna' look, live like grace. And I know just where to start. I'll let you be my beauty mark </segment5>
		<segment6>Dressed up in. Love and joy, peace and kindness. Gentleness and self control. Nothing, nothing is more beautiful. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeahey </segment6>
		<segment7>I wanna' look like love. I wanna' look like, live like faith. I wanna' let this life in me show on my face. I wanna' look like hope. I wanna' look, live like grace </segment7>
		<segment8>And I know just where to start. I'll let you feel my beauty mark </segment8>
		<segment9>I'm gona' let you be my beauty mark. Yeah, yeah, oh, oh </segment9>
		<segment10>I wanna' look like hope (look like hope). I wanna' look like, live like grace. And I know just where to start. I'll let you be my beauty mark </segment10>
		<segment11>I'll let you be my beauty mark    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
