<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Before The Morning </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Do you wonder why you have to, feel the things that hurt you, if there's a God who loves you, where is He now?</segment1>
		<segment2>Maybe, there are things you can't see. and all those things are happening. to bring a better ending. some day, some how, you'll see, you'll see</segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus: Would dare you, would you dare, to believe, that you still have a reason to sing, 'cause the pain you've been feeling, can't compare to the joy that's coming</segment3>
		<segment4>so hold on, you got to wait for the light. press on, just fight the good fight. because the pain you've been feeling, it's just the dark before the morning</segment4>
		<segment5>My friend, you know how this all ends. and you know where you're going, you just don't know how you get there. so just say a prayer. and hold on, cause there's good who love God, life is not a snapshot, it might take a little time, but you'll see the bigger picture</segment5>
		<segment6>Would dare you, would you dare, to believe, that you still have a reason to sing, 'cause the pain you've been feeling, can't compare to the joy that's coming</segment6>
		<segment7>so hold on, you got to wait for the light. press on, just fight the good fight. because the pain you've been feeling, it's just the dark before the morning. yeah, yeah, before the morning, yeah, yeah</segment7>
		<segment8>Once you feel the way of glory, all your pain will fade to memory. once you feel the way of glory, all your pain will fade to memory. memory, memory, yeah</segment8>
		<segment9>Would dare you, would you dare, to believe, that you still have a reason to sing, 'cause the pain you've been feeling, can't compare to the joy that's coming</segment9>
		<segment10>Would dare you, would you dare, to believe, that you still have a reason to sing, 'cause the pain you've been feeling, can't compare to the joy that's coming</segment10>
		<segment11>com'n, you got to wait for the light. press on, just fight the good fight. because the pain you've been feeling, it's just the hurt before the healing. the pain you've been feeling, just the dark before the morning. before the morning, yeah, yeah. before the morning    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
