<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Better Is One Day </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>One day, hey. One day, hey. One day, hey</segment1>
		<segment2>How lovely is Your dwelling place. Oh, Lord Almighty. For my soul longs and even faints for You. For here my heart is satisfied. Within Your presence. I sing beneath the shadow of your wings</segment2>
		<segment3>'Cause better is one day in Your courts. Better is one day in Your house. Better is one day in Your courts. Than thousands elsewhere. 'Cause better is one day in Your courts. Better is one day in Your house. Better is one day in Your courts. Than thousands elsewhere. Than thousands elsewhere</segment3>
		<segment4>One thing I ask and I would seek. To see Your beauty. To find You in the place Your glory dwells. One thing I ask and I would seek. To see Your beauty. To find You in the place Your glory dwells</segment4>
		<segment5>'Cause better is one day in Your courts. Better is one day in Your house. Better is one day in Your courts. Than thousands elsewhere. 'Cause better is one day in Your courts. Better is one day in Your house. Better is one day in Your courts. Than thousands elsewhere</segment5>
		<segment6>My heart and flesh cry out. For You the living God. Your Spirit's water for my soul. I've tasted and I've seen. Come once again to me. I will draw near to You. I will draw near to You</segment6>
		<segment7>Better is one day in Your courts. Better is one day in Your house</segment7>
		<segment8>'Cause better is one day in Your courts. Better is one day in Your house. Better is one day in Your courts. Than thousands elsewhere. 'Cause better is one day in Your courts. Better is one day in Your house. Better is one day in Your courts. Than thousands elsewhere. Than thousands elsewhere. Than thousands elsewhere    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
