<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Bike Song </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>9 In The Morning Saturday Came. Moms In The Kitchen Fixing The Sink. And Dad Got Up Early To Work Hard Outside. Today Was The Day He Would Teach Me To Ride</segment1>
		<segment2>I Rush To The Kitchen To Eat Up The Meal. Dad Waltzing In With A Smile That Was Real. He Knew I Was Watching He Knew I Was There. Ready To Chase All The Birds In The Air</segment2>
		<segment3>Traveling Faster And Racing The Wind. All Is Alive And The Sky Has A Grin. While It Welcomes Me Right Here. I Have No Limits And No Need To Cry. Free Like An Eagle High In The Sky. What Could Stop These Wings When They Fly</segment3>
		<segment4>Dad Takes My Hand We Walk Out The Door. Hes Ready To Show Me Just How To Soar. He Took Off The Trainers And Placed Me On top. Held On The Back As He Gave Me The Talk. I Kept On Moving And Once He Let Go. I Did As He Told Me Which Is All I Know. I Went Threw The Tunnel Straight To The Beach. Peddling Down The Sandy Concrete</segment4>
		<segment5>Traveling Faster And Racing The Wind. All Is Alive And The Sky Has A Grin. While It Welcomes Me Right Here. I Have No Limits And No Need To Cry. Free Like An Eagle High In The Sky. What Could Stop These Wings When They Fly</segment5>
		<segment6>I Pay No Attention To The Road All Around. A Rock Stops The Wheel As I Plunge To The Ground. I Cant Move A Muscle And The Ride Is Deformed. Im More Then Just Helpless In These Clothes That Are Torn. But Off In The Distance A Man Starts To Run. It Was My Daddy Saving His Son. And The More That I Cried. The More He Embraced. So I Rolled Onto His Shoulders And Flying Back Home. We Raced</segment6>
		<segment7>Traveling Faster And Racing The Wind. All Is Alive And The Sky Has A Grin. While It Welcomes Me Right Here. I Have No Limits And No Need To Cry. Free Like An Eagle High In The Sky </segment7>
		<segment8>When They Fly. When They Fly    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
