<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Billy Joe McGuffery </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19,segment20,segment21,segment22,segment23,segment24</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the first day of first grade, I'll tell you what he did. He tripped over a pencil box, flew up in the air. Landed on a kangaroo who pulled out all his hair</segment1>
		<segment2>First aid in the first grade. First aid in the first grade. First aid in the first grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment2>
		<segment3>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the second day of second grade, I'll tell you what he did. He slipped on a banana peel, flew up in the sky. Landed on a chimpanzee who poked him in the eye</segment3>
		<segment4>First aid in the second grade. First aid in the second grade. First aid in the second grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment4>
		<segment5>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the third day of third grade, I'll tell you what he did. He fell out of a fishing boat, splashed into the sea. Landed on a moray eel who bit him on the knee</segment5>
		<segment6>First aid in the third grade. First aid in the third grade. First aid in the third grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment6>
		<segment7>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the fourth day of fourth grade, I'll tell you what he did. He went out on a tadpole hunt, slipped into the creek. Landed on a large-mouth bass who bit him on the cheek</segment7>
		<segment8>First aid in the fourth grade. First aid in the fourth grade. First aid in the fourth grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment8>
		<segment9>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the fifth day of fifth grade, I'll tell you what he did. He went into the garden shop looking for a rose. Sniffed a baby's breath and got a bee caught up his nose</segment9>
		<segment10>First aid in the fifth grade. First aid in the fifth grade. First aid in the fifth grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment10>
		<segment11>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the sixth day of sixth grade, I'll tell you what he did. He went out on a field trip, the first one of the year. Backed into a sabertooth and pierced both of his ears</segment11>
		<segment12>First aid in the sixth grade. First aid in the sixth grade. First aid in the sixth grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment12>
		<segment13>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the seventh day of seventh grade, I'll tell you what he did. He tried out for the talent show to show how well he sung. Cracked a grin, a wasp flew in, and stung him on the tongue</segment13>
		<segment14>First aid in the seventh grade. First aid in the seventh grade. First aid in the seventh grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment14>
		<segment15>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the eighth day of eighth grade, I'll tell you what he did. He tried to play some basketball went up for a dunk. Landed in the bushes and got squirted by a skunk</segment15>
		<segment16>First aid in the eighth grade. First aid in the eighth grade. First aid in the eighth grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment16>
		<segment17>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the ninth day of ninth grade, I'll tell you what he did. He fed the pigs on grandma's farm, two piglets and a sow. Slipped on their slop and then got stepped on by a cow</segment17>
		<segment18>First aid in the ninth grade. First aid in the ninth grade. First aid in the ninth grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment18>
		<segment19>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the tenth day of tenth grade, I'll tell you what he did. He went out on some water skis and hit a sunken log. Wiped out all the lily pads, got spit on by a frog</segment19>
		<segment20>First aid in the tenth grade. First aid in the tenth grade. First aid in the tenth grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment20>
		<segment21>Now Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the eleventh day of eleventh grade, I'll tell you what he did. He swept and missed an alley cat while taking driver's ed. Ran into a tree and bumped the dashboard with his head</segment21>
		<segment22>First aid in the eleventh grade. First aid in the eleventh grade. First aid in the eleventh grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid</segment22>
		<segment23>Now.. Billy Joe McGuffrey was a really clumsy kid. On the twelfth day of twelfth grade, I'll tell you what he did. He walked into financial aid, fell and broke a bone. Showed them all his bills and got a great big college loan</segment23>
		<segment24>First aid in the twelfth grade. First aid in the twelfth grade. First aid in the twelfth grade. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid. You could buy a zoo with all the doctor bills he paid!    </segment24>
	</english>
</song>
