<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Blue Sweater </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I haven't heard your voice in a while, I miss the sound. I wanna see your face but you're in another place, oh, another town. Why did you have to leave on a trip that would take you away from me?. You're a thousand miles away but I know you hear this melody</segment1>
		<segment2>I'll play the sweet sound of your voice inside my head. Like a record. And I'll smell the wonderful scent, oh, you captured within. Your blue sweater. I wish every time you came into my mind I could. Write you a letter. Words can't contain what I feel so for now, I'll just wait 'til. We're together. I'll hold on to your blue sweater, yeah</segment2>
		<segment3>In my mind, I bring you back here. For as long as I allow. Oh, hurry, I'm starting to worry. I'll forget you now, but I don't know how. So I'll count down the days 'til I see you again. Who knew that it would feel like 200 years 'til then?</segment3>
		<segment4>So I'll play the sweet sound of your voice inside my head. Like a record. And I'll smell the wonderful scent, oh, you captured within. Your blue sweater. I wish every time you came into my mind I could. Write you a letter. Words can't contain what I feel so for now, I'll just wait 'til. We're together. I'll hold on to your blue sweater</segment4>
		<segment5>It's the one that I (?) given. If you have been, too, (?) listen. Take this chance with me 'cause we're living, yeah</segment5>
		<segment6>I'll play the sweet sound of your voice inside my head. Like a record. And I'll smell the wonderful scent, oh, you captured within. Your blue sweater. I wish every time you came into my mind I could. Write you a letter. Words can't contain what I feel so for now, I'll just wait 'til. We're together. I'll hold on to your blue sweater</segment6>
		<segment7>I'll play the sweet sound of your voice inside my head. Like a record (like a record). Like a record. Like a record     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
