<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Born Above </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>In the day he went about on the streets. Doing run of the mill Pharisee things. At night he met with his master, the Lord, he said. Show us what You mean. I'm a sage but You're highly divine. Your wisdom's respected you're second-to-none, top of the line. Oh. Jesus said, If you're born from above. You can get that. You can go where I'm at. You gotta get it while you're young. 'Cause you can't find much, baby till you're born above. That's what He told Him. Yeah, He said to Him, you must be born again. If you want God to increase your vision. Just like the wind blows just where it wills. The same thing happens to Christians. You never see it make its path yet somehow you know. Baby, whenever it blows past. Oh. Will you walk with Me out on the water?. Cause baby I can prepare you to know the Father. If you wanna know, here's the deal: You must become a little child. If you wanna know that God is real. Oh, let Me show you. Beyond this planet, Heaven's got a home. Seems like it's really far. The world's unaware but it's really near. And they don't have to look so hard. The amusing part is it's there in your heart. Yet it's somehow out of reach in your midst. You gotta die with Me daily or you're waitin' to die. And get everlasting death. The highway's jammed with folks whose steering's. Gonna get them burned alive. Well, everybody wants on the road to God. But there's no way there but Mine. Together, Nicky, we can live at this address. I'll scrub you of all the badness in your soul. Oh. Someday when you're born again. You're gonna get to that place that you really wanna go. And you'll walk with the Son. But till then can't find much baby till you're born above. C'mon with Me -- can't find much baby till you're born above   . C'mon with Me -- can't find much baby till you're born above.     </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
