<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Boy Moves To A New Town With Optimistic Outlook </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Just woke up, it's a brand-new day. So many things that I wanna say. It's been a while since I've felt this way. Everything's ok, nothing feels broken</segment1>
		<segment2>First day in a brand-new town. What will it be like, will it all go down?. Everyday I'm gonna write this down. Right here in my diary</segment2>
		<segment3>And all this time, while the world passes us by. What will we leave behind, but the pages of our lives?. And if we take our time, I bet we can all find. The things in life worth living for</segment3>
		<segment4>One thing I know is that when life's moving slow. I'm not out here on my own, I've got You (to get me through this). I'm on a long journey through mountains of apathy. And I'm not afraid to walk through</segment4>
		<segment5>Everywhere I look it's all so different. Another city but it makes no difference. Still going through the same old issues. Everything's ok, nothing feels broken</segment5>
		<segment6>With the days of the old behind me. Another summer and I feel like climbing. Write another page while the sun's still shining. Right here in my diary</segment6>
		<segment7>And all this time, while the world passes us by. What will we leave behind, but the pages of our lives?. And if we take our time, I bet we can all find. The things in life worth living for</segment7>
		<segment8>One thing I know is that when life's moving slow. I'm not our here on my own, I've got You (to get me through this). I'm on a long journey through mountains of apathy. And I'm not afraid to walk through</segment8>
		<segment9>Fading, hating, waiting for some place where I can fit in. Show me, grow me, hold me, till my balance starts to set in. Fading, hating, waiting for some place where I can fit in. Show me, grow me, hold me, till my balance starts to set in</segment9>
		<segment10>All this time, while the world passes us by. What will we leave behind, but the pages of our lives?. And if we take our time, I bet we can all find. The things in life worth living for</segment10>
		<segment11>(2, 3, 4)</segment11>
		<segment12>One thing I know is that when life's moving slow. I'm not out here on my own, I've got You (to get me through this). I'm on a long journey through mountains of apathy. And I'm not afraid to walk through    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
