<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Breaking Through </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I am a blind man trying to find the way. A deaf man with my ear to the ground. Just listening for what You say</segment1>
		<segment2>I've got no voice to sing the songs. Written by the prophets on the subway walls. The kingdom is a golden table and we are beggars all</segment2>
		<segment3>Are these just some words that I say aloud?. Is this just the sun breaking through the clouds?. Oh, I know it's more and I know somehow that. Heaven is breaking through. And it's You, it's You, it's You, it's You, You</segment3>
		<segment4>I've wandered deserts looking for a sign. A wild flower in a valley low. Just reaching for the light</segment4>
		<segment5>I have no place to lay my head, no sanctuary of my own. The kingdom waits with open arms. For pilgrims headed home</segment5>
		<segment6>Are these just some words that I say aloud?. Is this just the sun breaking through the clouds?. Oh, I know it's more and I know somehow that. Heaven is breaking through. And it's You, it's You, it's You, it's You, it's You</segment6>
		<segment7>(I am a blind man trying to find the way). I'm looking for. (I am a blind man trying to find the way). Heaven is breaking, heaven is breaking. (I am a blind man trying to find the way). Heaven is breaking through</segment7>
		<segment8>Heaven is breaking, heaven is breaking. (I am a blind man trying to find the way). Heaven is breaking through. Oh, heaven is breaking, heaven is breaking. (I am a blind man trying to find the way). Heaven is breaking through</segment8>
		<segment9>Heaven is breaking, heaven is breaking. (I am a blind man trying to find the way). Heaven is breaking through. And it's You, it's You, it's You, it's You, yeah. It's You, it's You, it's You, You</segment9>
		<segment10>I am a blind man trying to find the way    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
