<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Breathing </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I'm finding my way back to sanity again. Though I don't really know what I'm gonna do when I get there. I take a breath and hold on tight. Spin around one more time. And gracefully fall back to the arms of grace </segment1>
		<segment2>Cause I am hanging on every word you're saying. Even if you don't wanna speak tonight. That's alright, alright with me. Cause I want nothing more than to sit outside heaven's door. And listen to you breathing. Its where I wanna be, yeah. Where I wanna be </segment2>
		<segment3>I'm looking past the shadows in my mind into the truth. And I'm trying to identify the voices in my head. God wish won't you. Let me feel one more time what if feels like to feel. And break these caluses off me one more time </segment3>
		<segment4>Cause I am hanging on every word you're saying. Even if you don't wanna speak tonight. That's alright, alright with me. Cause I want nothing more than to sit outside of your door. And listen to you breathing. Its where I wanna be, yeah </segment4>
		<segment5>Oh I don't want a thing from you. Bet you're tired of me waiting for. The scraps to fall off of your table to the ground. La da da da.. Cause I just wanna be here now </segment5>
		<segment6>Cause I am hanging on every word you're saying. Even if you don't wanna speak tonight. That's alright, alright with me. Cause I want nothing more than to sit outside heaven's door. And listen to you breathing. Its where I wanna be, yeah. Where I wanna be </segment6>
		<segment7>Cause I am hanging on every word you're saying. Even if you don't wanna speak tonight. That's alright, alright with me. Cause I want nothing more than to sit outside heaven's door. And listen to you breathing. Its where I wanna be, yeah. Where I wanna be    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
