<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Brianna </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It was a good night I stayed on key. Me and the drummer were on the same beat. Had coordination in both my feet. Oh what a night!</segment1>
		<segment2>I took off my guitar and i met you. sweet little angel beneath the moon. The stars were shining and so were you. Then i saw the light</segment2>
		<segment3>So i took your fingers to my face. And with the tips began to trace. The way that my eyes and my mouth were shaped. And you had your sight. for a moment that night</segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus: Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. What a delight</segment4>
		<segment5>Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. I see you in the daylight</segment5>
		<segment6>You're only seven and you taught me. Life is much more than what we see. Behind the veil of history. Til faith becomes sight. (believing is seeing)</segment6>
		<segment7>Cause there's so much beauty to behold. A world of wonder to unfold. Safe with a pure in the heart and soul. Who turn on the light. In the dark of the night</segment7>
		<segment8>Chorus</segment8>
		<segment9>I talked to your mother the other day. And she told me you passed away. I couldnt find the words to say. I started to cry</segment9>
		<segment10>She said when the heart begins to ache. She can remember you in a place. Looking at Jesus face to face. Oh what a delight you got to sight. His hands in the light. You can see me tonight</segment10>
		<segment11>Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Yeah!!!</segment11>
		<segment12>Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Yeah!!!</segment12>
		<segment13>You can see me tonight. You can see me tonight. You can see me tongiht. Yeah!!!</segment13>
		<segment14>See it was a good night. Sure was a good night. It was a good night. Yeah!!!</segment14>
		<segment15>Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Bye Bye Brianna. Yeah!!!</segment15>
		<segment16>I see you in the daylight. I see you in the daylight. I see you in the daylight. Yeah!. (repeat 2X)</segment16>
		<segment17>Nanny. Papa. Sister goddy. Aunt vie. Uncle jackson. Uncle davis. Brianna</segment17>
		<segment18>C YA!!    </segment18>
	</english>
</song>
