<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Brick By Boring Brick </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Well, she lives in a fairy tale. Somewhere too far for us to find. Forgotten the taste and smell. Of the world that she's left behind</segment1>
		<segment2>It's all about the exposure. The lens I told her. The angles were all wrong now. She's ripping wings off of butterflies</segment2>
		<segment3>Keep your feet on the ground. When your head's in the clouds</segment3>
		<segment4>Well, go get your shovel. And we'll dig a deep hole. To bury the castle, bury the castle</segment4>
		<segment5>Go get your shovel. And we'll dig a deep hole. To bury the castle, bury the castle</segment5>
		<segment6>So one day he found her crying. Coiled up on the dirty ground. Her prince finally came to save her. And the rest you can figure out</segment6>
		<segment7>But it was a trick and the clock struck twelve. Well, make sure to build your heart. Brick by boring brick. Or the wolf's gonna blow it down</segment7>
		<segment8>Keep your feet on the ground. When your head's in the clouds</segment8>
		<segment9>Well, go get your shovel. And we'll dig a deep hole. To bury the castle, bury the castle</segment9>
		<segment10>Go get your shovel. And we'll dig a deep hole. And we'll bury the castle, bury the castle</segment10>
		<segment11>Well, you built up a world of magic. Because your real life is tragic. Yeah, you built up a world of magic</segment11>
		<segment12>If it's not real. You can't hold it in your hand. You can't feel it with your heart. And I won't believe it</segment12>
		<segment13>But if it's true. You can see it with your eyes. Oh, even in the dark. And that's where I want to be, yeah</segment13>
		<segment14>Go get your shovel. And we'll dig a deep hole. To bury the castle, bury the castle</segment14>
		<segment15>Go get your shovel. And we'll dig a deep hole. To bury the castle, bury the castle    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
