<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Bring 'Em Out </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>All the girls and the boys. And people making noise. Just let me hear you shout. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!). Pump up your fist. If you twist like this. 'Til the lights go out. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!) </segment1>
		<segment2>All the girls and the boys. And people making noise. Just let me hear you shout. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!). Pump up your fist. If you twist like this. 'Til the lights go out. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!)</segment2>
		<segment3>Katy. I don't know why I even try. 'Cause lately. You're always out with other guys. Pretty baby. Don't you know I'll treat you right. I'll go crazy. If you ask me out tonight </segment3>
		<segment4>Hey, hey, hey hey!. Hey, hey, hey hey hey! </segment4>
		<segment5>All this time can't get it off my mind. Dance the night away. Keep rocking. When the groove's alright. Rocking all night. I want to hear you say </segment5>
		<segment6>All the girls and the boys. And people making noise. Just let me hear you shout. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!). Pump up your fists. If you twist like this. 'Til the lights go out. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!) </segment6>
		<segment7>Wake up. I'm calling you up I need a ride. We're gonna shake up. So hurry it up no wasting time. The girls in their makeup. (Red black and white). Exchanging looks tonight. I just ran into some other friends of mine. Someone's comming 'round to pick them up at nine</segment7>
		<segment8>Hey, hey, hey hey!. Hey, hey, hey hey hey! </segment8>
		<segment9>All this time can't get it off my mind. Dance the night away. Keep rocking. When the groove's alright. Rocking all night. I wanna hear you say</segment9>
		<segment10>All this time can't get it off my mind. Dance the night away. Keep rocking. When the groove's alright. Rocking all night. Shake it shake it up until we break it. We won't stop till we just can't take it </segment10>
		<segment11>Everybody move to the beat, come on. Everybody move to the beat, come on. Everybody rock to the break of dawn. Everybody else just sing along </segment11>
		<segment12>Everybody move to the beat, come on. Everybody move to the beat, come on. Everybody rock to the break of dawn. Everybody else just sing along </segment12>
		<segment13>Everybody move to the beat, come on. Everybody move to the beat, come on. Everybody rock to the break of dawn. Everybody else just sing along </segment13>
		<segment14>All this time cant get it off my mind. Dance the night away. When the groove's all right. Rockin all night. I wanna hear you say </segment14>
		<segment15>All this time cant get it off my mind. Dance the night away. When the groove's all right. Rockin all night. I wanna hear you say </segment15>
		<segment16>All the girls and the boys. And people making noise. Just let me hear you shout. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!). Pump up your fist. If you twist like this. 'Til the lights go out. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!)</segment16>
		<segment17>All the girls and the boys. And people making noise. Just let me hear you shout. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!). Pump up your fist. If you twist like this. 'Til the lights go out. (Bring 'em out! Bring 'em out!)</segment17>
		<segment18>.     </segment18>
	</english>
</song>
