<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Bring Your Praise </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1> [Verse:]. Everything about you. Looks like you're defeated. Came here with a bible. But I can tell you ain't read it. And you're full of complaints (complaints). I can think of 10 reasons. That you should give him praise. Here's a good one you're still breathing</segment1>
		<segment2>[Bridge:]. Everything you're going through. My God's gonna fix it for you. But you got to be willing to do the things he wants you to do. He wants you to lift your hands. He wants you to move your feet. He wants to see you dance. He wants to hear you sing</segment2>
		<segment3>[Chorus:]. So when your back is against the wall (you betta bring your praise). When your family in trouble (you betta bring your praise). When you step up on your job (you betta bring your praise). When you're up against the devil (you betta bring your praise). When you about to go to war (you betta bring your praise). When you gotta fight 'em off (you betta bring your praise). Before you go to battle (you betta bring your praise). You bettah bring your praise (you betta bring your praise)</segment3>
		<segment4>[Verse:]. Come on church now. Won't you let me invite you. Into the praise party (into the praise party). I'm here to recruit you. Into the praise only. There's nothing in your closet (There's nothing in your closet). That would let a praise?. I can tell you wanna holla. I can see the praise on you</segment4>
		<segment5>[Bridge]</segment5>
		<segment6>I got amazing but he wants you to praise him. He could do anything but he wants you to praise him. Don't think it's crazy when the rest start to praise him. If you want to see amazing, all you gotta do is praise him</segment6>
		<segment7>[Chorus:]. So when your back is against the wall (you betta bring your praise). When your family in trouble (you betta bring your praise). When you step up on your job (you betta bring your praise). When you're up against the devil (you betta bring your praise). When you about to go to war (you betta bring your praise). When you gotta fight 'em off (you betta bring your praise). Before you go to battle (you betta bring your praise). You bettah bring your praise (you betta bring your praise)</segment7>
		<segment8>Clap clap clap your hands. Clap clap clap (everybody go). Clap clap clap your hands. Clap clap clap (everybody go)</segment8>
		<segment9>See you gotta learn to praise no matter what you're going through</segment9>
		<segment10>I got amazing but he wants you to praise him. He could do anything but he wants you to praise him. Don't think it's crazy when the rest start to praise him. If you want to see amazing, all you gotta do is praise him</segment10>
		<segment11>[Chorus:]. So when your back is against the wall (you betta bring your praise). When your family in trouble (you betta bring your praise). When you step up on your job (you betta bring your praise). When you're up against the devil (you betta bring your praise). When you about to go to war (you betta bring your praise). When you gotta fight 'em off (you betta bring your praise). Before you go to battle (you betta bring your praise). You bettah bring your praise (you betta bring your praise)    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
