<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Broken Wing </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Here comes an opening, she's gotta broken wing, If you can feel the sting, Take care of everything, if she can make a scene, I'll show you what I mean</segment1>
		<segment2>She pack a loaded gun, set fire to anyone, Knows how to make 'em run, She's down on sixth street, she's goin' sixty, She'll show you how to breathe</segment2>
		<segment3>I don't want to see, I don't want to be, I don't wanna be anyone, anymore, I don't want to fake, I don't want to break, I don't wanna say anything, anymore</segment3>
		<segment4>Every time you walk away, I wish you'd stay, Instead of pushin' further away, Every time I hear you say, I just need one, to take this pain away</segment4>
		<segment5>You're a broken wing, not a broken thing, You can heal in time, if you try, It'll be okay, you can walk away, Sweet Julia..</segment5>
		<segment6>Here comes an opening, he's gotta broken wing, If you can feel the sting, Take care of everything, if he can make a scene, I'll show you what I mean. He packs a loaded gun, set fire to anyone, Knows how to make 'em run, He's down on sixth street, he's goin' sixty, He'll show you how to breathe</segment6>
		<segment7>I don't want to see, I don't want to be, I don't wanna be anyone, anymore. I don't want to fake, I don't want to break, I don't wanna say anything, anymore,</segment7>
		<segment8>Every time ya walk away, I wish you'd stay, Instead of pushin' further away, Every time I hear you say, I just need one, to take this pain away. You're a broken wing, not a broken thing, You can heal in time, if you try, It'll be okay, you can walk away, Sweet Julia..</segment8>
		<segment9>And I won't laugh, I won't look, I won't listen if you just get up, And I won't laugh, I won't look, I won't listen if you just stand</segment9>
		<segment10>Every time I lie awake, I wish I, could take it all away, Every time my heart breaks, I wish I could make it seem safe...</segment10>
		<segment11>Every time ya walk away, I wish you'd stay, Instead of pushin' further away, Every time I hear you say, I just need one, to take this pain away. You're a broken wing, not a broken thing, You can heal in time, if you try, It'll be okay, you can walk away, Julia...     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
