<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Broken Girl </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Look what hes done to you. It isnt fair. Your light was bright and new. But he didnt care. He took the heart of a little girl. And made it grow up too fast</segment1>
		<segment2>Now words like innocence. Dont mean a thing. You hear the music play. But you cant sing. Those pictures in your mind. Keep you locked up inside your past</segment2>
		<segment3>This is a song for the broken girl. The one pushed aside by the cold, cold world. You are. Hear me when I say. Youre not the worthless they made you feel. There is a Love they can never steal away. And you dont have to stay the broken girl</segment3>
		<segment4>Those damaged goods you see. In your reflection. Love sees them differently. Love sees perfection. A beautiful display. Of healing on the way tonight. Tonight</segment4>
		<segment5>Look what hes done to you. It isnt fair. Your light was bright and new. But he didnt care. He took the heart of a little girl. And made it grow up too fast</segment5>
		<segment6>Now words like innocence. Dont mean a thing. You hear the music play. But you cant sing. Those pictures in your mind. Keep you locked up inside your past</segment6>
		<segment7>This is a song for the broken girl. The one pushed aside by the cold, cold world. You are. Hear me when I say. Youre not the worthless they made you feel. There is a Love they can never steal away. And you dont have to stay the broken girl, girl. You don't have to stay the broken girl, girl</segment7>
		<segment8>Let your tears touch the ground. Lay all your shattered pieces down. And be amazed by how Grace can take a broken girl. And put her back together again</segment8>
		<segment9>This is a song for the broken girl. The one pushed aside by the cold, cold world. You are. Hear me when I say. You're not the worthless they made you feel. There is a Love they can never steal away. And you don't have to stay the broken girl, girl. You don't have to stay the broken girl, girl. You don't have to stay the broken girl    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
