<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Butterfly Kisses </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>There's two things I know for sure. She was sent here from Heaven. And she's daddys little girl. As I drop to my knees by her bed at night. She talks to Jesus and I close my eyes. And I thank God for all of the joy in my life. Oh but most of all </segment1>
		<segment2>For butterlfy kisses after bedtime prayer. Stickin little white flowers all up in her hair. Walk beside the pony dady. It's my first ride. I know the cake looks funny daddy. But i sure tried. Oh with all that I've done wrong. I must have done something right. TO deseve a hug every mornin. And butterfly kisses at night</segment2>
		<segment3>Sweet 16 today. She's lookin like her mama. A little more every day. One part woman. The other part girl. To perfume and mke up. From ribbons and curls. Trying her wongs out in a great big world. But I remember </segment3>
		<segment4>Butterlfy kisses after bedtime prayer. Stickin little white flowers all up in her hair. You know how much I love you dady. But if you don't mind. I'm only gonna kiss you on the check this time. Oh with all that I've done wrong. I muct have done something right. To deserve her love every mornin. And butterfly kisses at night</segment4>
		<segment5>All the precious time. Like the wind the years go by. Precious Butterfly. Spread yuor wings and fly</segment5>
		<segment6>She'll change her name today. She'll make a promise and I'll give her aways. Standing in the bride room just starin at her. She asked me what I'm thinkin. And I said I'm not sure. I just feel like I'm loosin my baby girl. And she leaned over </segment6>
		<segment7>And gave me butterfly kisses with her mama there. Stickin little white flowers all up in her hair. Walk me down the isle daddy. It's just about time. Does my wedding gown look pretty daddy?. Daddys don't cry. Oh with all that I've done wrong. I must have done something right. To deserve her love every mornin and butterfly kisses. I couldn't ask GOd for more than this is what love is. I know I've got to let her go but I'll always remember. Every hug in the mornin and butterly kisses    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
