<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Called My Wife </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Called my wife Eve, the serpent he jumped in. Jumped in cause he was never good for nothing. Nothing cept his lies and his empty boasts. Closed our foolish eyes and he ended our hopes. All life long Ill remember the day. When Eden was around now its taken away. Eve says just to deal with it I feel morose. When it costs the life of a sheep or goat. Calm down this aint recess. I wanna tell you the rest. And if I give you a test. Sons, you two both better do your best. Sacrifice something that matters. Like Abel did with his sheep. Cause youre my reason to breathe. Dont want my sons ending up like me. Cmon my sons listen up I plead. Cain, dont let it go to waste. I love you, dont just vegetate. Hates keeping you down. Abel, yeah, youre going great. I love you, but I hesitate. Cains sneaking around. When I found out we need covered. I covered up with some leaves. I made a one-piece for Eve. Over the shoulders down to the knees. Didnt get any closer to making both of us wise. It left me empty inside. From then on Ive got something to hide. From then on Ive got something to hide. Cain, dont let this grow to rage. I love you, whyd you make that face. Snakes seeking you out. Abel, yeah, I know your faith. I love you, but you aint that safe. Cains creeping me out. Called my wife Ive been searchin since sunset. Something must be wrong have you seen our sons yet. Not yet but I spy someone gettin close. Closer, yes, its Cain at the end of the road. Oh, my son, whats that thing on your face. And Abels not around whered you take him today. He was in the field with you I fear you know. You look kind of like youve just seen a ghost. My son, son, what have you just done. Son, son, tell me what have you just done. Son, my son, Cain, I dont wanna guess. Cain you better go away. I love you but I hate that snake. Cant keep him around. Abel, what a total waste. Id love to go and take your place. Laid deep in the ground. Done, done, on to the next son. Done, Im done, now Im warning you Seth    </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
