<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Cartoons [Live] </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I was thinkin' the other day. &quot;What if cartoons got saved?. They'd start singing praise. In a whole new way&quot;</segment1>
		<segment2>Yeah, I was thinkin' the other day. &quot;What if cartoons got saved?. They'd start singing praise. In a whole new way&quot;, Yeah yeah</segment2>
		<segment3>Fred and Wilma Flintstone. Sing, &quot;Yabba dabba do yah&quot;. Scooby Doo and Shaggy. &quot;Scooby dooby doo yah&quot;. And the Jetsons' dog named Astro. &quot;Rough rough roo yah&quot;</segment3>
		<segment4>'Cause, I was thinkin' the other day. &quot;What if cartoons got saved?. They'd start singing praise. In a whole new way&quot;, Yeah yeah yeah</segment4>
		<segment5>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles. &quot;Cowabunga loo yah, dude&quot;. Then there's, Kermit the Frog here, singing. &quot;High ho le loo yah&quot;. And that little bald guy, Elmer Fudd. &quot;How ay woo yah&quot;</segment5>
		<segment6>'Cause, I was thinkin' the other day. &quot;What if cartoons got saved?. They'd start singing praise. In a whole new way&quot;</segment6>
		<segment7>Oh, that big old moose and his friend Rocky. &quot;Bullwinkle loo yah&quot;. And our favourite bear named Yogi. &quot;Hey, boo boo boo loo ya&quot;. Then there's all those little blue guys. And they'd sing, &quot;Hah la la la la la la la la lay loo yah&quot;. How about Beavis and that other guy?. &quot;Nah&quot;</segment7>
		<segment8>Now, there's a point to this looney tune. I'm not an Anamaniac. But there's a lot of praisin' to do. And cartoons were made for that. It's our God, yeah yeah yeah. So, let's sing Hallelujah</segment8>
		<segment9>Hallelujah. Hallelujah. Hallelujah. Hallelujah</segment9>
		<segment10>Yabba dabba do yah. Scooby dooby doo yah. Rough rough roo yah.     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
