<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Chapstick, Chaped Lips And Things Like Chemistry </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>ok, so, who doesn't own a cell phone. who brought back their permission slip. because i know nobody wants to stay home. while the rest of us go out and make a day of it</segment1>
		<segment2>cause theme parks are so much more fun when the sun's outside. and i lost my phone to the lake beneath the batman ride</segment2>
		<segment3>they're starting something, and i don't want to begin it. they're looking for trouble, but with me it won't be found. and i regret that i'm completely out of daytime minutes. and so i guess i'll have to wait a lot till 8 o'clock comes around</segment3>
		<segment4>ok, so, who doesn't own a cell phone. well i don't need to ask my friends. because i know mine was fastened to my jawbone. thanks to all those nights and weekends</segment4>
		<segment5>cause theme parks are so much more fun when the sun's outside. and i lost my phone to the lake beneath the batman ride</segment5>
		<segment6>they're starting something, and i don't want to begin it. they're looking for trouble, but with me it won't be found. and i regret that i'm completely out of daytime minutes. and so i guess i'll have to wait a lot till 8 o'clock comes around</segment6>
		<segment7>when it comes to relationships i'm the dumbest one. and i don't mean just with girls, i mean with everyone. your illustrations always point out just what's wrong with me. it's chapstick, and chapped lips, and things like chemistry</segment7>
		<segment8>it's chapstick, and chapped lips, and things like. it's chapstick, and chapped lips, and things like. it's chapstick, and chapped lips, and things like chemistry</segment8>
		<segment9>can i relate to you the way you relate to me. can you help me out with my chemistry. i don't want to be precieved the way i am. i just want to be percieved the way i am    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
