<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Choke </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>If every star fell out of the sky tonight. Every wish Id make would take me closer to you. Have you ever wanted something so bad it hurts?. To never wake from the world that you once knew. (repeat)</segment1>
		<segment2>You said we'll meet where the dreams are made. So I'll climb in my battered ship and voyage to the ends of the earth. Closing my eyes and setting sail on the dark waves. We'll suck this dream world dry of every ounce of love that it's worth</segment2>
		<segment3>Ive fallen and I cant get up, such intoxicating synergy. Flying to the highest mountains and swimming through the darkest deepest seas</segment3>
		<segment4>I'll search for what mother nature finds most divine. Lets get lost in this moment, Ill do anything to make you mine. Inhaling each others ecstasies, admiring your God-given design. Together forever, finally our souls can intertwine</segment4>
		<segment5>We'll wake the dead tonight to tell them all about the love we found. Sitting and listening to the dry bones crawl out of the ground. They'll dance till dusk with great bliss and celebration. And then they'll hide like the moon when it sees the sun</segment5>
		<segment6>Ill search for what mother nature finds most divine. Lets get lost in this moment, Ill do anything to make you mine. Inhaling each others ecstasies, admiring your God-given design. Together forever, finally our souls can intertwine</segment6>
		<segment7>If every star fell out of the sky tonight. Every wish Id make would take me to you. Have you ever wanted something so bad it hurts?. To never wake from the world that you once knew. (repeat)</segment7>
		<segment8>You said we'll meet where dreams are made. So I'll climb in my battered ship and voyage to the ends of the earth. Closing my eyes and setting sail on the dark waves. We'll suck this dream world dry of every ounce of love it's worth    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
