<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Chorus Of Angels </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Chorus of Angels. Destroy my silence. That haunts me. That claims me. While darkness walks beside me </segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus of Angels. Destroy my silence. That haunts me. That claims me. While darkness walks beside me </segment2>
		<segment3>[Chorus:]. I saw the Angels sing along to wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Their voices will rise to test the strength of man. Wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Wake up. wake up now, wake up now (ambient) </segment3>
		<segment4>We will see the fire. We will see. The skies will open up. The sky will open. The clouds will burn red and our sins will forget us. Our sins will forget us. And time will not shake us. Our hearts are made of gold. Made of gold. These walls won't over take us. These walls won't over take us. Over take us </segment4>
		<segment5>[Chorus:]. I saw the Angels sing along to wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Their voices will rise to test the strength of man. Wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Wake up </segment5>
		<segment6>We will see the fire. We will see. The skies will open up. The sky will open. The clouds will burn red and our sins will forget us. Our sins will forget us. And time will not shake us. Our hearts are made of gold. Made of gold. These walls won't over take us. These walls won't over take us. Over take us </segment6>
		<segment7>[Chorus:]. I saw the Angels sing along to wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Beautiful sleeping world. Their voices will rise to test the strength of man. Wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Wake up </segment7>
		<segment8>Chorus of Angels. Destroy my silence. That haunts me. That claims me. While darkness walks beside me </segment8>
		<segment9>Chorus of Angels. Destroy my silence. That haunts me. That claims me. While darkness walks beside me </segment9>
		<segment10>[Chorus:]. I saw the Angels sing along to wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Chorus of Angels, wake me, wake me. I saw the Angels sing, wake up the beautiful sleeping world. Wake up, lay the foundations, the foundations of the earth, of the earth </segment10>
		<segment11>Wake up now, wake up now, wake up now, wake up now, wake up now, wake up now, wake up now, wake up now, wake (ambient fade out).     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
