<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Churches and Serial Killers </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>There is a part of me that always sees the easy way out. If it doesn't hurt, then not another word. You keep the reasons all but hidden, it feels like we will drown. Do I hold on, when it's so far gone? </segment1>
		<segment2>To recall all the footsteps in the hall, with our loose lips. Chemicals in the bloodstream. Start the surgery. Take care not to hurt me. </segment2>
		<segment3>Send the signal. Send the signal. Send the signal. Send the signal. </segment3>
		<segment4>There is a part of me that always sees the easy way out. (Is this the easy way?). If it doesn't hurt, then not another word. (then take me back inside..). You keep the reasons all but hidden, it feels like we will drown. (is this is where we were..). Do I hold on, when it's so far gone? </segment4>
		<segment5>Brush the skin; blood involved. Lose the voice. She rejoices if I'm all alone. Beauty takes more than anything. But I can't stop whats inside of me. </segment5>
		<segment6>Send the signal. Send the signal. Send the signal. Send the signal. </segment6>
		<segment7>There is a part of me that always sees the easy way out. (Is this the easy way?). If it doesn't hurt, then not another word. (then take me back inside..). You keep the reasons all but hidden, it feels like we will drown. (is this is where we were..). Do I hold on, when it's so far gone? </segment7>
		<segment8>Is there a chance, just a chance that you need me?. Or are we better off thinking that in this dance the romance is a secret?. But I'm not quite sure I believe it. </segment8>
		<segment9>With my eyes, with my words, slowly rise and fall.. (Catch me, I'm slipping through). Slowly rise and fall. (Catch me, I'm slipping through). Slowly rise and fall. (Catch me, I'm slipping through your fingers)    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
