<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Citadel </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19,segment20,segment21</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>How ferocious are we, a head full of poison, And a pen to bleed dry, like the valley of bones.</segment1>
		<segment2>We have gathered our sins, and soaked them in wine. We have cheated this world, made it out with our head on our shoulders now..</segment2>
		<segment3>Why can't we call this even?. Why do you care that I,</segment3>
		<segment4>Would need another reason, To tell you lies?</segment4>
		<segment5>Keep moving like we never had a choice, I'm burning this citadel to the ground. Wake up as our broken bodies collide,</segment5>
		<segment6>If we're going down, we're going down with a fight.</segment6>
		<segment7>Keep moving on, keep dreaming on.</segment7>
		<segment8>We we're sly as hell, and lived like the wolves, But our crooked smiles, have disappeared.</segment8>
		<segment9>We have gathered our sins, and soaked them in wine. We have cheated this world, made it out with our head on our shoulders now..</segment9>
		<segment10>Why can't we call this even?. Why do you care that I,</segment10>
		<segment11>Would need another reason, To tell you lies?</segment11>
		<segment12>Keep moving like we never had a choice, I'm burning this citadel to the ground. Wake up as our broken bodies collide,</segment12>
		<segment13>If we're going down, we're going down with a fight.</segment13>
		<segment14>Keep moving on, keep dreaming on. Keep moving on, keep dreaming on.</segment14>
		<segment15>I fall asleep with twisted dreams,</segment15>
		<segment16>What'd you do because I just can't seem to shake this?. I fall asleep with twisted dreams, What'd you do because I can't move on without this?. I fall asleep with twisted dreams,</segment16>
		<segment17>What'd you do because I just can't seem to shake this?. I fall asleep with twisted dreams, What'd you do because I can't move on without this?</segment17>
		<segment18>Keep moving like we never had a choice,</segment18>
		<segment19>I'm burning this citadel to the ground. Wake up as our broken bodies collide, If we're going down, we're going down with a fight.</segment19>
		<segment20>Keep moving on, keep dreaming on.</segment20>
		<segment21>Keep moving on, keep dreaming on.     </segment21>
	</english>
</song>
