<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>City Lights </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>These city lights burn so bright. But inside there is a darkness. Oh why do I feel helpless. The whole world in my sights. But I'm still reaching. for something in the distance</segment1>
		<segment2>Was it you that disappeared. Or did I turn away. Am I the one to blame. For my own heart ache</segment2>
		<segment3>We used to be so close. But with time we drifted apart. Now I'm on my way down the road. To where you are to find your heart</segment3>
		<segment4>It's like the highway never ends. This road is getting narrow. I travel to the mountains. Drove the sunset</segment4>
		<segment5>Was it you that disappeared. Or did I turn away. Am I the one to blame. For my own mistakes</segment5>
		<segment6>We used to be so close. But with time we've drifted apart. Now I'm on my way down the road. To where you are to find your heart</segment6>
		<segment7>We used to be so close. But we drifted apart. Now I'm on my way down the road. To where you are to find your heart</segment7>
		<segment8>This is where I want to be. This is where you're calling me. To travel down this road. This narrow road. The straight and narrow. It's the straight and narrow. The straight and narrow. This is where I wanna be. Oh, this is where you're calling me. On the straight and narrow</segment8>
		<segment9>We used to be so close. We used to be so close</segment9>
		<segment10>And we used to be so close. But with time we've drifted apart. Now I'm on my way down the road. To where you are to find your heart</segment10>
		<segment11>We used to be so close. But we drifted apart. I'm finding you on this road. On this road</segment11>
		<segment12>This narrow road. This narrow road. This narrow road. This is where I want to be     </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
