<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>City Boy </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>He wakes up, wakes up early today. He doesn't feel like, feel like going through this routine day. Uh, oh, he runs to, runs to catch a spot on the subway. He gets to, gets to work, it's 5 past 8</segment1>
		<segment2>But when he sees her he's not just a typical city boy. She makes him feel like so much more. She helped him believe, things are more than they seem. And have some hope</segment2>
		<segment3>His friends, they, friends, they laugh and say he's crazy. Because he believes his life will really go somewhere. Oh, I know that, know that sometimes life seems so unfair. But some day, some day I know he'll get there</segment3>
		<segment4>'Cause when he sees her he's not just a typical city boy. She makes him feel like so much more. She helped him believe, things are more than they seem. And have some hope</segment4>
		<segment5>Again, oh, again, again</segment5>
		<segment6>He wakes up this morning, he finds his luck run out. In fact he hears a warning, can he be enough?. Can people see that, see that he's too good to be true. And it's hard to believe after all he has been through</segment6>
		<segment7>I never seen someone so filled with love like you. Visit http://www.xtralyrics.com. How can it be you, be you cannot see it too?</segment7>
		<segment8>Because to me he is a not just a typical city boy. Because to me he is so much more. He helped me believe, things are more than they seem. And to have some hope</segment8>
		<segment9>Not not just a typical city boy. She makes him feel like so much more. She helped him believe, things are more than they seem. And have some hope</segment9>
		<segment10>Again, oh, again, again</segment10>
		<segment11>Because he's so much more and he's so much more. He's so much more to me. So much more, he's so much more to me    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
