<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Come Around </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Verse 1:</segment1>
		<segment2>Come around come around.</segment2>
		<segment3>Well it was me and you on the sidewalk talking we had stopped to watch the joggers walking thinking back to the time when we first met well I admit it's hard to forget all you said it's in my head and it's telling me even in the light I got a shadow chasing me how can I shake it it's moving me all around now how can I take it when it's breaking me down. </segment3>
		<segment4>You're making it hard for me I mean it's hard to be walking around you're bringing me down when I don't wanna be and is it hard for you I mean is it hard to do livin life like a broken record doin the things you don't wanna do cuz it seems to me that we should not be together but then I miss your company.</segment4>
		<segment5>Chorus:</segment5>
		<segment6>Come around come around no please don't come around you always bring me down whenever you come around. Come around come around no please don't come around you always bring me down.</segment6>
		<segment7>You bring me down to the ground where I don't wanna be at. Why did I go and do that? </segment7>
		<segment8>Verse: 2 </segment8>
		<segment9>Well it's a new day and I got a whole new way of livin forget about the bad decisions and how I give in. Listen to my heartbeat but don't be beaten like an athlete cheatin and later is defeated. It's bitterweet thinkin I can do it on my own kid I need some friends to help me when I'm struggling and when I'm stumbling, fumblin and my world is crumblin being humbled and in need of something. Look at the addicts with habits that damage and ravage their soul. You think their really livin when they out of control? </segment9>
		<segment10>(Chorus)</segment10>
		<segment11>You bring me down. She's got a lot of good reasons and so I say as she's leaving. She's got a lot of good reasons and so I say as she's leaving. </segment11>
		<segment12>This goes out to yesterday and all the mistake that we made I'm praying they will go away ending all the memories.     </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
