<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Communication </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I was born in 82, a poor mans son. When it came to hand-me-downs he only gave me one. At first I was ungrateful, at once I was confused. He said, music is the cup for you I pour. Its all I really have, wish I could give you more. But I have to catch my ride, son, Im off to a distant shore. You see my dad gave me the keys but Id have to show myself to the door</segment1>
		<segment2>Soon the words he left were too faint to hear. And a path with no direction made it hard to steer. My soul was dry and thirsty, my mind was so unclear. While wandering around and searching there. I came across a man Id seen before I swear. And again Id see him too on a beach with the fading of the moon</segment2>
		<segment3>And hed say, Communication is calling you its all in you. No hesitation, youve got to see this through</segment3>
		<segment4>I needed something to fill me up. In my bag a gift from dad, my music cup. Well, I should have looked here first in an attempt to quench the thirst. The taste was like a melody. With words to follow so expressively. I was off to share my song and no, it wouldnt be too long. til I was standing on the stage and the crowd would sing it back to me</segment4>
		<segment5>And wed say, Communication is calling us its all in us, a celebration for you and me and the universe, our destination</segment5>
		<segment6>(How we find the answers). When we search beyond ourselves you know we always learn. (We become so clever). Let our walls crumble and burn away. (Make a change forever). Can we lend a better hand than the one that weve been dealt?. Let the music be the way we get there</segment6>
		<segment7>And we sing, La la la la la la la la</segment7>
		<segment8>I walked the beach that morning and I found my faithful friend. Waiting there with words of wisdom and a fishing rod in hand. I watched him and I listened so peculiar and so sweet. Saying Love is all that we need and communication</segment8>
		<segment9>I said, Communication is calling me and yes, its all in me</segment9>
		<segment10>The cup has served me well for fifteen years. With music in my world Ive shed some fears. And Ive tried to understand how to be a better man. There is rhythm to my life that ebbs and flows. And at times the inspiration comes and goes. But whenever it arrives, well, I go down a take a dive. When I swim up to the surface I sing communication every time    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
