<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Company Car </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Mike was right when he said I'd put up. A fight to be someone. A fight to be me. But see now, I'm down. Under the pavement. Of capital hills and lowercase people. As time rolls by my dreams have become. That which is attainable. Not what I'm looking for</segment1>
		<segment2>I've got the company car. I'm the one swinging at two below par. Yeah I've become one with the ones. That I've never believed in. But I've got the company car</segment2>
		<segment3>Hey, I'm the king. Of things I've always despised. I'm the gingerbread man. Who got eaten alive. I'm half-baked, I'm fake. But see I've got hotels. On Park Place and Boardwalk. And two hundred bucks. I pass go, but oh, life's taken it's toll. Have I won Monopoly, to forfeit my soul</segment3>
		<segment4>But see I've got the company car. I'm the one swinging at two below par. Yeah I've become one with the ones. That I never believed in. But I've got the company car</segment4>
		<segment5>Yeah all the kings horses. At the foot of the wall. They're taking pictures of. The man who's lost all of his. Masks of pretension. He's got two faces left. His is the one that he hides. On the left behind that smile</segment5>
		<segment6>Hiding tears and fear. That burns like an engine. That drives him away. From the ones that he loves. Mike was right. Hey Mike, we're one and the same. We're the faceless combantants. In the loneliest game</segment6>
		<segment7>Ah but say, I'll wave as I'm driving by. With that smirk in my eye, yelling. Hey, I'm something man, check me out</segment7>
		<segment8>I've got the company car. I'm the one swinging at two below par. Yeah I've become one with the ones. That I never believed in. But I've got the company car. Yeah, check me out. I've got the company car. Yeah, check me out. I've got the company car    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
