<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Count Your Blessings The Martins </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>(Verse 1). He had family friends and money, loved the lord with all his heart. So the devil went to God and said ole Job would fall apart. If you would take away his fortune, let me put him to the test. Soon poor Job had lost his health, and wealth, and all the rest. And as his troubles added up, he fell down on his knees. He said lord I still got one thing, and thats your love for me</segment1>
		<segment2>(Chorus). You got to count your blessing, youll find one if you try. Count on the lord and watch that blessing multiply. All those might have, could have, should have beens, are nothing but distressing. When youre down and out, its time to count your blessing</segment2>
		<segment3>(Verse 2). You might go through hard times, when you fall into despair. Remember youre surrounded by his blessings everywhere. Its in a neighbors helping hand, or in the sunshine of a smile. One blessing leads to one more, youll be counting for a while. Its best to look at what you have, forget what you have not. And just learn a lesson from ole Job and give thanks for what you got</segment3>
		<segment4>(Chorus). You got to count your blessing, youll find one if you try. Count on the Lord and watch that blessing multiply. Those might have, could have, should have beens, are nothing but distressing. When youre down and out, its time to count your blessing</segment4>
		<segment5>(Bridge). One risen savior, one perfect love, one holy promise, one is enough</segment5>
		<segment6>(Chorus). You got to count your blessing, youll find one if you try. Count on the lord and watch that blessing multiply. All those might have, could have, should have beens, are nothing but distressing. When youre down and out, its time to count your blessing</segment6>
		<segment7>Count your blessing, count your blessing name them one by one, Count your blessing    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
