<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Creed </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I believe in God the Father. Almighty Maker of Heaven and Maker of Earth. And in Jesus Christ His only begotten Son, our Lord. He was conceived by the Holy Spirit. Born of the virgin Mary. Suffered under Pontius Pilate. He was crucified and dead and buried</segment1>
		<segment2>And I believe what I believe is what makes me what I am. I did not make it, no it is making me. It is the very truth of God and not the invention of any man</segment2>
		<segment3>I believe that He who suffered was crucified, buried, and dead. He descended into hell and on the third day, rose again. He ascended into Heaven where He sits at God's mighty right hand. I believe that He's returning. To judge the quick and the dead of the sons of men</segment3>
		<segment4>And I believe what I believe is what makes me what I am. I did not make it, no it is making me. It is the very truth of God and not the invention of any man</segment4>
		<segment5>I believe it, I believe it. I believe it. I believe it, I believe it</segment5>
		<segment6>I believe in God the Father. Almighty Maker of Heaven and Maker of Earth. And in Jesus Christ His only begotten Son, our Lord. I believe in the Holy Spirit. One Holy Church. The communion of Saints. The forgiveness of sin. I believe in the resurrection. I believe in a life that never ends</segment6>
		<segment7>And I believe what I believe is what makes me what I am. I did not make it, no it is making me. I did not make it, no it is making me. I said I did not make it, no it is making me. It is the very truth of God and not the invention of any man</segment7>
		<segment8>I believe it, I believe. I believe it, I believe. I believe it, I believe it. I believe it, I believe it. I believe it, I believe it. I believe it    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
