<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Cross My Heart </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>cross my heart, hope to die. i swear i won't say what happened that night. so starting today things are gonna be all right. your best you tried, and yeah you did fine. no better than fine, perfect in my mind. in fact, i wish your heart was mine. and i can hear the memory in my ears. back to the years and all those tears. but hear me when i say im glad we steered that way. because now we're here</segment1>
		<segment2>do you want to get away? get in the car we can leave today. do you want to celebrate our just made little holiday?. cus now today is your day. all that stuff you used to take. im glad you threw all that away cus now you look so great. you never need to be afraid just know yuo went the right way</segment2>
		<segment3>because even though we never get things right. and it gets so old just saying we'll keep trying. its mine to decide when ill be alright</segment3>
		<segment4>i know you're going crazy (crazy). but happy is all that you make me (all you make me). and now things are gonna get better baby. i know everything went wrong OK (OK). but now its time to get some better days (some better days). cus i don't want to keep acting this way</segment4>
		<segment5>cus man i know we never get things right. and it gets so old just saying we'll keep trying. but its mine to decide when and if ill be alright.. and thats just a thing that take time</segment5>
		<segment6>so keep going till you know when its time, when its right. keep showing yourself in that light. cus back in school man that gets cruel. but one thing is true is that man now look at you. your heart is big enough for two</segment6>
		<segment7>because i can hear the memories in my ears. back to the years and all those tears. but hear me when i say im glad because we're here</segment7>
		<segment8>i know you're going crazy (crazy). but happy is all that you make me (you make me). and now things are gonna get better baby. i know everything went wrong OK (OK). but now its time to get some better days (better days). cus i don't want to keep acting this way</segment8>
		<segment9>cus man i know we never get things right. and it gets so old just saying we'll keep trying. but its mine to decide when and if ill be alright.. and thats just a thing that take time    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
