<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Day Like Today </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Woke up this morning, jumped out of bed, Hit my head on a lampshade and the clock said. That I'm running late so I'm rushing trying to get on my way. (Huuuh)Get to my car and the gauge is on E, Get gas and i pay a dollar ninety-three (What?). Got stopped by the cops cause I was speeding. Eighty-nine in a fifty-five Lord, why me </segment1>
		<segment2>On a day like today, All has gone wrong and my life seems crazy. Gotta hold on, smile on my face. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way. On a day like today, Look up at the sky and know life's so amazing. And I know I will be okay. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way </segment2>
		<segment3>It's days like this there's a lesson learned. When I get up on the wrong side of the world. It's easy to dwell on my situation instead of every good thing. (But I know I've been blessed) I gotta say thank you. (And though there's stress) I'm still grateful. (It's just a test) He's more than able to see me through on a day </segment3>
		<segment4>On a day like today, All has gone wrong and my life seems crazy. Gotta hold on, smile on my face. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way. On a day like today, Look up at the sky and know life's so amazing. and I know I will be okay. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way </segment4>
		<segment5>I know it wouldn't hurt to smile. It's not as bad as it could be it will work out in a while (repeat) </segment5>
		<segment6>On a day like today, All has gone wrong and my life seems crazy. Gotta hold on, smile on my face. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way. On a day like today, Look up at the sky and know life's so amazing. And I know I will be okay. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way </segment6>
		<segment7>So I just hold tight, know that everything is alright. Gotta believe I will see the light. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way </segment7>
		<segment8>So I just hold tight, know that everything is alright. Gotta believe I will see the light. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way </segment8>
		<segment9>On a day like today, All has gone wrong and my life seems crazy. Gotta hold on, smile on my face. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way. On a day like today, Look up at the sky and know life's so amazing. And I know I will be okay. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way </segment9>
		<segment10>On a day like today, All has gone wrong and my life seems crazy. Gotta hold on, smile on my face. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way. On a day like today, Look up at the sky and know life's so amazing. And I know I will be okay. Cause I know the sun's gonna shine my way </segment10>
		<segment11>Suns gonna shine (yea yea). Fade out.     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
