<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Dear Charlotte </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Memory conveys that you were something to be. When you weren't held captive in an aged body. You had a family that needed you and job security. You had everything a man could ever need. But where did your children go? Where is your family?. Did they turn into the adults that you always hoped they'd be?. Did you finally retire from that job that tortured you?. I thought all your dreams had come true. So why are you depressed when your life is at it's best. Is it really cause it's not what it seems?. Or are you unable to see that you should be happy. 'Cause your still living in yesterday's dreams</segment1>
		<segment2>Your eldest son reminds you of the way life used to be. When you didn't bear the chains of matrimony. You had no job that you hated, no responsibility. You were youthful and careless and free. And the woman you wed, she seemed better in bed. When there wasn't a ring on her finger. Yes your life seemed all right when you partied all night. Those days are gone, does the flavor still linger?. Don't tell me life would be great if you were reprobate. And had friends who were losers and fiends. You've a family a wife and a meaningful life. But you're still holding on to yesterdays dreams</segment2>
		<segment3>Loneliness reduces you to disharmony. Your life seems so hopeless and melancholy. You're still young but you can't find the strength to move on. Now that the woman who loves you is gone. Did you find she wasn't so close when you needed her most. Is it hard facing up to rejection?. You might understand that she needed a man. But you're still seeking maternal protection. Don't give up you're still young and your life's just begun. At every corner opportunity screams. Sometimes life is abrupt but it's time to grow up. And stop clinging to yesterday's dream    </segment3>
	</english>
</song>
