<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Deity </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Every move yeah every move [x2]</segment1>
		<segment2>The chronology of my theology is not based on philosophy or Greek mythology, But before the garden where we all started, Existed one of three: the trinity. More real than the trees, the mountains, the seas, the flowers, the breeze, the whole galaxy. 'Cause every move I make, and every breath I take is a gift, a deity. Yea, every move I make, and every breath I take is a gift, a deity. Now you say, if your God is real why can't you feel him? Why can't you see him?. I say can you look into the sun and retain your vision?. Can you dissect the wind with accurate precision?. Can you feel your own brain while it makes a decision?. No, I didn't thinks so. These eyes were not made for such beauty, such splendor, Nor could they behold such a wonderful sight. His shafts of light, his strength his might. Are more than my frame of thought can handle. Yet, I see him every time I'm lost in the dark, Or whenever life shoots an arrow straight through my heart. I feel him by my side, his strength he provides. I feel my confidence even after fears have reside. More real than the trees, the mountains, the seas, the valleys, the breeze, the whole galaxy. 'Cause every move I make, and every breath I take is a gift, a deity, Yea, every move, you take, every breath you make is a gift, a deity. Think about it.</segment2>
		<segment3>Every move, yeah, every move [x2]</segment3>
		<segment4>Every move I make and every breath I take.. (More real than the trees, the mountains the seas, the valleys the breeze, the whole galaxy). Every move I make and every breath I take.. (More real than the trees, the mountains the seas, the valleys the breeze, the whole galaxy). It's a diety. (More real than the trees, the mountains the seas, the valleys, the breeze, the whole galaxy)</segment4>
		<segment5>[Cute baby talk at the end]    </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
