<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Desperate </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Seek and you will find, they say. but I've been looking everyday. for a way past this wall that's in front of my face. I'm on hands and knees searching for my faith.</segment1>
		<segment2>I know there's so much at stake. but I don't know if I can take one more pat on the back saying I'll be okay. Can't you see me whole life is in disarray?</segment2>
		<segment3>You've got me desperate.</segment3>
		<segment4>I know You hear me, Would You give me a sign?. Reel me in before I've fallen in line. You've put me on a path I don't understand. I'm standing on a ledge waving my hands.</segment4>
		<segment5>You've got me desperate (do You see me?). Desperate (do You hear me?). Desperate (will You help me?). You've got me desperate.</segment5>
		<segment6>I know You're my only hope. The only One who truly knows how it feels, what it's like when it all starts to fall. You're the One I can trust who hears when I call.</segment6>
		<segment7>You've got me desperate.</segment7>
		<segment8>I know You hear me, Would You give me a sign?. Reel me in before I've fallen in line. You've put me on a path I don't understand. I'm standing on a ledge waving my hands.</segment8>
		<segment9>You've got me desperate (do You see me?). Desperate (do You hear me?). Desperate (will You help me?). You've got me desperate.</segment9>
		<segment10>Some things I'll never figure out. Until I let hope erase my doubt.</segment10>
		<segment11>You've got me desperate.</segment11>
		<segment12>I know You hear me, Would You give me a sign?. Reel me in before I've fallen in line. You've put me on a path I don't understand, I'm standing on a ledge waving my hands.</segment12>
		<segment13>You've got me desperate (do You see me?). Desperate (do You hear me?). Desperate (will You help me?). You've got me desperate.</segment13>
		<segment14>You've got me desperate. (Oh do You see me?). Desperate (do You hear me?). Desperate (will You help me?). You've got me desperate!    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
