<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Despite Your Valor </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Try to breathe, smile as we make our peace, Make our peace with God, Himself. Smile as we make our peace. As we..</segment1>
		<segment2>As we swiped the guardrail we said our prayers,</segment2>
		<segment3>As we lost our focus, we're nearly there. So take my hand now, don't be shy, I know you've done this before.</segment3>
		<segment4>As we swiped the guardrail we said our prayers, As we swiped the guardrail we said our prayers.</segment4>
		<segment5>Despite your valor, I'd say you're losing control, No, nothing is impossible (you look so innocent asleep, you can't do anything to me). Despite your valor, I'd say you're falling apart, Just wait, this is your favorite part (you look so innocent asleep, you can't do anything to me).</segment5>
		<segment6>Burning halos like crosses, don't you dare cross us.</segment6>
		<segment7>. Try to speak, tremble as we set you free, Set you free from life itself, Tremble as we set you free. As we..</segment7>
		<segment8>I can tear the guilt out of every sin, Let me hold the door as you stumble in. So take my hand now, don't be shy. I know you've done this before.</segment8>
		<segment9>As we swiped the guardrail we said our prayers, As we swiped the guardrail we said our prayers.</segment9>
		<segment10>Despite your valor, I'd say you're losing control, No, nothing is impossible (you look so innocent asleep, you can't do anything to me).</segment10>
		<segment11>Despite your valor, I'd say you're falling apart, Just wait, this is your favorite part (you look so innocent asleep, you can't do anything to me).</segment11>
		<segment12>Burning halos like crosses, don't you dare cross us.</segment12>
		<segment13>. I warned you.. I warned you..</segment13>
		<segment14>As we swiped the guardrail we said our prayers, As we swiped the guardrail we said our prayers.</segment14>
		<segment15>Despite your valor, I'd say you're losing control, No, nothing is impossible (you look so innocent asleep, you can't do anything to me). Despite your valor, I'd say you're falling apart,</segment15>
		<segment16>Just wait, this is your favorite part (you look so innocent asleep, you can't do anything to me).</segment16>
		<segment17>Burning halos like crosses, don't you dare cross us.     </segment17>
	</english>
</song>
