<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Do Everything </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>You're picking up toys on the living room floor. for the 15th time today. Matching up socks and sweeping up lost. Cheerios that got away. You put a baby on your hip and color on your lips. and head out the door. And while I may not know you I bet I know you. Wonder sometimes does it matter at all. We'll let me remind you it all matters just as long as you</segment1>
		<segment2>Do everything you do to the glory of the One who made you. Cause He made you to do. Every little thing that you do to bring a smile to His face. And tell the story of grace. With every move that you make. And every little thing you do</segment2>
		<segment3>OOoh ooooh oooooh</segment3>
		<segment4>Maybe you're that guy with the suit and tie. Maybe your shirt says your name. You may be hooking up mergers, cooking up burgers. But at the end of the day</segment4>
		<segment5>Little stuff big stuff in between stuff. God sees it all the same. And while I may not know you I bet I know you. Wonder sometimes does it matter at all. We'll let me remind you it all matters just as long as you do</segment5>
		<segment6>Everything you do to the glory of the One who made you. Cause He made you. To do every little thing that you do to bring a smile to His face. And tell the story of grace with every move that you make. And every little thing that you do</segment6>
		<segment7>Well maybe you're sitting in math class. Maybe anekatips on a mission in the Congo. Maybe you're working at the office. Singing along with the radio. Maybe you're dining at a five star. Or feeding orphans in Myanmar. Anywhere and everywhere you are. Whatever you do it all matters. So do what you do and don't ever forget. to do</segment7>
		<segment8>Everything you do to the glory of the One who made you. Cause He made you to do. Every little thing that you do to bring a smile to His face. And tell the story of grace as you do. Everything you do to the glory of the One who made you. Cause He made you to do. Every little thing that you do to bring a smile to His face. And tell the story of grace with every move that you make. And every little thing that you do</segment8>
		<segment9>Ooh oooooh. Every little thing you do    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
