<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Draw Near </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Chorus: Death wispers words of defeat in my ear. My God I draw near, my God I draw near</segment1>
		<segment2>God of creation here I stand. I've left babylon to find out who I am. I've traveled I've struggled I've failed in vain. My own ability will never see eternal gain. God of creation it's you whom I seek. Lord I feel strapped n tied down and my strenght is weak. Oh Lord when I cry out please hear what I speak. Bring life to my body awaken this sleep</segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus</segment3>
		<segment4>When all vanishes and I stand in this. place to face the truth for what it is. With no human esacpe to hide behind. just my soul n God and I find it mind blowing. Knowin that humanity and a mere mortal man like me. Can have my slate cleaned of mistakes and. the chance to put on immortality. Even though darkness has hardened us in. deception and spoken otherwise. Man I refuse to take in that nonsense, and. i refuse to buy into these lies. These lies of pain, these lies of shame, these lies of complete disfunction</segment4>
		<segment5>This lie of hopelessness that will make a. person feel like they're nothing. This lie that will make me feel like my. struggle is one too much to fix'n. Isn't that what darkness wants for me to. play the role of a victim. But I'm a child of light and no longer. am I bound by slavery. I say oh death were is your sting. And oh hades where's your victory?</segment5>
		<segment6>Hear my cry oh God. Attend to my prayer. From the end of the earth I will cry to you. When my heart's overwhelmed I will cry to you. Leave it to the rock that is higher than I. For you have been a shelter for me. I will abide in your time forever. My God I draw near, my God I draw near</segment6>
		<segment7>Chorus    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
