<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Droppin' on the Sun </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It ain't no joke, no lie, the Bible clearly spoke. To teach the world to fear the furnace underneath. To teach the world about hellfire but there's liars. Who say they know Christians are wrong, even bad people rest in peace. It gets enough attacks. I know men doubt that it's fact. It's not like any map shows exactly where it's at. But just like gravity you cannot see it really exists. And it does no good but they'll deny it just to stay in their sins. So don't delay, act now! Your time is runnin' out!. Find out while you're still alive -- The true way is Jesus Christ. And if you follow the way, you'll have no sorrow but if. the offer's done, you might as well be droppin' on the sun. Two thousand years ago He spoke out and they wrote down. All the best in the New Testament together in a book. And He told how it was dark, surrounded by fire. Where teeth will be gnashin', man, Christ said Hell happens. And so He spelled it out, so to help out those who felt doubt. Then He brought it back up when He talked against the self-proud. And religious hypocrites threw hissy fits. Because that's just what happens when they're faced with their sins. So don't delay, act now! Your time is runnin' out!. By now I'm sure you've surmised -- There's two places to arrive. And if you follow the way you'll have no sorrow, but if. The offer's shunned, you might as well be droppin' on the sun. It ain't no joke that He's gonna take the sheep and goats. And He'll steer them to the left and right, but, listen, folks: The ones that's goats get disposed of. God won't just burn their souls up. They'll be livin' in eternal Godless hopeless darkness. So don't risk that, get facts, you ought to take a look at. Luke 16, Mark 9 and Jude -- There's one little chapt'r. Look today at Matthew chapter 10, verse 28. You need to read in Revelation 20 what does it say?. So don't delay, act now! Your time is runnin' out!. Find now while you're still alive -- Matthew chapter 25. And if you follow the way -- you'll have no sorrow, but if. You drop and punt, you might as well be droppin' on the sun     </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
