<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Easier Than Love </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Sex is currency. She sells cars, She sells magazines. Addictive bittersweet, crack your hands, with the hopeless nicotines</segment1>
		<segment2>Everyone's a lost romantic, Since our love became a kissing show. Everyone's a cassanova, Come and pass me the mistletoe</segment2>
		<segment3>Everyone's been scared to death of dying here alone</segment3>
		<segment4>She is easier to love. It's easier to lie. It's easier to fake and smile and brag</segment4>
		<segment5>It's easier leave. It's easier to lie. It's harder to face ourselves at night. Feeling alone, What have we done?. What is the monster we've become?</segment5>
		<segment6>Were is my soul?</segment6>
		<segment7>Sex is industry, The CEO, of corporate policy. Skin-deep ministry, Suburban youth, hailing so-called liberty</segment7>
		<segment8>Every advertising antic, I've been a ways with a neon glow. War and love become pedantic, We wage love with a mistletoe</segment8>
		<segment9>Everyone's been scared to death of dying here alone</segment9>
		<segment10>She is easier to love. It's easier to lie. It's easier to fake and smile and brag</segment10>
		<segment11>It's easier leave. It's easier to lie. It's harder to face ourselves at night. Feeling alone, What have we done?. What is the monster we've become?</segment11>
		<segment12>Were is my soul?</segment12>
		<segment13>It's easier to love, It's easier to love</segment13>
		<segment14>It's easier to love, It's easier to love</segment14>
		<segment15>She is easier to love, It's easier to, love</segment15>
		<segment16>Everyone's been scared to death of, Everyone's been scared to death of, Everyone's been scared to death of dying here alone, alone</segment16>
		<segment17>[Sing]. It's easier to love, It's easier to love, It's easier to fake and smile and brag</segment17>
		<segment18>It's easier to leave, It's easier to lie, It's harder to face ourselves at night. Feeling alone, What have we done?. What is the monster we've become?</segment18>
		<segment19>Where is my soul? (Where is my?). Where is my soul?    </segment19>
	</english>
</song>
