<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Everything You're Not </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I've been bruised and I've been broken. Can't believe that I put up with all this pain. I've been used and I was choking on the promise. I would never fall again</segment1>
		<segment2>I used to sing to your twisted symphony. The words that had me trapped inside your misery. But now I know the reason why I couldn't breathe</segment2>
		<segment3>'Cause all I want is everything you're not. So go ahead and slam the door 'cause you can't shut me out. No, I don't, don't care what you say. 'Cause all I really, all I really want is everything you're not</segment3>
		<segment4>Never gonna break my heart again. Never gonna see your face again. Never wanna feel this way again</segment4>
		<segment5>Your darkness was my weakness. But it turns out that it only went so deep, deep. A meaningless diversion. That is all that you ever meant to me, me, me, me</segment5>
		<segment6>And I am done with your twisted symphony. The words that had me sound like stolen poetry. I tore the pages and I can finally breathe</segment6>
		<segment7>'Cause all I want is everything you're not. So go ahead and slam the door 'cause you can't shut me out. No, I don't, don't care what you say. 'Cause all I really, all I really want is everything you're not</segment7>
		<segment8>Never gonna break my heart again. Never gonna see your face again</segment8>
		<segment9>I want a gentleman who treats me like a queen. I need respect, I need love, nothing in between. I will not spell it out for you if you can't see. 'Cause you're not worthy, you don't deserve me and now I'm gone</segment9>
		<segment10>Everything you're not, not, not. Everything you're not, not, not. One, two, three</segment10>
		<segment11>'Cause all I want is everything you're not. So go ahead and slam the door 'cause you can't shut me out. No, I don't, don't care what you say. All I really, all I really want is everything you're not</segment11>
		<segment12>Never gonna break my heart again. Never gonna see your face again. Never wanna feel this way again</segment12>
		<segment13>Never gonna break my heart again. Never gonna see your face again. Never wanna feel this way again</segment13>
		<segment14>Never gonna break my heart again. Never gonna see your face again. Never wanna feel this way again    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
