<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Everlasting God [New!] </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Strength will rise as we wait upon the Lord, wait upon the Lord, we will wait upon the Lord. Strength will rise as we wait upon the Lord, wait upon the Lord, we will wait upon the Lord.</segment1>
		<segment2>Our God, You reign forever. Our hope, our strong deliverer.</segment2>
		<segment3>You are the everlasting God, The everlasting God. You do not faint, You won't grow weary. You're the defender of the weak, You comfort those in need, You lift us up on wings like eagles.</segment3>
		<segment4>Strength will rise as we wait upon the Lord, wait upon the Lord, we will wait upon the Lord. Strength will rise as we wait upon the Lord, wait upon the Lord, we will wait upon the Lord.</segment4>
		<segment5>Our God, You reign forever. Our hope, our strong deliverer.</segment5>
		<segment6>You are the everlasting God, The everlasting God. You do not faint, You won't grow weary. You're the defender of the weak, Find More lyrics at www.sweetslyrics.com. You comfort those in need, You lift us up on wings like eagles.</segment6>
		<segment7>You are the everlasting God, The everlasting God, The everlasting God, The everlasting..</segment7>
		<segment8>Strength will rise as we wait upon the Lord, wait upon the Lord, we will wait upon the Lord. Strength will rise as we wait upon the Lord, wait upon the Lord, we will wait upon the Lord.</segment8>
		<segment9>(child speaking)</segment9>
		<segment10>The Lord is the everlasting God, The creator of all the Earth, He never grows weak or weary, No one can measure the depths of His understanding, He gives power to the weak, and strength to the powerless, Even youth will become weak and tired, And young men will fall in exhaustion, But those who trust in the Lord will find new strength, They will soar high on wings like eagles, They will run and not grow weary, They will walk and not faint,     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
