<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Express Yourself </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>&quot;A lot of brothers out there been. flaking and perpetrating but scared to kick reality.</segment1>
		<segment2>We been doing all this dope producing. You ain't had a chance to show 'em what time it is</segment2>
		<segment3>Well what you want me to do?&quot;</segment3>
		<segment4>Express yourself!</segment4>
		<segment5>I'm expressing with my full capabilities. And now I'm living in correctional facilities. Cause some don't agree with how I do this. I get straight and meditate like a Buddhist. I'm dropping flava, my behaviour is hereditary. But my technique is very necessary. Blame it on Ice Cube; because he said it gets funky. when you got a subject and a predicate. Add it on a dope beat; and it'll make you think. Some suckers just tickle me pink - to my stomach. Cause they don't flow like this one. You know what? I won't hesitate to diss one. or two before I'm through, so don't try to sing this. Some drop science; while I'm dropping English. Even if Yella, makes it acapella. I still express, yo, I don't smoke weed or sess. Cause it's known to give a brother brain damage. And brain damage on the mic don't manage - NOTHING. but making a sucka and you equal. Don't be another sequel. </segment5>
		<segment6>Woooaaah!. Express Yourself</segment6>
		<segment7>Now, getting back to the PG. That's program, and it's easy. Dre is back, new jacks are made hollow. Expressing ain't their subject because they like to follow. the words, the style, the trend. Again and again and again - yo, you're on the other end. Watch a brother blend dope rhymes, with no help. There's no fessing or guessing while I'm expressing myself. It's crazy to see people be. what society wants them to be, but not me. Ruthless, is the way to go, they know. Others say rhymes which fail to be original. or they kill where the hip-hop starts. Forget about the ghetto, and rap for the pop charts. Some musicians curse at home. But scared to use profanity when upon the microphone. Yeah, they want reality, but you will hear none. They'd rather exaggerate a little fiction. Some say no to drugs, and take a stand. But after the show, they go looking for the &quot;Dopeman&quot;. Or they ban my group from the radio. Hear Stretch Arm Strong say, &quot;Hell no!&quot;. But you know it ain't all about wealth. As long as you make a note to express yourself!</segment7>
		<segment8>Wooooooah!. Express yourself</segment8>
		<segment9>Cause if you wanna start to move up the chart. then expression is a big part of it (a big part of it)</segment9>
		<segment10>Expression is a big part of it, a big part of it!</segment10>
		<segment11>There's a little bit more to show. I got rhymes in my mind, embedded like an embryo. or a lesson - all of 'em expression. And if you start fessing, I got a Smith and Wessun for ya. I might ignore your record because it has no bottom. I get loose in the summer winter spring and autumn. It's Dre on the mic, getting physical. Doing the job, Stretch Arm Strong is the lynch mob!. Yes I'ma climb, but you know you need this. And the knowledge is growing just like a fetus. or a tumor, but here is the rumor. Dre is in the neighborhood and he's up to no good. When I start expressing myself, Yella, slam it. Cause if I stay funky like this I'm doing damage. Or I'ma be too hyped, and need a straight jacket. I got knowledge, and other suckers lack it. So, when you see Dre, a DJ on the mic. Ask what it's like - it's like we're getting hyped tonight. Cause if I strike, it ain't for your good health. But I won't strike if you just. </segment11>
		<segment12>Express yourself!. Wooooooooooooah</segment12>
		<segment13>Come on and do it. Come on and do it</segment13>
		<segment14>Express yourself!</segment14>
		<segment15>Originally by Charles W. Wright    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
