<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Falls Apart </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It falls apart from the very start. It falls apart. Falls apart everything around me falls apart</segment1>
		<segment2>It falls apart from the very start. It falls apart. Seems like everything I touch falls a part. Everything around me falls apart. When I walk away from You</segment2>
		<segment3>I wish I could but I don't always keep the promises I've kept. I wish I could, but I can't always give whatever I have left. And now its all so clear. Doesn't anyone see what's happening here?</segment3>
		<segment4>It falls apart from the very start. It falls apart. Seems like everything I touch falls apart. Everything around me falls apart. When I walk away from You. When I walk away from You</segment4>
		<segment5>I know I should but I don't always say what You want me to say. I know I could but I don't always act like everything's okay. And now its all so clear. Doesnt anyone see what's happening here?</segment5>
		<segment6>It falls apart from the very start. It falls apart. Seems like everything I touch falls apart. Everything around me falls apart. When I walk away from You. When I walk away from You. When I walk away from</segment6>
		<segment7>Everything I have ever been made of  hates who I am. I'm so glad You waited. Can't get my mind off how You could love me. I'm so behind. You're so far above me. And you'll always be the wind under my wings. Above me. And you'll always be the wind under my wings. Above me</segment7>
		<segment8>I will not let it go to waste. I'm takin all I got and leavin' this place. I will not let it go to waste. I'm takin all I got and leavin' this place. And I will not be takin' up space. I'll take my best shot. I'm pickin up the pace</segment8>
		<segment9>It falls apart from the very start. It falls apart. Seems like everything I touch falls apart. Everything around me falls apart. When I walk away from You</segment9>
		<segment10>It falls apart from the very start. It falls apart. Seems like everything I touch falls apart. Everything around me falls apart. When I walk away from You. When I walk away from You. When I walk away from You    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
