<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Fences </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I'm sitting in a room, Made up of only big white walls and in the hall. There are people looking through. The window in the door. they know exactly what we're here for.</segment1>
		<segment2>Don't look up. Just let them think. There's no place else. You'd rather be.</segment2>
		<segment3>You're always on display. For everyone to watch and learn from, Don't you know by now, You can't turn back. Because this road is all you'll ever have.</segment3>
		<segment4>And it's obvious that you're dying, dying. Just living proof that the camera's lying. And oh oh open wide, 'cause this is your night. So smile, 'cause you'll go out in style. You'll go out in style.</segment4>
		<segment5>If you let me I could, I'd show you how to build your fences, Set restrictions, separate from the world. The constant battle that you hate to fight, Just blame the limelight.</segment5>
		<segment6>Don't look up. Just let them think. There's no place else. You'd rather be.</segment6>
		<segment7>And now you can't turn back. Because this road is all you'll ever have.</segment7>
		<segment8>And it's obvious that you're dying, dying. Just living proof that the camera's lying. And oh oh open wide, 'cause this is your night. So smile.</segment8>
		<segment9>Yeah, yeah you're asking for it. With every breath that you breathe in. Just breathe it in. Yeah, yeah well you're just a mess. You do all this big talking. So now let's see you walk it. I said let's see you walk it.</segment9>
		<segment10>Yeah, yeah well you're just a mess. You do all this big talking. So now let's see you walk it. I said let's see you walk it.</segment10>
		<segment11>And it's obvious that you're dying, dying. Just living proof that the camera's lying. And oh oh open wide, yeah oh oh open wide. Yeah, oh oh open wide, 'Cause you'll go out in style. You'll go out in style.    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
