<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Flop Culture </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>When I was young I used to turn up the bass. And rock out to Billie Jean and Thriller in my basement. When Michael Jackson was a pop sensation. Every second song on the radio. Remember Axle telling us to have patience. And records sold without any affiliation. When William hung and music still had no relation. Someone tell Janet bring back the rhythm nation</segment1>
		<segment2>No gloves, no zipper coats. No more yellow submarines or kokomos. If we could ask Luther Vandross. I bet he'd wonder the same</segment2>
		<segment3>Can you tell me what happened to Michael Jackson. And MTV trading music for acting. Avril Lavigne's on the cover of Maxim. Woah oh oh oh</segment3>
		<segment4>And there's a million other people with a lot on their mind. But for me I'm not the type to let a good thing die. If we could bring The Beatles back to rock it one more time. We could turn this mess around, one beat at a time</segment4>
		<segment5>When I was young I used to turn up my headphones. And flip through the pages of the Ro-oh-lling Stone. Used to turn it up to 10 on my drive home. With Mick Jagger singing &quot;It's only rock-n-roll</segment5>
		<segment6>No gloves, no zipper coats. Just rock stars eating their filet mignon. Where did Van Halen put guitar solos. I bet they'd wonder the same</segment6>
		<segment7>Can you tell me what happened to Michael Jackson. And MTV trading music for acting. Avril Lavigne's on the cover of Maxim. Woah oh oh oh</segment7>
		<segment8>Can you tell me what happened to Michael Jackson. And bands reuniting just to get a reaction. Britney should have never covered satisfaction. No no oh oh oh</segment8>
		<segment9>And there's a million other people with a lot on their mind. But for me I'm not the type to let a good thing die. If we could bring The Beatles back to rock it one more time. We could turn this mess around, one beat at a time</segment9>
		<segment10>You're killing me softly with this whole mirage. And replace the music with hydraulic cars. I'll trade my first favorite old fashion. If we could retrace the steps we've made so far</segment10>
		<segment11>Can you tell me what happened to Michael Jackson. And MTV trading music for acting. Avril Lavigne's on the cover of Maxim. Woah oh oh oh [x2]</segment11>
		<segment12>Can you tell me what happened to Michael Jackson. And bands reuniting just to get a reaction. Britney should have never covered satisfaction. No no oh oh oh.     </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
