<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Flurry </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Everything's snow flurries and everyone's snow flakes. Whatever God has sent you as evidence that snow adds up. It all combines and now you cannot lift it off. Like a branch you're bound to somehow bend or fall. You can read in Romans 1 -- you can read 19. You know our eyes detect Him from all that we have seen. I wonder what you're doin' -- imagine there's no God. This notion seems ingenius but that's not very smart. Can you fake it all away, can you shake it all away. When it's shoveled in your face, as plain as it can be. Can't explain it all away, unless your brain's evolved away. Well it doesn't take much faith. Everyone is straying -- they won't accept God's real. They make up their own ethics depending on just how they feel. But I am shocked at how you cannot hear that call. While the world around you shouts out there's a God. And you can read the Psalms once, you can read 19. I know that God will save you so won't you please come clean. And Romans chapter 2 says no matter where you are. Your conscience bears me witness. Cause God's law's there in your heart. Can't fake it all away, can't shake it all away. When it's shoveled in your face, as plain as it can be. Can't explain it all away, has your brain evolved away?. Well it doesn't take much faith -- it's plain as it can be. Nobody goes to God and shouts &quot;Nobody told me&quot; judgment day. In the Word showed you where to turn. Showed you with the stuff He made. Folks that He showed you testified. Don't forget what your conscience said. Every way showed you where to turn. Showed you yet you ran away. Can't fake it all away, can't shake it all away. When it's shoveled in your face, as plain as it can be. Can't explain it all away, has your brain evolved away?. Well it doesn't take much faith -- it's plain as it can be. It's plain as it can be</segment1>
		<segment2>.     </segment2>
	</english>
</song>
