<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>For The Sake Of The Call </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>For The Sake Of The Call. from the album &quot;For The Sake Of the Call&quot;. (NOTE:  this format observes lyrical &quot;commas&quot;. and fits perfectly on an iPhone screen)</segment1>
		<segment2>. CHORUS 1. We will abandon it all. for the sake of the call. No other reason at all. but the sake of the call. Wholly devoted to live and to die. For the sake of the call</segment2>
		<segment3>Nobody stood and applauded them. So they knew from the start. This road would not lead to fame. All they really knew for sure. was Jesus had called to them. He said, &quot;Come follow me,&quot;. and they came. With reckless abandon. they came</segment3>
		<segment4>Empty nets lying there. at the waters edge. Told a story that few could believe. and none could explain. How some crazy fishermen. agreed to go where Jesus lead. With no thought. for what they would gain. For Jesus had called them by name. and they answered</segment4>
		<segment5>CHORUS 1</segment5>
		<segment6>Drawn like the rivers. are drawn to the sea. No turning back. for the water cannot help but flow. Once we hear the Savior's call. we'll follow wherever he leads. Because of the love He has shown. And because he has called us to go. we will answer</segment6>
		<segment7>CHORUS 2. We will abandon it all. for the sake of the call. No other reason at all. but the sake of the call. Wholly devoted to live and to die</segment7>
		<segment8>BRIDGE. Not for the sake. of a creed or a cause. Not for a dream or a promise. Simply because. it is Jesus who calls. And if we believe we'll obey</segment8>
		<segment9>CHORUS REPRISE. (We will abandon it all). We'll abandon it all. for the sake of the call. (No other reason at all). No other reason at all. but the sake of the call</segment9>
		<segment10>(We will abandon it all). We'll abandon it all. for the sake of the call. (No other reason at all). No other, no other reason at all. but the sake of the call. Wholly devoted to live and to die. For the sake of the call</segment10>
		<segment11>For the sake of the call. (We will abandon it all). Abandon it all. For the sake of the call. (No other reason at all). No other reason, no other reason. (We will abandon it all). We'll live, live and to die. (For the sake of the call). (We will abandon it all)    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
