<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Four Word Letter (Part Two) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I wrote a four word letter, with post-script, in crooked lines, &quot;tho I'd lived I'd never been alive.&quot;. You know who I am. you held my hem as I traveled blind listening to the whispering in my ear, soft but getting stronger, telling me the only purpose of.  my being here is to stay a bit longer. stealing a bicycle chain, as the handlebars crashed to the ground, the back wheel detached from the frame, it kept rolling, yea, but aimlessly drifting around. Oh, doubters, let's go down, let's go down. won't you come on down, oh doubters,  let's go down , down to the river to pray?. &quot;But I'm so small I can barely be seen. How can this great love be inside of me?&quot;. Look at your eyes - they're small in size, but they see enormous things. Wearing black canvas slippers in our frog-on-a-lily-pad pose we sewed. buttons and zippers to chinese pink silk and olive night clothes. if you can someday stop by.  somehow we'll show you the pictures and fix you some tea. (see, my dad's getting a bit older now, and just unimaginably lonelier). oh, pretenders, let's go down, let's go down. won't you come on down, oh pretenders, lets go down, down to the river and pray?. &quot;But I'm so afraid,&quot; or &quot;I'm set in my ways&quot;. but he'll make the rabbits and rocks sing his praise. &quot;oh, but I'm so tired, I won't last long.&quot;. No, hell use the weak to overcome the strong!. Oh, Amanda, let's go down, let's go down,  wont you come on down. Mama, Nana, lets go down, down in the dirt, or the river to pray. you strike the match. Why not be utterly changed to fire?. To sacrifice the shadow and the mist of a brief life you never much liked. So if you'd care to come along we're gonna curb all our never-ending, clever complaining (as who's ever heard of a singer criticized by his song?). We hunger,  but through all that we eat brings us little relief. we don't know quite what else to do, we have all our beliefs, but we don't want our beliefs, God of peace, we want You.     </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
