<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Fresh </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Time for change, let it rain, pour down something new. Not the same, something more, something different something. Out with the old. Just let it go. And let the lord be something. Eyes haven't seen. Ears haven't hears. You cant even imagine. What God has is so fresh</segment1>
		<segment2>I want something like its straight out the box. I mean something supernatural. Something that's never been used. That nobody's got. 'Cause I'm tired of the same old -same old. Need a brand new start. With a brand new heart. Forgetting those things behind me. I'm ready for the new thing Lord. There's gotta be something better. There must be something more.. What God has is so fresh</segment2>
		<segment3>(chorus)</segment3>
		<segment4>I want whats next. Only the best. Time for me to move forward. I want whats in store. An open door. A new life to live more abundant. I want you breathe. Breathe on me. Release your power and glory. I-I-I want something more. Ma-Ma-Make me over Lord. Not gonna live life still no more. What God has is so fresh</segment4>
		<segment5>(chorus)</segment5>
		<segment6>So fresh y'all( God has is so fresh). Yeah, so fresh y'all( God has is so fresh). Yeah so fresh y'all( God has is so fresh). So fresh y'all( so fresh). So fresh y'all( so). F-R-E-S-H fresh, fresh,fresh, that's right. We can start all over again.( fresh). Yeah, time for a brand new start. Yeah we can start all over again. So fresh, so fresh, so fresh</segment6>
		<segment7>Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Out man everything fresh man everything. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Out with the old, in with the new. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Out with the old, in with the new. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Hold out do something new. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh. Everything fresh man everything fresh </segment7>
		<segment8>Copyright © Tye Tribbett    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
