<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>G.O.B. Vs Tony Wonder </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>
Everybody knows.. Everybody knows.. Everybody knows she's a riot when she's striking a pose.. Place your bets.. Place your bets, . on the girl in the short skirt showing off her assets.. They call her home wrecker, but she's not a humble beggar.. There's a closet full of skeletons an undertaker. couldn't spot with a keen sense of dark apparitions.. Her lips are poisonous, but men'll die just to kiss 'em.</segment1>
		<segment2>She works her magic with a devil's ability.. She's a monster, a monster.. She's got a fashion that could humble an enemy.. She's a monster, a monster.</segment2>
		<segment3>She needs help. (No doubt about it.). Sex can sell. (We won't allow it.). She needs help. (No doubt about it.). Who's gonna' be the one to break the news?</segment3>
		<segment4>She's got the looks of a mystery,. With a line and a hook of a century.. Did she make your heart, make your heat skip a b-b-b-beat?. Don't be fooled by her innocent eyes.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf in a sheepish disguise.. C'mon, why don't you take a bit of good advice?. Why don't you take a bit of good advice?. Don't be fooled be her innocent eyes.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf in a sheepish disguise.. C'mon why don't you take a bit of good advice,. before you're spinning in a never ending web of lies?</segment4>
		<segment5>She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf.. She's a wolf. (She's a wolf.). She's a wolf.</segment5>
		<segment6>She works her magic with the devil's ability.. She's a monster, a monster.. She's got a fashion that could humble an enemy.. She's a monster, a monster.. She works her magic with the devil's ability.. She's a monster, a monster.. She's got a fashion that could humble an enemy.. She's a monster, a monster.</segment6>
		<segment7>She needs help. No doubt about it.. Sex can sell. We won't allow it.. She needs help. No doubt about it.. Who's gonna be the one to break the news?. 
    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
