<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Gah Ta Be </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Now you can have all the fun and money man can have. Sport a Porche or carry Gucci bags. You can gear in gold from your chest to your chin. But if you don't know the Savior, you'll never get in. The gates of hell shall prevail on your soul. If makin' money, shakin' honeys is your lifelong goal. There's a plan laid before you that can change the above. It can fit any man like a hand in a glove. There's only one way to heaven and that won't change. Cause my almighty Father's not respectful of names. So be saved</segment1>
		<segment2>(chorus). Saved, you gah ta be saved. Saved, you gah ta be saved. Saved, you gah ta be saved. Saved, you gah ta be saved</segment2>
		<segment3>I once knew a politician upon Capitol Hill. Attended all the right parties cause he voted on bills. He had big friends, he drove a Benz. But a life full of strife cause he was livin' in sin. He said he wasn't satisfied with life as it was. Everything he'd always wanted simply wasn't enough. When he asked me why so happy, I had to confess. I got Christ in my life, I've been more than blessed. You see there's nothin' wrong with finer things in life. But an eternity in heaven ain't displayin' a price. So be saved</segment3>
		<segment4>(repeat chorus)</segment4>
		<segment5>You gotta know it and believe it. You gotta show it and receive it</segment5>
		<segment6>(repeat chorus)</segment6>
		<segment7>From a brother to another, I'm not doggin' the bucks. Cause a bum without the Father is a bum outta luck. No mention of exemption, no requirements waived. To enter through the gates ya gotta gotta be saved. Don't make it complex, straight up text. No matter what race, creed, color, or sex. Accept Him, don't reject Him, heed the call of the Christ. He's at your heart's door knockin', He awaits a reply. This life is temporary, lay your treasures above. Eternal life is offered through His infinite love. Be saved</segment7>
		<segment8>(repeat chorus).     </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
