<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Girl Of The Year </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I met this girl who likes her heavy metal. She gets excited when Slipknot plays on Leno. She's a heck of a girl with no cares in the world. And she likes it that way </segment1>
		<segment2>She wears black socks with pink stripes in 'em. And she swears that her friend goes out with Richard Simmons. She's a one of a kind I can't get off my mind. And I like it that way </segment2>
		<segment3>And if you listen closely you will hear them say </segment3>
		<segment4>CHORUS: Stand clear she's the girl of the year. And there's no use in trying to get her off my mind. She stole my heart and she's tearin' it apart. It's never gunna be the same </segment4>
		<segment5>She's a love potion that play with your emotions. A big swimmer that won't go near the ocean. And if everything is fine she'll get to work on time. And they like her that way </segment5>
		<segment6>She wears black socks with pink stripes in 'em. And she swears that her friend goes out with Richard Simmons. She's a one of a kind I can't get off my mind. And I like it that way </segment6>
		<segment7>And if you listen closely you will hear them say </segment7>
		<segment8>Stand clear she's the girl of the year. And there's no use in trying to get her off my mind. She stole my heart and she's tearin' it apart. It's never gunna be the same </segment8>
		<segment9>And now I'm tapin' myself together. And now I'm tapin' myself together again. And now I'm tapin' myself together. And now I'm tapin' myself together again </segment9>
		<segment10>And I won't let this happen again. Hey Hey ayyyy. Hey Hey ayyyy </segment10>
		<segment11>Together again, and again, and again. Together again, and again, and again. </segment11>
		<segment12>CHORUS </segment12>
		<segment13>She stole my heart and she's tearin' it apart. She stole my heart and she's tearin' it apart. She stole my heart and she's tearin' it apart. It's never gunna be the same.     </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
