<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Give Me Your Eyes </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Looked down from a broken sky. Traced out by the city lights. My world from a mile high. Best seat in the house tonight. Touched down on the cold black tile. Hold on for the sudden stop. Breath in the familiar shock. Of confusion and chaos. Are those people going somewhere?. Why have I never cared?</segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus. Give me your eyes for just one second. Give me your eyes so I can see. Everything that I keep missing. Give me your love for humanity. Give me your arms for the broken hearted. The ones that are far beyond my reach. Give me your heart for the once forgotten. Give me your eyes so I can see. yeah . yeah . yeah . yeah</segment2>
		<segment3>Step out on a busy street. See a girl and our eyes meet. Does her best to smile at me. To hide whats underneath. Theres a man just to her right. Black suit and a bright red tie. To ashamed to tell his wife. Hes out of work. Hes buying time. Are those people going somewhere?. Why have I never cared?</segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus. Give me your eyes for just one second. Give me your eyes so I can see. Everything that I keep missing. Give me your love for humanity. Give me your arms for the broken hearted. The ones that are far beyond my reach. Give me your heart for the once forgotten. Give me your eyes so I can see. yeah . yeah . yeah . yeah</segment4>
		<segment5>Ive been there a million times. A couple of million eyes. Just moving past me by. I swear I never thought that I was wrong. Well I want a second glance. So give me a second chance. To see the way you see the people all alone</segment5>
		<segment6>Chorus. Give me your eyes for just one second. Give me your eyes so I can see. Everything that I keep missing. Give me your love for humanity. Give me your arms for the broken hearted. The ones that are far beyond my reach. Give me your heart for the once forgotten. Give me your eyes so I can see. yeah . yeah . yeah . yeah</segment6>
		<segment7>Give me your eyes for just one second. Give me your eyes so I can see. Everything that I keep missing. Give me your love for humanity. Give me your arms for the broken hearted. The ones that are far beyond my reach. Give me your heart for the once forgotten. Give me your eyes so I can see. yeah . yeah . yeah . yeah</segment7>
		<segment8>Copyright © Brandon Heath    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
