<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Glass House </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Come on in</segment1>
		<segment2>Sometimes it feels as though my life is like a test. With expectations that i've got to be the best. Feels like everybody's always watchin'. One little slip gets people talkin'. So many unkind words are spoken. You see my heart is hurting. But it's still open</segment2>
		<segment3>i have no other choice, but to let you see so</segment3>
		<segment4>Come on in 'cuz i know i can take it. You can throw those stones. Even tho i may be fragile. You're not gonna see me shatter</segment4>
		<segment5>'Cuz i know who i am and i won't fake it. I'm gonna take a stand. 'Cuz it's my faith that keeps me strong. That is all. The light is on. In my glass house. In my glass house</segment5>
		<segment6>So tomoro morning when we step outside our castle. We think before we let the judgement calls unravel. Our Savior said to love one onother. Why must we go on hurting one another. Though it may be easier to run and hide</segment6>
		<segment7>I'm gonna let you in. 'Cuz i can take it. Even though i maybe fragile. You're not gonna see me shatter, no</segment7>
		<segment8>'Cuz i know who i am and i won't fake it. I'm gonna take a stand. 'Cuz it's my faith that keeps me strong. The light is on</segment8>
		<segment9>May i always find a way to give compassion. And remember how it hurt. When someone else's world is crashing. Lord, i pray for love, yeah</segment9>
		<segment10>Come on in 'cuz i know i can take it. You can throw those stones. Even though i may be fragile. You're not gonna see me shatter. No</segment10>
		<segment11>'Cuz i know who i am and i won't fake it. I'm gonna take a stand. 'Cuz it's my faith that keeps me strong. The light is on. In my glass house</segment11>
		<segment12>Come on in 'cuz i know i can take it. You can throw those stones. Even though i may be fragile. You're not gonna see me shatter. No</segment12>
		<segment13>'Cuz i know who i am and i won't fake it. I'm gonna take a stand. 'Cuz it's my faith that keeps me strong. And it's all. In my glass house</segment13>
		<segment14>Welcome    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
