<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Go Buck </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>[INTRO:]. They ain't ready man, I don't think they ready. Let em go  they ain't ready man, I don't think they ready. Let em go  they ain't ready man, I don't think they ready. Let em go  they ain't ready man, I don't think they ready. Let em go  they ain't ready man, I don't think they ready. Let em go  they ain't ready man, I don't think they ready. Let em go  they ain't ready man, I don't think they ready. STOP! Ya'll ain't really ready</segment1>
		<segment2>[HOOK:]. Go buck with the angels. Buck with the angels. [Repeat]. STOP!. GO!</segment2>
		<segment3>[VERSE:]. You're new to the faith and truly that's great. Cause. That's enough to make the angels in Heaven celebrate. And. Now a party over one shorty that truly escape. The Wrath of. Father cause Abba has now given them grace. There is joy. In the Heaven's when a sinner repents. Way over 99 who's. Already convinced. So when you see us and you thinking we. Ain't got no sense. It's definitely due to the fact that we've. Been given a gift. See we're ignited like a volcano blast. And. We're having the same party that the angels are having. In. The Heavens all in the presence of the anchor we have. Now. That's peace no longer beef. No longer angering Dad. So. When you see us get buck with our hands in the sky. And. You see us go dumb without us getting' high. It's cause the. Father sent the Son and now where running to die cause. We never STOP!. Yup! Here we go again!</segment3>
		<segment4>[HOOK:]. Go buck with the angels. Buck with the angels. [Repeat]. STOP!. GO!</segment4>
		<segment5>[VERSE:]. Forget the popular topic of club hopping. Forget the. Topic of bottle the bubb popping. We keep it rocking for God. Cause we love doctrine. We keep it hopping ain't stopping. Like subs knocking. We spaz out when they're truly. Convinced. Of the truth that our Jesus has forgiven they. Sins. How He takes us and shapes and makes sharp as a. Crease. How He's got us under arrest like they called the. Police (Listen). We're real excited and acknowledge you. Came. Into the knowledge of our Savior who is reigning as. King. And now He's changing things inside of you and. Making it plain. That you were stained one of the one's who. Ready to fly. Counted the cost and recognizing that it is. High. Carry your cross knowing that you're ready to die. So. Count 1.. 2.. 3.. 4</segment5>
		<segment6>[HOOK:]. Go buck with the angels. Buck with the angels. [Repeat]. STOP! Let me stop playing with ya'll. GO!</segment6>
		<segment7>[VERSE:]. This the type of feeling that I can't explain. All I. Really know is that I'm glad He came. Lived a perfect life. Then He died for FLAME. And everyone else putting trust in. His name. Since the beginning men have been in the. Bind. Scripture renders us ignorant and considers us. Blind. So when the Unregenerate is giving His eyes. There's. A party before God for the naughtiest guys. So when we. Stand to our feet and we're pounding the earth. Stomping. The ground it's going down in the church. Cause He rose. From the grave and left death in the dirt. And when He. Ascended He sent the Holy Spirit to work. When we see. Genuine repentance then we go berserk. It's real sweet like. Dessert. Him removing the curse. How He digs in the heart. Starts ruling the turf. He'll never STOP!</segment7>
		<segment8>[HOOK:]. Go buck with the angels. Buck with the angels. [Repeat]. STOP! Ya'll ain't really ready. GO!    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
