<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>God's Own Son </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Is God's own Son</segment1>
		<segment2>You see the star from the East came to the West. To show the wise men to the Savior's address. Oh yeah, He's God's only Son. Yeah, yeah and they worshiped the King. Infant ruler of everything, that's why I said</segment2>
		<segment3>Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Is God's own Son</segment3>
		<segment4>I said, the star from the East came to the West. To show the wise men to the Savior's address. Oh yeah, oh yeah, He's God's only Son. Oh yeah, yeah and they worshiped the King. Infant ruler of everything, somebody help me sing now</segment4>
		<segment5>Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Is God's own Son, I said that</segment5>
		<segment6>Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Is God's own Son</segment6>
		<segment7>So go tell it on the mountain. Over the hills and everywhere. Go tell it on the mountain. That Jesus Christ is born</segment7>
		<segment8>Why don't you go tell it on the mountain. Over the hills and everywhere. Go tell it on the mountain. That Jesus Christ is born</segment8>
		<segment9>Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Is God's own Son. Didn't you hear me now</segment9>
		<segment10>Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Is God's own Son. Did you hear me now?</segment10>
		<segment11>Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Mary's Christmas baby. Is God's own Son</segment11>
		<segment12>Hush little baby, don't You cry</segment12>
		<segment13>And she brought forth her firstborn son. And wrapped in swaddling clothes. And laid Him in a manger. Because there was no room for them in the inn</segment13>
		<segment14>And there in the same country, shepherds abiding in the field. Keeping watch over their flock by night. And lo, the Angel of the Lord came upon them. And the glory of the Lord shone round about there. And they were so afraid</segment14>
		<segment15>And the Angel said unto them, &quot;Fear not, but behold. I bring you good tiding of great joy which will be to all people. For unto you is born this day in the city of David. A Savior, which is Christ the Lord&quot;    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
