<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Going, Going... Gone </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>
Is it greed or ignorance or is it both?. as the bulldozer trashes a thousand years growth. clearcutting with a clear conscience-a burning desire to burn. if a tree falls and no ones around-the wildlife still hear it crashing down</segment1>
		<segment2>You were gone before we even knew you. and there's no way to ever get you back</segment2>
		<segment3>Gorilla seven days old ripped from his dead mother's arms. her hand-now an ashtray-souvenir for a tourist's charms</segment3>
		<segment4>Will I join the ranks of the photo gallery?. It may be the only way left to ever see me</segment4>
		<segment5>Thousand acres a day. burning it all away. extinction the price to pay</segment5>
		<segment6>A ton of rhino, a pound of horn. the Javan one cursed-the wheels of greed are born. medicinal myth, smuggled to Hong Kong. ancient superstition-reality gone wrong</segment6>
		<segment7>I joined the ranks of the photo gallery. it's the only way left to ever see me. You were gone before we even knew you. and there's no way to ever get you back</segment7>
		<segment8>The greatest land animal killed for a foot of ivory. will your children live to see one-or witness decimation by tyranny</segment8>
		<segment9>Passenger pigeons blackened the sky. never a chance we would say goodbye. oh how I wish I could see one fly</segment9>
		<segment10>You were gone before we even knew you. and there's no way to ever get you back</segment10>
		<segment11>American symbol of freedom and power. only for target practice by the hour. buffalo sat on the brink of no more</segment11>
		<segment12>Will I join the ranks of the photo gallery? . It may be the only way left to ever see me . 
    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
