<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Goodbye Waves And Drive Ways </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Just walk away. Gather your thoughts for the second length. Of this argument on this epic changing day. Its crazy to think an hour ago all things were great. But we stand both proud both wrong and right. Throwing cheap shots in this stubborn fight. And our lives are so intertwined in one. And were just so stuck in this moment its clear that were coming undone</segment1>
		<segment2>And you see its hard for me to breathe. When I get all worked up with these feelings. And I dont know exactly how it is. That we can be so mad we consider to not exist. And we both know theres so much love clenched within our fists</segment2>
		<segment3>The goodbye waves in the driveway just resonate. And yes Im throwing it right back at her. Whiles were drowning in rivers from our faces. We just wanna know if this is this over. Trembling silence fills the air. As we stand here so impaired, but so aware</segment3>
		<segment4>I sit in this house. Alone with fresh photographs. And I just cant relax. Cigarette smoke, Im starting to choke on this. Then half of my souls on the road in a car with a girl in a dress</segment4>
		<segment5>See its making it hard for me to breathe. And I get all worked up with these feelings. And I dont know exactly how it is. That just to say Im right your wrong we both loose to it</segment5>
		<segment6>The goodbye waves in the driveway just resonate. And yes Im throwing it right back at her. Whiles were drowning in rivers from our faces. We just wanna know if this is this over. Trembling silence fills the air. As we stand here whoa-oh</segment6>
		<segment7>So hey now, maybe we're just being stupid. Hey, maybe we're being dumb. No, hey, maybe it's time that we stopped. and we realize that like the flag in the wind we are one. How at first its made so cute and lovely. And the battle can be torn to shreds. And with time and with patience and love and affection. Can beat this with needle and thread. Because I love you and you love me. And nothing will make this leave. I said I love you and you love me. And nothing will make, make, make, make this leave. So remember me, yeah!. Remember me, yeah!. Remember me</segment7>
		<segment8>Dont walk away    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
