<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Granny's Angel </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>He was standing on the corner again. While she was praying for God to forgive his sin. And out of nowhere, two inches of lead. To him it's still a mystery, how the bullet missed his head?</segment1>
		<segment2>But granny cried, &quot;Lord Jesus, help my baby boy. 'Cause he ain't doin' the things that he's supposed to,&quot; yeah, yeah. Then she cried, &quot;Lord Jesus, it would bring me joy. To see him live to be someone who loves you&quot;</segment2>
		<segment3>'Cause you can't keep livin' on granny's Angel. See it's about time you get one of your own. I'm telling you can't keep livin' on granny's Angel. 'Cause whatcha gonna do when granny's gone</segment3>
		<segment4>Stuck in traffic at a quarter 'til nine. Shirley's cursing, oops that fatal wreck on my side. No compassion 'cause she don't realize. Had she been any earlier, boom it would have been her life</segment4>
		<segment5>But this is what happened. But Granny cried, &quot;Lord Jesus, help my baby girl. To do the things she knows that she's supposed to&quot;. Then she cried, &quot;Lord Jesus, it would mean the world. To see her live to be someone who loves you&quot;</segment5>
		<segment6>'Cause you can't keep livin' on granny's Angel, no, no. See it's about time you get one of your own. I'm telling you can't keep livin 'on granny's Angel. 'Cause whatcha gonna do when granny's gone</segment6>
		<segment7>See we've all been a little guilty of. Living on the prayers of somebody else from time to time. Sometimes it's the prayers of your mama. Sometimes it's the prayers of your daddy. And sometimes it's the prayers of your little old granny</segment7>
		<segment8>But the truth of the matter is God didn't have any stepchildren. He has no grandchildren, only sons and daughters. So I'm here to let you know. You can't keep livin' on somebody elses Angel. 'Cause it's time you get one of your own</segment8>
		<segment9>'Cause you can't keep livin' on granny's Angel. It's about time you get one of your own. I'm telling you, you can't keep livin' on granny's Angel. I said whatcha gonna do when granny's gone. I said whatcha gonna do when, think about it. Whatcha gonna do when grannys gone</segment9>
		<segment10>'Cause you can't keep livin' on. No you can't keep livin' on. Whatcha gonna do when. Whatcha gonna do. Whatcha gonna do when. I'm asking you. Whatcha gonna do when. Whatcha gonna do when gone    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
