<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Guide the Way </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Standing with lions beneath the floor tonight. And there's a lion-here we go. Right away I try to pray, I kneel there, waiting, Lord. &quot;Daniel don't go and pray,&quot; they said to me. They made a mockery of you, Lord</segment1>
		<segment2>Save life! Claws sharp! C'mon God! Move quick!</segment2>
		<segment3>This cat thinks I'm such a little beefcake. Get here quick I think I'm on the meat tray. Point and click to make your bid on eBay. Teach that king that's not the way that we pray</segment3>
		<segment4>Don't allow! Blood bath! In cave! Stop them!</segment4>
		<segment5>Standing with lions beneath the floor tonight. And there's a lion-help me, Lord. Guide the way, when lions prey, they feed there, tame Him, Lord!</segment5>
		<segment6>Meow (x16)</segment6>
		<segment7>Bad cat! Don't sic! Paws off! Open!</segment7>
		<segment8>Kit cat's nice but, no, don't want to hold one. Not gonna strike but I'm a not-so-bold one. Might not bit, I know, you never know but. God I like this story though it's no fun</segment8>
		<segment9>Stop there! Mean lion! Get back! Hard stop!</segment9>
		<segment10>Standing with lions I see them show their whites. And there's a lion-every hole. Find a way, my life's at stake I see their great big jaws. &quot;Daniel, don't go and pray,&quot; they said to me. Beneath them I'll be on the floor. By the way, I find it strange I'll be here praying more</segment10>
		<segment11>Ooh ah, kittens better listen. Ooh ah, kittens can't resist Him. Ooh ah, kittens kept their distance. Ooh ah, kittens never bit me. Ooh ah, kittens lost their mittens. Ooh, I guess I'm not a victim. Ooh, I'm gettin' out of prison--Hoo hah!</segment11>
		<segment12>Daniel 6:19 stayed here overnight. And there's a light on-early show. By the way, it's light of day, I see that breaking dawn. &quot;Daniel,&quot; the Persian king he calls to me. And he's remarking, &quot;Oh poor soul&quot;. By an angel I was saved, I know You love me Lord</segment12>
		<segment13>Standing with lions I've seen You show Your might. That I relied on to get me home. Right away I cried, You saved, I beat them, Thank You, Lord    </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
