<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Hand Grendades </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I'm handing over my transgressions, My deep and dark confessions.</segment1>
		<segment2>I'm telling you the truth, for the first time it's the truth. And I'm well aware of consequences, Don't give me second chances, Do what you gotta do, do what you gotta do.</segment2>
		<segment3>You shouldn't test me. You caught me paying attention, I finally figured it out. And when your head's full, And it's not easy to sleep, You'll feel that heavy chill, strike you like a stone in your bed.</segment3>
		<segment4>I'm taking all the sins I carry, To a hidden sanctuary, Down a spiraling cascade, through a spiraling cascade. And when you walk through all the fences, To every house you lived in,</segment4>
		<segment5>You fall asleep alone, you fall asleep alone.</segment5>
		<segment6>You shouldn't test me. You caught me paying attention, I finally figured it out. And when your head's full,</segment6>
		<segment7>And it's not easy to sleep, You'll feel that heavy chill, strike you like a stone in your bed.</segment7>
		<segment8>It's only natural to get ahead of ourselves. We fight with hand grenades, because we've got nothing left.</segment8>
		<segment9>I am a champion, survival lives in blood. You speak of treachery, like you've got nothing to love.</segment9>
		<segment10>You caught me paying attention, Well I finally figured it out.</segment10>
		<segment11>You need to be more impressive..</segment11>
		<segment12>I can tell by the way that you're shaking, You've seen this before, and you can't wait til it's over. While you're scared to death, I can offer you wisdom,</segment12>
		<segment13>Baby, we're growing up, and we're still building character. I can tell by the way that you're shaking, You've seen this before, and you can't wait til it's over.</segment13>
		<segment14>While you're scared to death, I can offer you wisdom, Baby, we're growing up, and we're still building character.     </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
