<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Hanger </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Not one motion of her gesture could I forget. The prettiest bag lady I ever met. Pushing her cart in the rain. Then gathering plastic and glass. She watched the day pass. Not hour by hour. But pain by pain. If I was a basket filled with holes. Then she was the sand I tried to hold. And ran out behind me. As I swung with some invisible hands</segment1>
		<segment2>I stopped believing, you start to move. She was like wine turned to water then turned back to wine. I stopped my leaving and the better man bloomed. And you can pour us out and we won't mind</segment2>
		<segment3>I was dead, then alive. She was like wine turned to water and turned back to wine. You can pour us out, we won't mind. A scratch around the mouth of the glass. My life is no longer mine</segment3>
		<segment4>If you're still looking for a blanket. Sweetie, I'm sorry, I'm no sort of fabric. But if you need a tailor. Then take your torn shirt, and stumble up my stairs. And mumble your pitiful prayers. And in your tangled night's sleep, our midnight needles go to work. Until all comfort and fear flows in one river. Down on the shelf by the mirror where you see yourself whole. And it makes you shiver</segment4>
		<segment5>I stopped believing, you start to move. She was like wine turned to water then turned back to wine. I stopped my leaving and the better man bloomed. And you can pour us out and we won't mind</segment5>
		<segment6>I was dead, then alive. She was like wine turned to water and turned back to wine. You can pour us out, we won't mind. A scratch around the mouth of the glass. My life is no longer mine</segment6>
		<segment7>Our lives our not our own even the wind plays still. All I felt was fire and bone. And movement, movement. If they ask you for a sign of the Father. Tell them it's movement, movement (of hope)    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
