<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Hawaiian Roller Coaster Ride </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Aloha e aloha e. 'Ano 'ai ke aloha e. Aloha ae aloha e. A nu ay ki aloha e</segment1>
		<segment2>There. Then on my surfboard out at sea. Lingering in the ocean blue. And If I had one wish come true. I. Beyond the horizon </segment2>
		<segment3>A wiki wiki mai lohi lohi. Lawe mai i ko papa he'e nalu. Flyin by on the Hawaiian roller coaster ride</segment3>
		<segment4>A wiki wiki mai lohi lohi. La we mai iko papa he na lu. Pi'i na nalu la lahalaha. O ka moana hanupanupa. Lalala i kala hanahana. Me ke kai hoene i ka pu'e one. Helehele mai kakou e. Hawaiian roller coaster ride</segment4>
		<segment5>There. Than on the seashore dry, wet free. On golden sand is where I lay. And if I only had my way. I'd play til the sun sets. Beyond the horizon</segment5>
		<segment6>Lalala i kala hanahana. Me ke kai hoene i ka pu'e one. It</segment6>
		<segment7>Hang loose, hang ten, howzit, shake a shaka. No worry, no fear, ain't no biggie braddah. Cuttin' in, cuttin' up, cuttin' back, cuttin' out. Front side, backside, goofy footed, wipe out</segment7>
		<segment8>Looking for the wipeout. Let's get jumpin', surf's up and pumpin'. Coastin' with the motion of the ocean. Whirlpools swirling, cascading, twirling. Hawaiian roller coaster ride</segment8>
		<segment9>There. Then on my surfboard out at sea. Lingering in the ocean blue. And if I had one wish come true. I. Beyond the horizon</segment9>
		<segment10>A wiki wiki mai lohi lohi. Lawe mai i ko papa he'e nalu. Flyin by on the Hawaiian roller coaster ride</segment10>
		<segment11>A wiki wiki mai lohi lohi. La we mai iko papa he na lu. Pi'i na nalu la lahalaha. O ka moana hanupanupa. Lalala i kala hanahana. Me ke kai hoene i ka pu'e one. Helehele mai kakou e. Hawaiian roller coaster ride     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
