<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>He Did That </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>he went and rose of the third yeah he did that. gave me all his promise and his word yeah he did that. what you never ever heard? yeah he did that did that. well then its time that ya learned that he did that did that</segment1>
		<segment2>eh yo the kids back this cat can only claim he did that. I only aim to give back the holy name with this fact. Im a state with this rap Jesus came to fix that. I was lame sin stacked but right now since that. i found the way crossed it tossed it and then passed. the sin of up on my life just at the cross where he nixed that. like rocking two different types of socks is a mismatch. is you trying to ice out ya watch with some thick stacks. now yous up a creek with no paddle on a big raft. think you got a handle on ya life and you can kick back. but dude heres a sample of advice I wouldnt risk that. youre lies are the whopper but you far from a big mac. I aint a thug but I hangs with the riff raff. to attract em like a bug to the light with a lit match. now ya life may break apart in pieces like a kit kat. but thats why Jesus came to free us from the sin trap </segment2>
		<segment3>. now he was beaten he was bruised but never hit back. can u see the lashes that been used now on his his back. now everything that happened he went through cause of this fact. that hes so deep now in love for you he went and did that. now everything I ever thought was cool I threw in his trash. and let him dump it out just to prove I never been back. now the pain and all the hurt I ever knew its just been since smashed. since I went and gave it all up to you Ive never missed that. now forever Im a live up with you its evidenced that. whatever Im a lift up to you I always sense that. that together I can live through any storm life gives back. when I remember that the veil has been torn when you finished that. and you got the perfect timing on and on like a click track. whether or not my problems kind of big or small like a tic tac. now I could try and count all ya done but never list that. Id rather get my hands up to the one and steady lift that and say.     </segment3>
	</english>
</song>
