<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Hey Now </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Hey now, I feel a new one comin on so that you can sing along with it. Right now and Im gonna dedicate this song to everyone of Gods children. Hey now, one love, one God out of many his people. Right now its been a long time comin but Im serving up the sequel</segment1>
		<segment2>Back from the day, Im the sleeper done slumbering. Pass me the mic and I might stop mumbling. Crumble like a cracker, Ill fall like a leaf. But the hole in my souls been filled underneath. So whether youre a loser or a winner by the numbers. Everyone knows a tie goes to the runner. So lace up your shox, get yourself in this race. Cause this little thing here gonna set a new pace</segment2>
		<segment3>Sometimes we do it like this, sometimes we do it like that. Sometimes we say it with words so you can see where we at. And on a different level I persist to reach a girl or any fella. I believe we receive a little then we all do better. Hey now, help is coming anyday now. Hope it can reach me when I am way down. One love, one God and Im ok now. Ten years, TOBYMAC and GRITS stay down</segment3>
		<segment4>What you think of this here, gotta get with this here. Diverse City, are you gonna get it this year?. What you think of this here, gotta get with this here. Diverse City and well run it till He gets here</segment4>
		<segment5>Get your back up off the wall. Live a little, come on. Get your back up off the wall. Everybody come on</segment5>
		<segment6>One love, one God, I feel a new one comin on so that you can sing along with it. One love, one God, and Im gonna dedicate this song to everyone of Gods children. One love, one God, one love, one God out of many his people. One love, one God, its been a long time comin but Im serving up the sequel. One love, one God    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
