<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Hold On (He's Strong) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>[HOOK]. Say  Say  Say. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a warrior. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, just look at your neighbor say. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast</segment1>
		<segment2>[VERSE]. This walk it ain't easy. Matter of fact it gets hard. You've enlisted for war. The battleground is your heart. It's going to be some stress and strain. And discomfort and involved. But my advice to you homie is to make your resolve. To fight for your joy. In God's keeping grace. So at the end you can say like Paul that I've kept the Faith. You see the way is hard. Cause narrow is the gate. And those who find it are few. I'm praying you complete the race. But yet his yoke is easy. And His burdens are light. But that's the fight for us to rest and find in Him delight. You see our self reliance and self exaltation. Is still pacing in our souls as we battle with Satan. You see it's unbelief that spring from our sinful pride. That straight denies that what God supplies can really satisfy. But God is working for us even though we hate the struggle. In decisions make the one's that strengthen your Faith muscle</segment2>
		<segment3>[HOOK]. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a warrior. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, look at your neighbor say. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast</segment3>
		<segment4>[VERSE]. I been crucified with Christ so it's no longer I who live. But it's Christ who's living inside your boy. Now my whole life's defined by dying. To the praise of my God as I fight for joy. It's getting bloody as I pluck out eyes. Matthew 5:29 flat our war (on the flesh). To set my mind on the flesh is death. Gotta keep my mind set on the Spirit of course. Plus Satan came to kill and destroy (and steal). Steal sheep from being the children of God (Amen). Let my relationship run real deep (oh Lord). How deep? All the way to the core. We're in this process. Of making progress. Sanctification is taking place in our mindset. Cause we were united with Christ when He resurrected. Now we can reflect with the power of God</segment4>
		<segment5>[HOOK]. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a warrior. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, look at your neighbor say. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast</segment5>
		<segment6>[VERSE]. You see this new life. It comes with new rules. You're a new born baby. You're fresh out of the womb. The Holy Spirit of God has given you new birth. Now your Father's the Trinity you're apart of the church. And all the church is  is the body of Christ. Jesus is the head of this organism giving it life. You see it's one body, but yet it's many members. Nothing but plenty sinners. Given His grace then He cleanse us. Man we need each other. The hand can't say to the feet. That I don't need you if I despise my eyes then I can't see. So if one member suffers we suffer across the globe. So if my nose is broken then we'll dysfunction-ally grow. So we must kill all individual talk. We're all necessary visible invisible parts. So being in isolation only leads to more of sin. Don't hurt the covenant like the cutting of foreskin</segment6>
		<segment7>[HOOK]. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a warrior. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, look at your neighbor say. Hold on, He's strong. Hold on, cause our God is a beast</segment7>
		<segment8>Don't you ever give up! (Repeat).     </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
