<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Hollywood </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>All american boy with big dreams of glamour life. Bright lights and boogie nights. The hype is &quot;Everything could be yours if the price is right&quot;. Grab your nothing and hold it tight. The first chance you get your heading out to the west. This decision is one you won't regret. Move to the place where everybody knows ya. Like Hollywood, Los Angeles, California. So you wanna be a Superstar. Welcome to Hollywood. Quick money, fly women, fast cars. Welcome to Hollywood. So you wanna be a Superstar. Welcome to Hollywood. High times, big dreams, living large. Welcome to Hollywood</segment1>
		<segment2>One way ticket, then you'll live this. Life of a Superstar caught up in this business. God as my witness, you will never change. Only been here a day, already in the game. You changed your name, you don't even look the same. Now you're on top of the world, money, power and fame. Picture perfect, just like you planned. No longer him, 'cause you the man</segment2>
		<segment3>So you wanna be a Superstar. Welcome to Hollywood. Quick money, fly women, fast cars. Welcome to Hollywood. So you wanna be a Superstar. Welcome to Hollywood. High times, big dreams, living large. Welcome to Hollywood</segment3>
		<segment4>You'll never get the best of me</segment4>
		<segment5>The time ticks away, you've had your play. Sold your soul for the roll, now you gots to pay. Forfeit integrity, overnight celebrity. Settle for selfish gain rather than dignity. Another sucka, why did you trust a playa like me fool. Eternal hustler. I'm taking everything and now you know I hate to tell you but I told you so</segment5>
		<segment6>So you wanna be a Superstar. Welcome to Hollywood. Quick money, fly women, fast cars. Welcome to Hollywood. So you wanna be a Superstar. Welcome to Hollywood. High times, big dreams, living large. Welcome to Hollywood    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
