<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Homecoming Glory </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Tell us of angels on high, tell us of clouds I can feel under my feet. Tell us of vast golden fields and heavenly wonders that go beyond what I can see. Tell us of triumphant music, the brass sounding trumpets, tell of the welcoming choir. Tell us of majestic men, mighty in valor riding on chariots of fire</segment1>
		<segment2>Oh tell us were going home, tell us that heavenly story and oh. Tell of that homecoming glory its my favorite story by far. Cause it tells us who we are and it says where were going. Oh tell us were going home, tell us that heavenly story and oh. Tell of that homecoming glory its my favorite story by far</segment2>
		<segment3>Tell of the last liberation, the end of the suffer beginning of good things to come. Tell of the sweet celebration, the debut, excitement of knowing that your work is done. Tell of that moment in time when time is no longer and life will be forever lived. Tell of the fresh falling rain soaking the hearts of which to you we freely give</segment3>
		<segment4>Oh tell us were going home, tell us that heavenly story and oh. Tell of that homecoming glory its my favorite story by far</segment4>
		<segment5>Because it tells us who we are I wanna be in that number. Oh tell us were going home, tell us that heavenly story and oh. Tell of that homecoming glory its my favorite story by far</segment5>
		<segment6>How wonderful you are to me. How wonderful that day will be. How wonderful you are to me. How wonderful that day will be</segment6>
		<segment7>Tell of the last declaration, the ringing of freedom, the promise of sorrow no more. Tell of the first close encounter with you our Father the lone one whom we all adore</segment7>
		<segment8>Oh tell us were going home, tell us that heavenly story and oh. Tell of that homecoming glory its my favorite story by far. Because it tells us who we are I and it says where were going and. Oh tell us were going home, tell us that heavenly story and oh. Tell of that homecoming glory its my favorite story by far</segment8>
		<segment9>Oh tell us that story. Oh tell us that story. Oh tell us that story. Oh tell us</segment9>
		<segment10>Its my favorite story. My favorite story. My favorite story. My favorite story by far    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
