<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>How You Rewind Me </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I never made it as a lineman. I couldn't cut it as a Pittsburgh Steeler. I'm tired of losin' all the time, man. But sin keeps sendin' my defenses reelin'. And this is how You rewind me. This is how You rewind me up when I'm really bad. This is how You rewind me up when I'm really bad. I'm not like You -- I'm so sorry. The world's waitin' on a distant glory. Each time I'm mistaken. Lord thanks to You I'm not forsaken. And I've been wrong; I've been down. But through the battles and every struggle. These five words in my head scream &quot;But He isn't done yet&quot;. Yet, yet, yet, oh no, yet, yet, yet, oh no. It's not like I didn't know better. I still don't want to do the things I still do. It must have been Romans 7. Cause livin' in me is the sin that killed You. And this is how You rewind me up when I'm really bad. This is how You rewind me up when I'm really bad. Seems all I do is say I'm sorry. You're Word's waiting with forgiveness for me. It's time I put faith in 3:22 in Lamentations. And I've been wrong, You bent down. And turned the bottomless pits to potholes. These five words in my head scream &quot;But He isn't done yet&quot;. Yet, yet, yet, oh no, yet, yet, yet, oh no. Yet, yet, yet, oh no, yet, yet, yet, oh no. I never made it as a nice man. I hope I'm counted as the poor in spirit. And this is how You designed me. This is how You refine me. This is how You rewind me up when I'm really bad. This is how You rewind me up when I'm really bad. You blot out my sins - Isaiah 43. 1:18 -- Your forgiveness floors me. This time I'm just beggin'. Lord can You cure my heart's frustration?. And I've been wrong, I've been down. But soon my problems are getting smaller. These five words in my head scream &quot;But He isn't done yet&quot;. Yet, yet, in Philippians 1:6, Yet, yet, oh He isn't done yet. (Oh in my head) Yet, yet, oh He isn't done yet, (Oh in my head) Yet, yet, oh He isn't done yet</segment1>
		<segment2>    </segment2>
	</english>
</song>
