<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Identity Crisis </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>[Intro]. This is for the girls that used to diss me. Now they all just..wanna diss me</segment1>
		<segment2>[Chorus]. It's an identity crisis (repeat 3X). I do not know what to do. Grow dreads or sport a bald head. I don't know. It's an identity crisis (repeat 3X). I do not know what to do. Wear Nikes or be Dick Van Dike. I don't know</segment2>
		<segment3>[Verse]. I was walking down the street. To a funky beat. Feeling real nice. Feeling real neat. Had a little money so I had something to eat. Sitting alone so I kicked up my feet. And what do you know another freakazoid. Had a little confidence and didn't feel void. Stood up slow to dust myself off. Not too hard, not too soft. She was shopping at Miller's Outpost dude. She looked 14, I was that plus two. I was kinda dusty cause I just finished skatin'. Went over to her and she started hesitatin'. I tried to ignore it, then I kicked my game. And ever since then I never been the same. She looked me up and down to check my stilo. Before I said a word, she said she had to go. I said &quot;Can I come?&quot; Started kicking my drag. She paused for a minute, listened to what I had. I said, &quot;Can we talk over the phone or something. Instead of in the mall, be all alone or something&quot;. She said &quot;No thanks, it just don't feel right. Cause you walk black and act white&quot; (say word?). And as she walked away. I could hear the ricochet. And it's effect on my whole dang life</segment3>
		<segment4>[Chorus]</segment4>
		<segment5>So I grew out my hair, switched up my clothes. Down with LA Symph and I rocked some shows. Dancing and acting a fool and stuff. But in the back of their mind is it all a bluff. Am I doin' all of this just to cover it up. All of my insecurities is hovering up-ac.     </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
