<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Identify </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Trained to fail before I could walk. Now I'm undoing 20 years of lies I've been taught. Not always easy let the past be forgot, when memories keep you caught. Let's travel back, now hold up stop, why. Cuz if I dwell on the past I get focussed to who I'm not. I strive to stay away but that ain't easy. When who I was wants to control my destiny testing me. Man, it's got me tripping. its in these moments of despair I feel my foundation's slipping. Its starts ripping leaving me broken. Now I'm completely confused and I'm vulnerable and open. I try to run, but who am I running from?. See, what within myself this battle has come. So basically, You say it's up to me. Cuz I'm my greatest ally or my worst enemy</segment1>
		<segment2>BRIDGE. I stepped out of my body to let God slide in. Although I'm still dressed in flesh I spiritually died in. Alive in Christ, a new creation started breathing. Life exists and through this came completion (x2)</segment2>
		<segment3>CHORUS. Get your mind body and soul under control. Who am I? Identify. Who are You? All is new</segment3>
		<segment4>I feel like my soul keeps challenging my spirit. And my spirit keeps challenging my soul. Which ever one I choose to excersize the most. Will be the one to obtain control. Man, I feel like I got multi-personalities. I dabble in multi-mentalities. My own thoughts hold me captive in a world of confusion. As the monipulation increases gradually. Now If a lies placed before me and I buy into it. Then am i responsible for the deception?. If I have no acceptance. Who's to blame for these feelings of rejection?. Man I bring these feelings of confusion. I challenge all that my heart believes. I'm the one that drags my past up from the grave. telling myself I wont succeed</segment4>
		<segment5>BRIDGE and CHORUS</segment5>
		<segment6>I'm not that person anymore!!!. Thats what blood was shed for, NO LONGER A FAILURE!!!. Living life more abundantly, Therefore you'll never see me living less than victory!!!!. (repeat)    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
