<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>I Don't Want It </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>S-E-X is a test when I'm pressed. So back up off with less of that zest. Impress this brother with a life of virtue. the innocence that's spent is gonna hurt you. Safe is the way they say to play. Then again safe ain't safe at all today. So just wait for the mate that's straight from God. Don't have sex till ya tie the knot</segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus: I don't want it. I don't want it, want it. I don't want it. Want your sex for now. I don't want it. I don't want it, want it. I don't want it. 'Till we take the vows</segment2>
		<segment3>Verse 1: Girl, it's gonna take a little time for us to see (the Truth). That love is simply more fulfilling than the need (for S-E-X). Respect is what we need to find the cure for this disease (of lust). And trust in God above to shape our lives in harmony. That's why I'm saying</segment3>
		<segment4>REPEAT CHORUS</segment4>
		<segment5>PRELUDE TO VERSE 2: (Ah, yah, really, I don't think I copy that. Uh, did you say you DON'T want sex for now?. Uh, I'm confused, could you clarify? Over.)</segment5>
		<segment6>VERSE 2: Girl, they say that it takes two to make a thing go right (for love). But girl, we gotta remember there's another in our lives (in God we Trust). We must add up the cost before indulging in the heat (for now). And trust that God will give us something better if we wait (Is that affirmative?). That's why we keep saying</segment6>
		<segment7>REPEAT CHORUS</segment7>
		<segment8>BRIDGE: 1-900-LOVE. S-E-X is on the TV. Too much skin is in your vision. You better make the right decision. God has set his standards higher. Purity is his desire. I'm gonna choose to wait. I don't want it. I don't want it, want it. I don't want your sex for now</segment8>
		<segment9>RAP: Yo! S-E-X is a test when I'm pressed. So back up off with less of that zest. Impress this brother with a life of virtue. The innocence that's spent is gonna hurt you. Safe is the way they say to play. Then again safe ain't safe at all today. So just wait for the mate that's straight from God. Don't give it up till ya tie the knot</segment9>
		<segment10>(REPEAT CHORUS)</segment10>
		<segment11>B CHORUS: I don't want your sex for now. Wait until we take the vows. Even if they dog me out. I don't want your sex. (REPEAT)</segment11>
		<segment12>Really, Really I don't think I copy. Your sex for now!</segment12>
		<segment13>S-E-X is test when I'm pressed. So back up off with less of that zest. Impress this brother with a life of virtue. The innocence that's spent is gonna hurt you. Safe is the way they say to play. Then again safe ain't safe at all today. So just wait for the mate that's straight from God. Don't have sex 'til you tie the knot. (chorus). I don't want it, I don't want it, want it. I don't want it, want your sex for now. I don't want it, I don't want it, want it. I don't want it, 'til we take the vows. Girl, it's gonna take a little time. For us to see (the truth). That love is simply more. Than fulfilling the need (for S-E-X). Respect is what we need to find the cure. For this disease (of lust). And trust in God above. To shape our lives in harmony. That's why I'm saying.. (chorus). Girl, they say that it takes two. To make a thing go right (for love). But girl, we gotta remember. There's another in our lives (in God we trust). We must add up the cost. Before indulging in the heat (for now). And trust that God will give us. Something better if we wait. That's why we got to say.. (chorus). 1-900-LOVE, S-E-X is on the TV. Too much skin is in your vision. You gotta make the right decision. God has set His standard higher. Purity is His desire, I'm gonna choose to wait. I don't want it, I don't want it. I don't want your sex for now. Yo, s-e-x is a test when I'm pressed. So back off with less of that zest. Impress this brother with a life of virtue. The innocence that's spent is gonna hurt you. Safe is the way they say to play. But then    </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
