<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>I'll Be With You </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I've seen it and felt it. Hopelessness with no lifeline. The wicked are feeding on. Innocence and our decline</segment1>
		<segment2>You and I we are the same. Torn apart by different things. All our faith is barely alive. But we're going to make it through the night. I want you to know</segment2>
		<segment3>When the world is on your back. And you think that you will never last. When you're lonely and you are confused. I'll be right beside you. When the walls are closing in. And you think you'd rather sink than swim. When you think there's nothing left for you to lose. I'll be right beside you. I'll be with you</segment3>
		<segment4>We are precious. More than priceless is our worth. Loved by the Father. Heaven's children here on earth. You and I we are the same. Lifted up above the pain. By its wounds we have been healed. And in our love it is revealed. I want you to know (I need you to know)</segment4>
		<segment5>When the world is on your back. And you think that you will never last. When you're lonely and you are confused. I'll be right beside you. When the walls are closing in. And you think you'd rather sink than swim. When there's nothing left for you to lose. I'll be right beside you</segment5>
		<segment6>Hold on, don't you let go of me. I'll be here through it all. Hold on, when you're ready to fall. I will carry you. I will never leave you. I will lift you if you fall</segment6>
		<segment7>When the world is on your back. And you think that you will never last. When you're lonely and you are confused. I'll be right beside you. When the walls are closing in. And you think you'd rather sink than swim. When there's nothing left for you to lose. I'll be right beside you. I'll be with you. I'll be right beside you    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
