<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>I'm Back </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>This song goes out to everybody who was down and got pounded out too early. All of your friends looked at you while you were down and they thought it was over for you. But how many know you're back better than you were before?. Stronger, wiser, everything is brighter, just because you didn't give up, you held on to the Lord in. and now you're back to give God all you got, can we do it singers, come on</segment1>
		<segment2>Better than I was before, strong. Stronger now that I am . Wiser, wiser now you make me see. Lift my hands in victory, lift my hands in victory, come on, shout it in the atmosphere. I am back, I am back come on, to give you all I have or am want</segment2>
		<segment3>Better than I was, better than I was before, stronger now. Stronger now that I am . anybody smarter in the building, come on. wiser now you make me see. lift my hands in victory, lift my hands in victory. I am back, Lord I'm gonna give you all I got, to give you all I got. This is somebody's testimony, you gave me. you gave me another change. I deliver, I deliver, I'm in .. Now  to give you all I got, you gave me, you gave me another chance. Oh you didn't stop there, didn't know. and in hands, and in hands</segment3>
		<segment4>Now I can say I'm back to give you all I have or am got. Now all the victory people in the house, every winner in the building. jump on your feet and put your hands together right here, ah, come on. I'm back, I'm back from confusion in my mind, say it, I'm back. I'm back from depression yeah I got my head lifted up, I'm back. The devil thought he had me but guess what, Jesus mada a way of escape I got away, I'm back. You thought it was over for me but I'm back, come on, Devil you can't have my mind, cuz Jesus gave me a sound mind devil you can't have my mind. You can stop wasting, you can stop wasting your time. Devil you won't steal my piece, since Jesus gave His peace to me devil you won't steal my peace. and Cause victory belongs to me, since JesusChrist has set or made me free* victory belongs to me, I'm back. Ooh, they calling me out too early, but now I'm back. I'm back bigger, I'm back better, I'm back stronger, I'm back. No weapon formed fond against me will that gets me Take out it's and use is or will it's gonna prosper, come on, I'm back. Can I get a witness in the house? Talk yo the unity . Devil you can't have my mind, you can stop wasting. You can stop wasting your time. Devil you won't steal my victory, victory belongs. Victory belongs to me, I'm back. Yes I'm back with a smile on my face, I'm back. I'm back with a bigger heart, a bigger mind, a bigger soul, I'm back. Everything that the enemy thought he had written in my name, I'm back. I cancel it right now in the name of Jesus, devil you can't have. Devil you can't have my mind, you can stop wasting. You can stop wasting your time, you won't steal my peace. You won't steal my peace, cause victory belongs, victory belongs to me, say victory belongs. victory belongs to me, say victory belongs yeah. victory belongs to me, yeah, yeah, it belongs. victory belongs to me, say victory is mine. victory belongs to me, yeah, yeah. victory belongs to me, here we go</segment4>
		<segment5>I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back. I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back. I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back. I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back. I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back. I am back, come on sing. I am back, to give you all I got.     </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
