<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>I'm Doing Everything (For You) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Do you ever do a thing or two just to wait. When you don't have a thing to say. I'll try to take this love but I don't know. Cause I don't wanna wait I'm tired of. looking for the folks who try to say. that we don't know until were old cause. that's how it goes but what do i know, oh. And please pick me I'm a terrible mess. You know I just can't help it and I just gotta confess. You do what you do when I care a little less</segment1>
		<segment2>[Bridge:]. So stay I'm gonna do everything I'm gonna make it right. I'm gonna make it good I'm gonna do it alright. I'm gonna write it down I'm gonna make a sound</segment2>
		<segment3>[Chorus:]. Cause I'm doing everything for you. Cause I love to be near to you. Something just takes me away to a place where I'm happy. Cause I'm doing everything for you. Yeah you know that I adore you. and I just can't take it anymore</segment3>
		<segment4>Oh! Oh! you know I gotta know, yeah, oh no</segment4>
		<segment5>So I'll be making up things for you to see. Like romantic lights surrounding Italy. Cause you deserve the very best, and I'll never rest. So I'll be sure to pass that test. And I just smile and say whoa cause you just gotta know. That every time we stay you never lose your way. It reaches to the stars shines up the clouds and lights up this whole world. Bless your heart you've made me happy again. It's been so long and I'm sick of pretending. You've enlighted the pain in my heart</segment5>
		<segment6>[Bridge Repeat]</segment6>
		<segment7>[Chorus Repeat]</segment7>
		<segment8>Cause I do wanna wait for another day cause I can feel this is right. I do wanna make this go on for too much longer. Cause you've got a ringless finger and I could go buy a ring right now. Well.. Actually I don't have money but that's ok. Cause I can figure it out</segment8>
		<segment9>[Chorus Repeat]    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
