<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Indivisable </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>For all the people in the world that don't understand. Exactly what it is we have here in this motherland. See the Father's hand started up a master plan. There's been many through the test of time take a stand. But had they ran who knows where we would be now. I thank God it's something I don't have to think about. Instead my thoughts are on the ones who laid it on the line. KIA gave their lives to let freedom shine. But in the meantime I think of those of your kind. And wonder how it is you get things so messed up inside your mind. Just think a second how long it's been going on before you. They're the one's who even helped you have the right to argue</segment1>
		<segment2>Stop complaining move along. Open your eyes and see what's going on. We need to get back to the ways of the days of old. One nation under God indivisible</segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus</segment3>
		<segment4>All the people let me hear you give a holler. In God we trust, In God we trust. We stamp it on our penny, nickel, dime, quarter, dollar. In God we trust, In God we trust. The people of the nation let me hear you give a holler. In God we trust, In God we trust. We stamp it on our penny, nickel, dime, quarter, dollar. In God we trust, In God we trust</segment4>
		<segment5>The other day I saw the news somebody else complaining. They want the motto taken off of the Benjamin Franklin. They got a problem with my God and that I believe in it. But the don't got a problem with the money when they spend it. They're so offended by 4 words that need no explanation. In GOD we trust the motto of this greatest nation. Not just a motto but something that we truly believe. If you don't like it you can pack a bag and you can leave</segment5>
		<segment6>One nation under God indivisible. You can't take back that, that was never yours    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
