<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>I Never Got To See The West Coast </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>So is it courage or strength. and is that what I'm waiting for?. If I could just kill myself. would it also kill the remorse?. I wanted so badly to catch a break. but I'm only breaking down. I'm still here and standing. but if it's up to me. I don't think I'll be hanging around</segment1>
		<segment2>The drink slips down my throat. and the burn cures nice and slow. All the worst parts I wouldn't want you to see. The only parts left of me. Now, here I am. Just a kid without a better plan. But it's the simple thoughts that haunt me the most. I never got to see the west coast</segment2>
		<segment3>Spent my nights just asking why. Would God let me become like this. Was it a joke from the start?. Was I suppose to laugh more at it?. And everyone's quoting their teachers and preachers. but their words make me feel so alone. No one ever says that they've had those thoughts. in the middle of the night. No one ever admits that they wanted to take their life.</segment3>
		<segment4>The drink slips down my throat. and the burn cures nice and slow. All the worst parts I wouldn't want you to see. The only parts left of me. Now, here I am. Just a kid without a better plan. But it's the simple thoughts that haunt me the most. I never got to see the west coast</segment4>
		<segment5>But it's the life I dreamed I have. The love I find in my grasp. The words I could share with someone. Those thoughts keep the breath in my lungs. That tomorrow my hope will become. to feel a love that can't be undone. And save a wretch like me.</segment5>
		<segment6>So if the drink slips down your throat. and the burn cures nice and slow. All the worst parts you wouldn't want me to see. The same parts, I have in me. Now, scares me to we look this way. I feel just like you do. But when you're by yourself you should know    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
