<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>In My Heart (Remix) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Oh ya, oh ya </segment1>
		<segment2>Verse 1: Pick up my dreams. That need a jump start. Given all I can. I crash and for what. You stick up for me when I fall hard. Take down all my fear. Juggle my thoughts around in my head. So I won't break down around each bend. With my foot on the pedal I'll race ahead. Drive this life with me </segment2>
		<segment3>Pre-chorus 1: I am I am aware. I hear that You are near </segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus: You are. You are in my heart. You are. You are in my heart. When every little thing is falling apart. You're beating in my heart. You're beating in my heart </segment4>
		<segment5>Verse 2: When the clock strikes night and I'm in the dark. You'll be here and there you are. When the lines get cut and I feel far. Reaching out to me. When I feel like a freak. The words you say tell me to believe that I'm OK. When I don't make sence cause I'm this way. You see the best in me </segment5>
		<segment6>Pre-chorus 2: I am I am aware. I hear that You are near </segment6>
		<segment7>Chorus: You are. You are in my heart. You are. You are in my heart. When every little thing is falling apart. You're beating in my heart. You are. You are in my heart. You are. You are in my heart. When every little thing is falling apart. You're beating in my heart. You're beating in my heart </segment7>
		<segment8>Bridge: There's a love I can be. There's a buzz around You and me. You're the sum of all I need. I count the number of things You do for me </segment8>
		<segment9>You are (oh ya) </segment9>
		<segment10>Chorus: You are. You are in my heart. You are. You are in my heart. When every little thing is falling apart. You're beating in my heart. You are. You are in my heart. You are. You are in my heart. When every little thing is falling apart. You're beating in my heart. You're beating in my heart. You're beating in my heart </segment10>
		<segment11>You are..     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
