<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>In Pieces </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>We got acquainted on a warm summer's night. Top floor of your apartment was where we started clicking for the first time. And our future it was so bright. I was there to be the melody. and under the impression that you would be my harmony</segment1>
		<segment2>Pretty soon we were dressed up in lights. But if you wanted center stage, I was there on your right. I was singing on the grandstand where i think we made our first plans. To be a constant source of friction, a clear contradiction. This is where we discovered our dissonance</segment2>
		<segment3>All these things I think about in pieces. All these scenes I play again in my mind. When were the two of us destined to come undone?. When we had just begun</segment3>
		<segment4>Is it possible I got something wrong?. In the middle of a moment, while we labored over song?. And we toiled over every word. Was it your voice you wanted heard?. At the time I thought I tried to strip away some my pride. but I couldn't understand where you were coming from</segment4>
		<segment5>All these things you could explain in pieces. All these things you could have said but never tried. You were always there waiting for us to come undone. And now all that we've built, yes everything we have came undone</segment5>
		<segment6>We always used to fight. The record that we kept of wrongs and rights would lock us there inside. You turned and walked away. and left me picking pieces off the ground in scattered disarray </segment6>
		<segment7>All these things I could explain in pieces. And all these things I'd want to say but how could I?. I was always there waiting for you to come undone. And I knew you would. I knew you would break someday and come unglued. I knew you were waiting for the day. when you'd leave us and be gone for good</segment7>
		<segment8>We always used to fight. The record that we kept of wrongs and rights would lock us there inside. You turned and walked away. and left me picking pieces off the ground but I am here to stay. (although in pieces I'll go pick up the pieces). I'm waiting out the night. For when we see the sun the work we've done will finally come to light. And with the break of day. we'll put the pieces back in place somehow until we find our way. (although in pieces). I'll go pick up the pieces every time    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
