<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Intro </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>[Talking:] We gon fight [2x]</segment1>
		<segment2>[Chorus (4x):]. I'm fighting temptations [2x]. I'm fighting fighting [2x]</segment2>
		<segment3>[Verse 1:]. Ahh, I'm trying to live a godly life. Be lying if I said it ain't hard. I can't even open my eyes. Cause everything is Rated R. Can't believe what I'm seeing, I'm speechless. All I see is your booty and cleavage. You just tryin to find my weakness. I'm determined to pass your test</segment3>
		<segment4>[Repeat Chorus (4x):]</segment4>
		<segment5>[Verse 2:]. Ahh, Tryin to be spirit lit. I ain't gon let you in my head. And like a spider you are weaving your web. Tryin to get a brotha in your bed. You don't like it, that I'm standing tall. Though the reason why faith didn't fall. So put away your seduced lips. I know the devil's all in your kiss</segment5>
		<segment6>[Repeat Chorus (4x):]</segment6>
		<segment7>[Verse 3:]. Ahh, under pressure to make this money. This recession makin things so hard. I don't wanna do nothing illegal. Then I gotta put my trust in god. Lord, I'm reaching out for help. I can't win the war by myself. Lord, I need a little more patience. And more strength so I can fight temptations</segment7>
		<segment8>[Vamp:]. Everytime I turn around, I can see you trying to take me down, trying to keep me bound. The annointing on my life just won't allowyou to trap me, zap me, stop me, block me. God's got me in his hands, somebody gotaa stand, I'll be the man. I refuse to run, yep, I'm the one, that's gonna get the job done, God's son. Like David, I'm gonna slay the giant, you know god's with me, you can't deny it. Tryin yo best to keep me quiet, what you sellin I refuse to buy it. You might as well find someone else to lie with. Every disease, you probably got it, keep it to yourself, because I don't want it. No, I don't want it.    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
