<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Irene </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Hush little baby don't you cry. Daddy's gonna sing you a lullaby. Everything's gonna be alright. The Lord's gonna answer your prayer tonight </segment1>
		<segment2>Hush little baby don't you cry. Daddy's gonna sing you a lullaby. Everything's gonna be alright. The Lords gonna answer your prayer </segment2>
		<segment3>Last night you had a dream you was the homecoming queen. Today you're 18, happy birthday Irene. Quit school you had to drop out to raise your little child. Doesn't seem to be anyone around. You've got to reach up to touch rock bottom. The powers that be keep you downtrodden. Daughter of Zion, I heard you prayer. Just cast your cares and please beware of snakes. They come in all shapes and sizes. Tempt you, put scales on your eye lids. Don't waste your sorrows. They'll give you strength tomorrow..tomorrow. Your Calvary's about to come so. Keep your head up, don't you ever let up. This storm will pass you'll be ready for the next one </segment3>
		<segment4>Hey little girl with the pressures of the. World on you shoulders. Don't say that it's over. I heard your prayers, just cast your cares. And I'll be there so don't you fear (2x) </segment4>
		<segment5>CHORUS (2x) </segment5>
		<segment6>Irene, I carried you when you was to weak to walk. I took to you when you gave your heart to God. Faithful and true, that's what I'll always be to you. Believe in you, believe in Me and these mountains have to. Move. You have dreams and aspirations. I knew you before Creation. Your foundation's solid. I will give you a palace, restore your soul. You'll be up for any challenge. Many storms are on the way; better sharpen your faith. Count the cost, take up your Cross. And wear it everyday. Rest in me and I will give you strength. Blessed is she, Irene, who seeks my face </segment6>
		<segment7>Hey little girl with the pressures of the. World on you shoulders. Don't say that it's over. I heard your prayers, just cast your cares. And I'll be there so don't you fear (2x) </segment7>
		<segment8>CHORUS (2x) </segment8>
		<segment9>Everything's gonna be alright (3x). Be alright (2x) </segment9>
		<segment10>(Yeah)Father I'm stronger I say. Father I'm stronger I say. Father I'm stronger. Than when I first believed yeah (2x) </segment10>
		<segment11>I say hey little girl with the pressures of. The world on her shoulders. Don't say that it's over (2x) </segment11>
		<segment12>I heard your prayers, just cast your cares. And I'll be there, so don't you fear </segment12>
		<segment13>CHORUS (2x) </segment13>
		<segment14>The Lord's gonna answer your prayer tonight. The Lord's gonna answer your prayer tonight. The Lord's gonna answer your prayer.    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
