<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Is Forever Enough </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>What makes. All of us hate. We're all the same. We roll the dice. And we play your game. We complicate. Show us the way. Before it's to late and the whole thing breaks. We have a name. We all create. Everything else but mistakes we made. We'll make a change. We'll concentrate. Before we suffocate!</segment1>
		<segment2>Can't hold this in and keep it quiet any longer. We're fallin' in and now this feeling's getting stronger</segment2>
		<segment3>Take my breath away. Now I'm tryin' to get up. I'm tryin' to retrace my steps back. To where ever I messed up. Is forever enough?. (I'm holdin' on). I know you'll be there whenever I wake up</segment3>
		<segment4>What makes. Everything change. We're not the same. We all get stuck in the same place shame. We take it in. We dominate. Put on the pressure and the whole thing breaks. Our common weight. Why do we hate. We throw it away like the last crusade. We rearrange. We need to change. Before we suffocate!</segment4>
		<segment5>Can't hold this in and keep it quiet any longer. We're fallin in and now this feeling's getting stronger</segment5>
		<segment6>Can't hold this in and keep it quiet any longer. We're fallin in and now this feeling's getting stronger</segment6>
		<segment7>Take my breath away now. I'm tryin' to get up. I'm tryin' to retrace my steps back. To where ever I messed up. Is forever enough. (I'm holdin' on). I know You'll be there whenever I wake up</segment7>
		<segment8>Now I'm tryin' to get up. I'm tryin' to retrace my steps back. I've falling in and now this feeling's getting stronger</segment8>
		<segment9>You take my breath away now. I'm tryin' to get up. I'm tryin' to retrace my steps back. To where ever I messed up. Is forever enough (Is forever enough). I'm holdin' on. I know You'll be there whenever I wake up. When ever I wake up. I'll know You'll be there. Whenever I wake up. Whenever I wake up. When I wake up!</segment9>
		<segment10>What makes. All of us hate. Show us the way. Before it's to late and the whole thing breaks    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
