<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>I've Got The Music In Me </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Ain't got no trouble in my life. No foolish dreams to make me cry. I'm never frightened or worried. I know I'll always get by </segment1>
		<segment2>I heat up, I cool down. When something gets in my way I go round it. Won't let life get me down. Gonna take it the way that I found it </segment2>
		<segment3>I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. </segment3>
		<segment4>Some say that life is a circle. But that ain't the way that I found it. Gonna move in a straight line. Keeping my feet firmly on the ground </segment4>
		<segment5>I heat up, I cool down. I've got words in my head so I'll say them. Won't let life get me down. Catch a hold of my blues and just play them </segment5>
		<segment6>I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. </segment6>
		<segment7>Feel funky, feel good. Gonna tell you I'm in the neighbourhood. Gonna fly like a bird on the wing. Hold onto your hat honey - sing, sing, sing, sing </segment7>
		<segment8>I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. I got music, I got music, I've got the music in me. I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. I've got music, pretty music, I've got the music in me. </segment8>
		<segment9>I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music. I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me. Yeah. I've got the music, I've got the music in me, I've got the music in me, I've got the music, I've got the music in me. Yeah.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
