<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Jacob's Name Is Israel </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>When Jacob was born he took a long time comin. Took the ankle of his older brother. They were twins, but Jake was later; Esau was his fathers favorite. Cause he spent his time as a hunter. And every single time, Jacob had to wait in line. He started then to strive to get his way. He was just a little boy; he was mamas pride and joy. He loved to work with mother all day. But now, now, Jacobs name is Israel  Whatd you say?. Jacobs name is Israel  By the way, I said. Jacobs name is Israel  Cause he strived. Jacobs name is Israel  The father of the tribes  His own 12. You could read in Genesis how Esau burst into the kitchen. And said, &quot;Jacob, give me some stuff to swallow!&quot;. Jacob said, Sell me your birthright! Esau said, What is it worth right now, Im dyin' of hunger; my stomachs hollow!&quot;. And so Esau sold his rights; Jacob later set his sights. Upon the blessing Isaac would pray. He pretended he was Esau, and his father couldnt see so. Jacob stole the blessing and ran away. But now, now, Jacobs name is Israel  Whatd you say?. Jacobs name is Israel  By the way, I said. Jacobs name is Israel  Cause he strived. Jacobs name is Israel  The father of the tribes  His own 12. After 20 years with Laban, well, the Lord spoke to Jacob: Take your family with you back to Canaan.. Jacob knew hed meet his brother as he travelled through the desert. He was scared, and I wouldnt blame him. And in the night he fought with a Man we think was God. He wrestled with him to the break of day. He took Jacobs hip and knocked it out of joint right at the socket. He blessed him, and He gave him this name. But now, now, Jacobs name is Israel  Whatd you say?. Jacobs name is Israel  By the way, I said. Jacobs name is Israel  Cause he strived. Jacobs name is Israel  The father of the tribes     </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
