<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>January 1979 </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>January, 1979 saw a terrible crash and it couldnt help but laugh. My ear pressed against the pass like a glass on a wall of a hospital photograph. My forehead no longer sweet with holy kisses worthy of your fiery lips. I was floating in a peaceful sea rescued by a sinking ship.</segment1>
		<segment2>If I could become the servant of all, no lower place to fall. (I could be your servant). If I could become the servant of all, no lower place to fall. (If I could be your servant). If I could become the servant of all, no lower place to fall. (I could be your servant). If I could become the servant of all, no lower place to fall. (If I could be your servant)</segment2>
		<segment3>You watch me like a ten car highway wreck with a tact, bold or curiosity?. Us looking down on the tops of the hats of us passersby from your seventh floor balcony. And grew such a height we missed creatures too small for sight. Carry on over conversation as the misguided insects. Crown me their grasshopper king with a dance of celebration.</segment3>
		<segment4>After years with their crown on my head, Im rolling over in bed unconcerned and comfortably numb. Kept busy indulging in the pleasures of the wealthy. Oh, someone make me afraid of what Ive become. At the first sign of possible sorrow Ill turn my heel and run. Oh, Ill never learn. My life is a cup of sugar I borrowed before time began and forgot to return.</segment4>
		<segment5>It was a matter of time, I always said I could see but now Im going blind. (I could be your servant). It was a matter of time, I always said I could see but now Im going blind. (If I could be your servant). It was a matter of time, I always said I could see but now Im going blind. (I could be your servant). It was a matter of miserable time but I heard somewhere, There was a cure for useless eyes. (If I could be your servant).     </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
