<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Jesus Medley: I Love Jesus/I Love the Lord/Bless That Wonderful Name of </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19,segment20</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Verse 1 (x3): I love Jesus. He's my Saviour. When the storms are raging. He's my shelter. Where He leads me. I will follow. Because I love Jesus. And He loves me</segment1>
		<segment2>I love the Lord, and I won't take it back (x3). He has been so good to me</segment2>
		<segment3>I love the Lord, and I won't take it back (x3). He has been so good to me</segment3>
		<segment4>I love the Lord, and I won't take it back (x3). He has been so good to me</segment4>
		<segment5>He's been so good (so good). So good (so good). So good (so good). So very good (been so very good). So good (so good). So good (so good). He has been so good to me. He's been so good (so good). Been so good (so good). So good (so good). So very good (been so very good). So good (so good). So good (so good). He has been so good to me </segment5>
		<segment6>Let's just bless that wonderful name of Jesus. Come on and bless that wonderful name of Jesus. Bless that wonderful name of Jesus. No other name (no other name I know). Come on bless that wonderful name of Jesus. Bless that wonderful name of Jesus (x2). No other (no other name I know)</segment6>
		<segment7>There is power in the name of Jesus. Yes there is power (power in the name of Jesus). Oh God there's power (there's power in the name of Jesus). No other name (no other name I know)</segment7>
		<segment8>Jesus, Jesus. No other name under heaven can save. But Jesus. Jesus, Jesus. No other name (no other name I know). Jesus, Jesus. No other name (no other name under heaven can save). Nobody but (Jesus). Come on say (Jesus). No other name I know</segment8>
		<segment9>Yes I got it (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life). Yes I got it (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life). Yes I got it (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life). I know that I have it (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life). Say yes I got it (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life). Everybody here knows (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life). Yes I got it (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life). Somebody raise your voice and say (yes I got it). Everlasting life (everlasting life)</segment9>
		<segment10>Everlasting life (everlasting life) [x4]</segment10>
		<segment11>Got everlasting life (everlasting life) [x4]</segment11>
		<segment12>Jesus gave it to me (everlasting life). Many years ago (everlasting life)</segment12>
		<segment13>Got everlasting life (everlasting life) [x2]</segment13>
		<segment14>Say Jesus (Jesus). Jesus (Jesus)</segment14>
		<segment15>Somebody call Him (Jesus) [x2]</segment15>
		<segment16>Let me hear you call Him (Jesus). Raise your voice and call Him (Jesus). Jesus (Jesus). Jesus (Jesus). The name of salvation (Jesus). The name of redemption (Jesus). The name of deliverance (Jesus). The name above names (Jesus). Jesus (Jesus)</segment16>
		<segment17>Call Him (Jesus) [x3]</segment17>
		<segment18>Oh Jesus (Jesus) [x3]</segment18>
		<segment19>Oh (Jesus) </segment19>
		<segment20>Somebody call Him (Jesus) [x2].     </segment20>
	</english>
</song>
