<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Joyful, Joyful </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Joyful, joyful, we adore You. God of glory and Lord of love. Hearts unfold like flowers before You. Opening to the sun above</segment1>
		<segment2>Joyful, joyful, we adore You. God of glory, Lord of love. Hearts unfold like flowers before You. Opening to the sun above</segment2>
		<segment3>Melt the clouds of sin and sadness. Drive the dark of doubt away</segment3>
		<segment4>Joyful, joyful, we adore You. Hearts unfold like flowers before You. Joyful, joyful, we adore You. Joyful, we adore You</segment4>
		<segment5>All Your works with joy surround You. Earth and Heaven reflect Your ways. Stars and angels sing around You. Center of unbroken praise</segment5>
		<segment6>Melt the clouds of sin and sadness. Drive the dark of doubt away</segment6>
		<segment7>Joyful, joyful, we adore You. Hearts unfold like flowers before You. Joyful, joyful, we adore You. Joyful, we adore You</segment7>
		<segment8>God our Father, Christ, our Brother. All who live in love are Thine. Teach us how to love each other. Lift us to the joy divine</segment8>
		<segment9>Oh God, our Father, Christ, our Brother. All who live in love are Thine. Teach us how to love each other. Lift us to the joy divine</segment9>
		<segment10>Oh God, our Father, Christ, our Brother. All who live in love are Thine. Teach us how to love each other. Lift us to the joy divine</segment10>
		<segment11>Joyful, joyful, we adore You. Hearts unfold like flowers before You. Joyful, joyful, we adore You. Hearts unfold like flowers before You</segment11>
		<segment12>Oh God, our Father. All who live in love are Thine. Teach us how to love each other</segment12>
		<segment13>Copyright © Casting Crowns     </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
