<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Just a Glimpse </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I don't have to fully know. Just how far Your love can go. To sing of Your love for me </segment1>
		<segment2>I don't have to comprehend. How Your mercy never ends. To sing of Your mercy </segment2>
		<segment3>And all I need is. All I really need is </segment3>
		<segment4>Just a glimpse of You. And I'm in awe. Just a glimpse of You. My God. Just a glimpse of You. And all I can do is worship. (All I can do is worship You Lord Yea) </segment4>
		<segment5>And I don't have to clearly see. How amazing grace can be. To sing of Your grace for me </segment5>
		<segment6>And I don't have to fully grasp. The measure of Your holiness. To sing holy holy </segment6>
		<segment7>And all I need is. All I really need is </segment7>
		<segment8>Just a glimpse of You. And I'm in awe. Just a glimpse of You. My God. Just a glimpse of You. And all I can do is worship </segment8>
		<segment9>I worship You. I worship You. I worship You </segment9>
		<segment10>Just a glimpse of You. And I stand in awe. Just a glimpse of You. You take my breathe away. My God. Just a glimpse of You. And all I can do is worship </segment10>
		<segment11>Just a glimpse of You (just a glimpse of You and Im in awe). And I'm in awe. Just a glimpse of You (a glimpse ofshow me Your glory). My God. Just a glimpse of You. And all I can do is worship </segment11>
		<segment12>Just a glimpse of You. And I'm in awe. Just a glimpse of You (oh God I stand in wonder). My God (and amazement of You). Just a glimpse of You. And all I can do is worship </segment12>
		<segment13>All go ahead and worship him tonight. We worship You (I worship You). We lift up our voices in praise. And thanksgiving Lord (I worship You). We worship You. I worship You </segment13>
		<segment14>We worship You Lord. In spirit and truth. We worship You. We stand in child like amazement. Oh with our eyes wide open. We worship You. With our hands stretched wide. We worship You. With our hearts wide open Lord. We worship You    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
