<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Leave It In The Valley </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I got your message on the phone. So tell me what's going on?. You say your day started so great. And then it went so wrong</segment1>
		<segment2>Well no one ever plans for the bad days. Do they? No. But I am here if you're needing a friend</segment2>
		<segment3>Hey, don't give up tonight. I know you're going through the valley. But you're gonna make it out alright</segment3>
		<segment4>Hey tell your trouble goodbye. Go on and leave it in the valley. Leave it in the valley tonight</segment4>
		<segment5>So you think He don't know what He's doing. You think He ain't by your side. Well, God knows when you're broken. And He's loving you, He's holding you. So, so tight</segment5>
		<segment6>So let the rain fall, He'll be standing there. Getting wet with you. You might get cold but you won't be there alone</segment6>
		<segment7>Hey, don't give up tonight</segment7>
		<segment8>But you're gonna make it out alright</segment8>
		<segment9>Hey tell your trouble goodbye. Go on and leave it in the valley. Leave it in the valley tonight</segment9>
		<segment10>And when you're hanging by a thread, hold on. You know the darkest part is right before the dawn. So when your fear has worn you out. Feels like the sky is on the ground. He ain't gonna let you down. He'll never let you down</segment10>
		<segment11>Hey, don't give up tonight. I know you're going through the valley. But you're gonna make it out alright</segment11>
		<segment12>Hey tell your trouble bye-bye. Go on and leave it in the valley. Leave it in the valley tonight</segment12>
		<segment13>Hey, leave it in the valley tonight. Hey tell your trouble goodbye. Go on and leave it in the valley. Leave it in the valley tonight. I got your message on the phone. So tell me what's going on?. You say your day started so great    </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
