<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Lessons Learned </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>There's some things that I regret. Some words I wish had gone unsaid. Some starts that had some better endings. Been some bad times I 've been through. Damage I could not undo. Some things I wish I could do all all over again. But it don't really matter. When life gets that much harder. It makes you that much stronger, oh. Some pages turned, some bridges burned. But there were lessons learned</segment1>
		<segment2>From every tear that had to fall from my eyes. From every day I wondered how I'd get through the night. From every change life has thrown me. I'm thankful for every break in my heart. I'm grateful for every scar. Some pages turned, some bridges burned. But there were lessons learned</segment2>
		<segment3>There's mistakes that I have made. Some chances I just threw away. Some roads I never should've taken. Been some signs I didn't see. Hearts that I hurt needlessly. Some wounds that I wish I could have one more chance to mend. But it don't make no difference. The past can't be re-written. You get the life you're given, oh. Some pages turned, some bridges burned. But there were lessons learned</segment3>
		<segment4>From every tear that had to fall from my eyes. From every day I wondered how I'd get through the night. From every change life has thrown me. I'm thankful for every breath in my heart. I'm grateful for every scar. Some pages turned, some bridges burned. But there were lessons learned</segment4>
		<segment5>And all the things that break you. Are all the things that make you strong. You can't change the past coz it's gone. And you gotta just move on. It's all lessons learned</segment5>
		<segment6>Bridge with new changes: and all the things that break you. Are all the things that make you strong. You can't change the past cuz it's gone. You just gotta move on. Because it's all lessons learned</segment6>
		<segment7>. .     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
