<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Let It Out </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>How long can you keep building. Those walls around your heart?. And how long can you keep running. From who you really are?</segment1>
		<segment2>Don't you know that he knows you. Sees everything you've done. So tell why you keep trying. To fool everyone?</segment2>
		<segment3>Do you wanna feel true redemption?. And do you wanna be free?</segment3>
		<segment4>Let it out. Let it out. Everything you've worked so hard to hide. Let it out. Let it out. Leave it at the cross where Jesus died. Take off your mask. Find peace at last. Cause He loves you more than you could ever know. Let it out</segment4>
		<segment5>The weary and the broken. Be everything that's true. Admit how much you need healing. Let Him bring it all to you</segment5>
		<segment6>Do you wanna have true salvation?. Do you wanna have peace?</segment6>
		<segment7>Let it out. Let it out. Everything you've worked so hard to hide. Let it out. Let it out. Leave it at the cross where Jesus died. Take off your mask. Find peace at last. Cause He loves you more than you could ever know</segment7>
		<segment8>Trade it all for love and freedom. Oooo Let it out. Trade it all for saving grace. Yah. Let the past go. Cause you can't know. It never will define you. Everything has made you. Nothings gonna be the same</segment8>
		<segment9>Let it out. Let it out. Everything you've worked so hard to hide. Let it out. Let it out. Leave it at the cross where Jesus died. Take off your mask. Find peace at last. Cause He loves you more than you could ever know</segment9>
		<segment10>Let it out. Let it out. Everything you've worked so hard to hide. Let it out. Let it out. Leave it at the cross where Jesus died. Take off your mask. Find peace at last. Cause He loves you more than you could ever know. Let it out     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
