<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Let The Church Say Amen (feat. Marvin Winans) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Let the church say amen, let the church say amen. God has spoken, so let the church say amen. Let the church, let em say amen. If you believe the word, let the whole church say amen. God has spoken, so let the church say amen. Lift your hands, lift your hands. God has spoken, so let the church say amen, Oh, thank you Lord. God has spoken, so let the church say amen </segment1>
		<segment2>Choir enter </segment2>
		<segment3>Let the church say amen. Let the church everybody say amen. God God has spoken. So let the church let the church say say amen </segment3>
		<segment4>Vocals and choir </segment4>
		<segment5>Can I get a witness let the church say amen. To what His plans are let the church say amen. To what His words say. God has spoken God has spoken. Let the church let the church say say amen amen </segment5>
		<segment6>Make this your response amen. To whatever He says amen. From the healing of your body amen. To the raising of the dead amen. No matter how you feeling amen. Or how your world is reeling amen. Battle on through the night amen. Cause you're going to win the fight amen. Even in the valley amen. Or standing at your red sea amen. Continue to say amen. Cause your help is on the way amen </segment6>
		<segment7>My God has spoken. I heard Him let the church so let the church say say amen. Lift your hands wherever you are, and let the church. Let the church say amen. Amen, say let the church let the church say say amen, God has spoken God has spoken. Hallelujah let the church let the church say say amen. All we needed was a word from the Lord. We've got it so let the church let the church say amen. Oh, let the church let the whole church say amen. God has spoken God has spoken well, well, well. Let the church let the church let the church say say amen </segment7>
		<segment8>I need you to say it amen. When your dream is about to die amen. Knowing that God is not a man amen. He just can't lie amen. In spite of what amen. What the devil does amen. Know you've got a word amen. That has come from above amen. Faith must be amen. Must be what you say amen. So open your mouth amen. And say amen today amen. Cause God has spoken. I heard Him when He said it let the church so let the church say amen </segment8>
		<segment9>You and you and you say amen. From the deacons amen. To the mothers amen. All of the sisters amen. All of the brothers say. God has spoken oh my my. let the church let the church say amen.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
