<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Let Us Pray </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I hear you say your heart is aching. You've got trouble in the making. You ask if I'll be praying for you please. And in keeping with convention. I'll say yes with good intentions. To pray later making mention of your needs. But since we have this moment here at heaven's door. We should start knocking now, what are we waiting for? </segment1>
		<segment2>Let us pray, let us pray, everywhere in every way. Every moment of the day, it is the right time. For the Father above, He is listening with love. And He wants to answer us, so let us pray </segment2>
		<segment3>So when we feel the Spirit moving. Prompting, prodding, and behooving. There is no time to be losing, let us pray. Let the Father hear us saying. What we need to be conveying. Even while this song is playing, let us pray. And just because we say the word, Amen. It doesn't mean this conversation needs to end </segment3>
		<segment4>Let us pray, let us pray, everywhere in every way. Every moment of the day, it is the right time. Let us pray without end and when we finish start again. Like breathing out and breathing in, let us pray </segment4>
		<segment5>Let us approach the throne of grace with confidence. As our prayers draw us near. To the One who knows our needs. Before we even call His name </segment5>
		<segment6>Let us pray, let us pray, everywhere in every way. Every moment of the day, it is the right time. For the Father above, He is listening with love. And He wants to answer us, so let us pray. Let us pray everywhere in every way. Every moment of the day, it is the right time. Let us pray without end and when we finish start again. Like breathing out and breathing in, let us pray </segment6>
		<segment7>Our Father which art in Heaven. Hallowed be Thy name. Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done. On earth as it is in Heaven. Let us pray.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
