<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Life </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Life is a series of impossible dreams, yeah. Full of disappointment and it ain't what it seems. Everybody's pulling you a different way. You want to close your eyes and make it all go away. But what you gonna do when the rent comes do. And the dollars in your wallet are numbered few. Or your neighbor comes knocking on your front door. He wants the mower that you borrowed. The night before your garage burned down. Your boss is screaming. 'Cause he walked in your office and. He found you on top of your desk asleep. But what you gonna do that's life! </segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus. Life! Too much to do and too much strife. Life! Your girlfriend left ya and it cuts life a knife. Life! Seventy years and a nagging wife. Life! You look in the mirror and it's Barney Fife. (What do you mean by that? [First Time]) </segment2>
		<segment3>You wrecked your buddy's car and. You cracked your head!. It wouldn't have happened if you'd looked ahead and braked. But your mind was racing. 'Cause you was thinkin'. 'Bout chasing that girl who turned you down. Everybody's talking 'bout it. All over town. But then things just get worse. You look in the mirror and you think it's a curse. Your hair is falling out on your pillow and all through the house. But what you gonna do that's life! </segment3>
		<segment4>(Chorus) </segment4>
		<segment5>Bridge. Life is a dirty trick. If you listen to the devil's lies. But life is another man's treasure. If he's given it up to Christ </segment5>
		<segment6>Now wait a minute buddy. My story ain't done. God said it all when He gave the world His only Son. To die on the cross. Just when you think that all is lost. There's hope for all mankind. Just give it to Him. And you can't find life more abundantly. And that's the only reason for life! </segment6>
		<segment7>(Chorus)    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
