<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Live Life Loud </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Someone throw your hands up. If you wanna take a chance, then. You gotta sing a little louder. Let's wake this crowd up</segment1>
		<segment2>Someone throw your hands up. If you wanna take a chance, then. You gotta sing a little louder. Let's wake this crowd up</segment2>
		<segment3>I got a hankering for something special. Tonight's the night it becomes official. Don't stop the rock, hold both your hands up. Show these people how to shake things up</segment3>
		<segment4>I'm not sitting down 'til I'm older. And I'm not shuttin' up 'til it's over. Raise your hands and shout if you're with me. Once we start, it won't make a difference</segment4>
		<segment5>If you wanna live life loud, throw your hands up. If you wanna scream and shout, let me hear you. Takin' all the fakers out if you're with me. Everybody work it, just keep living</segment5>
		<segment6>I started figuring with good intentions. Listen up now, give me your attention. Don't make a sound if you don't believe me. You won't wake up, you'll just keep living</segment6>
		<segment7>I'm not sitting down 'til I'm older. And I'm not shutting up 'til it's over. Raise your hands and shout if you're with me. Once we start, it won't make a difference</segment7>
		<segment8>If you wanna live life loud, throw your hands up. If you wanna scream and shout, let me hear you. Taking all the fakers out if you're with me. Everybody work it, just keep living</segment8>
		<segment9>Every time that I close my eyes, I catch a glimpse of the west coast sunrise. And I can tell you you're just as beautiful</segment9>
		<segment10>Someone throw your hands up. If you wanna take a chance, then. You gotta sing a little louder. Let's wake this crowd up</segment10>
		<segment11>Someone throw your hands up. If you wanna take a chance, then. You gotta sing a little louder. Let's wake this crowd up</segment11>
		<segment12>If you wanna live life loud, throw your hands up. If you wanna scream and shout, let me hear you. Takin' all the fakers out if you're with me. Everybody work it, just keep living</segment12>
		<segment13>Just keep living    </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
