<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Long Shot </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>You made the call. I step outside, cross that line. And I lose control. cause I've been waiting. It's beautifull to let go don't you know. Your everything I try to be. The rise and fall to respond to the call. I got butterflies</segment1>
		<segment2>Your all I have. So break me down. Your all I am. And nothing else matters</segment2>
		<segment3>This is a long shot. It's all I have. I'm ready to step it up. And all I need is your hand. And this is a long shot. Its who I am. I'm ready to take off. All I need is a plan</segment3>
		<segment4>I'm calling out. Take me, make me. I'm finding out. That You are my reason. It's beautifull to let go don't you know. Your everything I try to be. The rise and fall to respond to the call. I sing a new song</segment4>
		<segment5>You're all I have. So break me down. You're all I am. But nothing else matters. You're all I have. So break me down. You're all I am. And nothing else matters</segment5>
		<segment6>This is a long shot. It's all I have. I'm ready to step it up. And all I need is your hand. This is a long shot. It's who I am. I'm ready to take off. And all I need is a plan</segment6>
		<segment7>You're all I have x3. Yeah</segment7>
		<segment8>You're the plan. Yeah</segment8>
		<segment9>This is a long shot. It's all I have. I'm ready to step it up. And all I need is your hand. And This is a long shot. It's who I am. I'm ready to take off. All I need is a plan</segment9>
		<segment10>This is a long shot. This is the longest shot. I'm barely moving. You keep me breathing. This is a long shot. This is the longest shot. Cause I'm barely moving. You keep me breathing</segment10>
		<segment11>This is a long shot. It's all I have. Im ready to step it up. And all I need is your hand. This is a long shot. It's who I am. Im ready to take off. All I need is a plan</segment11>
		<segment12>    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
