<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Long Way Home </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I set out on a great adventure. The day my father started needing me home. He said there gonna be some mountains to climb. And some valleys were gonna go thorough. But I had no way of knowing. Just how hard this journey could be. Cause the mountains are stiper and the valleys are deeper. Than I ever would of dream</segment1>
		<segment2>But I know were gonna make it. And I know were gonna get there soon. And I know some times it seems like we. Doing the wrong way. But its just a long way home</segment2>
		<segment3>Some rocks in my shoes fears I wish I could lose. They make the mountain so hard to climb. And my heart gets so heavy. With the weight of the world some times. And theres a bag of regrets. I should have been and not gets. I keep on dragging around. And I can hardly can wait till the day I could lay them all dawn. Well I know that day is coming. And I know its gonna be here soon. And I know I wont turn back even if the whole world. Says Im doing the wrong way. Cause its just a long way home</segment3>
		<segment4>And when we cant take another step. The father will pick us up and carry us in his arms. And even on the best days. He says to remember were not home yet. So dont get too comfortable. Cause what you really are is just pilgrims passing through</segment4>
		<segment5>Well I know that day is coming. And I know its gonna be here soon. Ill keep on singing and believing. What all of my songs say. Cause our God has made a promise. And I know that everything he says its true. And he promised he would never ever leave us. Hes gonna lead us, Hell head us home. Every single step of the long way home. So keep on were gonna make it. Were just taking the long way home. Keep on were gonna make it. I know were gonna make it. Its just a long way home    </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
