<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Look Yourself </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Look, if you have one God. And one offer of eternity. That exceeds everything you ve ever wanted. With one opponent. Would you ask for it?. Or just let it slip? Yo</segment1>
		<segment2>He parks his Chevy, needs sleep, heart is heavy. He's thought about repentin already, sun is setting. This church is not having service it looks almost dead as he. Drops by but they keep on the electric. What a ghost town, he knelt down, don t know how. He opens his mouth just the word &quot;Help&quot; comes out. He's broken down, yet his heart is open now. The lost one's found, winds up homeward bound. Heads back to his family Look who's home, daddy. And, look, he's so happy, he chose his own path but he. Won't give up babbling, he broke his old habits they. Don't seem so bad to me, hope it's some fad. Like new Coke or Shaun Cassidy. Don't need no radical holy-rollin' masochist quotin' old passages. That's what'll happen then, though, he'll go fanatic-y. Better go batten the hatches and hope it don't last</segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus: You'd better look yourself in the mirror. You know that you wanted to get to Heaven when you're old. Do you really want God or not? Is it yes or no?. It's awful soon you say, but what is the right time?. You'd better look yourself in the book since you own it. In Romans, you never read it yet I know. You only get one shot to God, here's your chance to go. His offer to you may come once in your lifetime</segment3>
		<segment4>His soul's been saved even though his whole family's gaping. This world is blinded by Satan - they can't see. As he moves forward - it's true George Orwell. The moral of the story is truth's ignored, emotion's most important. He'll only cause problems, the Holy Ghost got him. He blows him all over, he knows the call's on him. Goes to go show his bro's at his Alma Mater, &quot;Welcome Back, Kotter&quot;. They know he's just one of their own, so don't bother. Said, &quot;Go home you barely know the Our Father&quot;. Well hold the phones cause he knows it holds water. If those don't want him no more he'll go farther. And he moved on and he read the Romans Road till he knows it cold and shows others. He's on his soap box and his tone becomes bold, I suppose he's no martyr. But the weak grows strong and the dumb becomes smarter</segment4>
		<segment5>Chorus: You'd better look yourself in the mirror. You know that you wanted to get to Heaven when you're old. Do you really want God or not? Is it yes or no?. It's awful soon you say, but what is the right time?. You'd better look yourself in the book since you own it. In Romans, you never read it yet I know. You only get one shot to God, here s your chance to go. His offer to you may come once in your lifetime</segment5>
		<segment6>No more names, I ve been changed, but you call it strange. To tell my mother 'n father truth off the true God's page. I was saying if you ve been sinning pursue God's grace. I've been shooed off and spit at like Rudolph the Reindeer. But I kept shinin' a lamplight that I can't stifle. You best believe somebody paid for my revival. Call the name of Christ and go find a Bible. Fact is I can't deny that I'm liable. To die if my plans collide with life's iceberg. Like the Titanic cause man needs God and you can't go buy a lifeboat. And it's no movie; there's no surprise survivors. This is high tide and you're tryin to row hard. And you're hittin' deeper waters tryin' to flee piranhas I see. Plus seaweed's got ya caught up between PBJ Otter and Bikini Bottom. Babe it's not a submarine you're on and you must believe the Son. He'll save you on the spot, He's comin ready or not. I've got to be to the point just like a nail on the cross. I formerly was lost, horrendously frail and fraught. With questions I know how Mother Hubbard's dog felt- famine, drought. Mom, I love you but this world has got to know. I cannot grow cold when Hell is hot. So please don't go into shock. Let the family talk. This way is their only opportunity to find God</segment6>
		<segment7>Chorus: You'd better look yourself in the mirror. You know that you wanted to get to Heaven when you're old. Do you really want God or not? Is it yes or no?. It's awful soon you say, but what is the right time?. You'd better look yourself in the book since you own it. In Romans, you never read it yet I know. You only get one shot to God, here's your chance to go. His offer to you may come once in your lifetime</segment7>
		<segment8>You can do anything if He gets inside you, man    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
