<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Lost at Sea </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Floating like driftwood. Slaved by the sea. Resolutely refusing to die. Without amnesty</segment1>
		<segment2>He's tossed by the waves. He's all out of flares. Nobody saves, nobody cares. Dehydrated lips speak words of despair. Unanswered prayer</segment2>
		<segment3>Amidst the sea of words. (Amidst the sea of words). He only hears the sound of sea birds. Who only whisper of a world beyond the waves</segment3>
		<segment4>And all those points of light. (All those points of light). The gently winking stars of night. Not out of sight but still his eyes are glazed</segment4>
		<segment5>And though his eyes perforate the horizon. He still can't find escape from his world. He lifts his head in unwanted motion. But he can't see himself tonight. Just broken starlight and waves</segment5>
		<segment6>Stupid and headstrong. She stands on the beach. She's calling his name out. But he doesn't hear her voice from where</segment6>
		<segment7>His vessel so small. Boat's bullied by waves to nowhere at all. Dehydrated lips speak words of despair. Unanswered prayer</segment7>
		<segment8>Amidst the sea of words. (Amidst the sea of words). He only hears the sound of sea birds. Who only whisper of a world beyond the waves</segment8>
		<segment9>And all those points of light. (All those points of light). The gently winking stars of night. Not out of sight but still his eyed are glazed</segment9>
		<segment10>Keep calling his name. Keep calling, perhaps he'll hear you. Keep calling his name. Maybe now he's not the one</segment10>
		<segment11>The one who's exiled form the world of you and me. The one who can't be reached,the one who's lost at sea. The one whose social skills have gone to atrophy. The one who drifts apart, the one who's lost at sea</segment11>
		<segment12>The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea</segment12>
		<segment13>The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea</segment13>
		<segment14>The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea</segment14>
		<segment15>The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea. The one who's lost at sea</segment15>
		<segment16>The one whose. Floating like driftwood. Floating like driftwood. Floating like driftwood. Floating like driftwood</segment16>
		<segment17>Floating like driftwood. Floating like driftwood. And talking like tree wood</segment17>
		<segment18>Floating like driftwood. Floating like driftwood. Floating like driftwood. Floating like driftwood    </segment18>
	</english>
</song>
