<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Lovely Day </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>When troubles come my way. I look to you and everything's ok. When help seems to disappear. I look to You and then its all so clear.</segment1>
		<segment2>When hard nights turn into hard days. How i long to seek your face. When blue skies turn to gray. I look to You and then I know its gonna be a. it's gonna be a lovely day.</segment2>
		<segment3>When I wake up in the morning, Lord. and the sun light hurts my eyes. and something without warning, Lord. bears heavy on my mind.</segment3>
		<segment4>Then I look to You (then I look to You). and the world's alright with me (and the world is alright). Just one look to You. and I know its gonna be (its gonna be). I think its gonna a lovely day.</segment4>
		<segment5>[chorus]. (a lovely day) lovely day, lovely day, lovely day, lovely day [4x]</segment5>
		<segment6>When the day that lies ahead of me. seems impossible to face. When someone else instead of me. always seems to know the way You know thats when I look to You.</segment6>
		<segment7>Then I look to You and the world's alright (and the world's alright with me). Then I look to You and the world is alright with me. Just one look to You (just one look to You and I know its gonna be). (just one look to You) just one look to You and I know it's gonna be. (and I know its gonna be) I think it's gonna be a lovely day.</segment7>
		<segment8>[chorus]. (a lovely day) lovely day, lovely day, lovely day, lovely day [4x]</segment8>
		<segment9>When I wake up in the morning Lord and the sun light hurts my eyes. and something without warning Lord You know that it bears heavy on my mind. When the day that lies ahead of me seems impossible to face, and there's someone else instead of me always seems to know the way.</segment9>
		<segment10>Then I look to You and the world is alright (and the world is alright with me). Then I look to You and the world is alright with me. Just one look to You and I know it's gonna be..gonna be..gonna be</segment10>
		<segment11>(a lovely day) lovely day, lovely day.....[until song fades out]    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
