<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Love, Peace &amp; Happiness </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Don't want to think about just where I would be. Had you not had the heart to come rescue me. Gave me a new start, on this life, had mercy. With you I fell in love, no I can see that I'm free. Your love is deep as the ocean. Wide as the sea. Your love has my deovtion. You get every part of me. There's so much that I can say but words don't really show. So I let my life speak so the world will know</segment1>
		<segment2>You've given me love, peace and happiness. You've given me life and I knowIi'm blessed. You've given me all that I need and yes. Lord with everything you've done for me. Most thankful cause you've given me you</segment2>
		<segment3>It's so amazing you were able to find. Something worth saving and with your love divine. You reached into this life andyou gave me a chance. Set my feet on a rock and now i can dance. Your love is deep as the ocean. Wide as the sea. Your love has my devotion. You get every part of me. There's so much I can say but words don't really show. So I let my life speak so the world will know</segment3>
		<segment4>You've given me love, peace and happiness. You've given me life and I know I'm blessed. You've given me all that I need and yes lord with everything you've done for me. Most thankful cause you've given me you</segment4>
		<segment5>There's so much that I can say like. So great and so powerful yes you are lord. There's so much that I can say like. Amazing incredible yes you are lord. There's so much that I can say but words. Don't really show. So I let my life speak so the world will know</segment5>
		<segment6>You've given me love, peace and happiness. You've given me life and I know I'm blessed. You've given me all that I need and yes lord with everything you've done for me. Most thankful cause you've given me you (3x) </segment6>
		<segment7>.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
