<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Made To Love </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>The dream is fading now I'm staring at the door. I know it's over 'cause my feet have hit the cold floor. Check my reflection, I ain't feeling what I see. Its no mystery</segment1>
		<segment2>Whatever happened to a passion I could live for?. What became of the flame that made me feel more?. And when did I forget .. </segment2>
		<segment3>That I was made to love You. I was made to find You. I was made just for You. Made to adore You. I was made to love and be loved by You. You were here before me. You were waiting on me. And you said You'd keep me never would You leave me. I was made to love (I was made to love). And be loved by You (Loved by You)</segment3>
		<segment4>The dream's alive with my eyes open wide. Back in the ring You got me swingin' for the grand prize. I feel the haters spittin' vapors on my dreams. But I still believe ..</segment4>
		<segment5>I'm reaching out, reachin' up, reachin' over. I feel a breeze cover me called Jehovah. And Daddy I'm on my way .. Cuz i was made to Love</segment5>
		<segment6>That I was made to love You. I was made to find You. I was made just for You. Made to adore You. I was made to love and be loved by You. You were here before me. You were waiting on me. And you said You'd keep me never would You leave me. I was made to love (I was made to love). And be loved by You (Loved by You)</segment6>
		<segment7>I was made to Love You. I was made just for You. Made to adore You. I was made to love (I was made to love) and be loved by You (loved by You). You were here before me. You were waiting on me. And you said You'd keep me never would You leave me. I was made to love(I was made to love). And be loved by You  (I'm Loved by You)</segment7>
		<segment8>Na na na na. Na na na na na. Na na na na. Na na na na na</segment8>
		<segment9>Anything, I would give up for You (Na na na na na). Everything, I'd give it all away (Na na na na na). Anything, I would give up for You (Na na na na na). Everything, I'd give it, I'd give it all away, oh yeah </segment9>
		<segment10>Cuz I was made to love You (I was made to love You). Yeah I was made to love You (I was made to find You). Cuz I was made to love You (I was made to adore You, made just for you)(Na na na na na). I was made to love You (I was made to adore You, made just for you). Cuz I was made to love You (I was made to adore You, made just for you)(Na na na na na). I was made to love You (I was made to adore You). Yeah I'm loved by You</segment10>
		<segment11>Laaaaaaaa, Laaaa, Laaaa. Yeah I'm loved by You (Na na na na na). Laaaaaaaa, Laaaa, Laaaa. Yeah I'm loved by You (Na na na na)</segment11>
		<segment12>Laaaaaaaa, Laaaa, Laaaa. Na na na na na. Laaaaaaaa, Laaaa, Laaaa. Na na na na na.     </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
