<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Man Of His Word </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>In the final days of summer, 1944, with just a preacher and a witness and a humble band of gold, They set out to find the future, not a penny to their name. Still with all the unknown danger, she knew her heart was safe, cause.</segment1>
		<segment2>He was a rock. He was the one that she ran to. And when he said the words &quot;Forever&quot;. She knew that it was true</segment2>
		<segment3>He wasn't a saint. But he was saint enough for her. He was a man, A man of his word.</segment3>
		<segment4>In the final days of summer, 1964, found a family undivided, divided on the war. Turning son against his elder, debating wrong and right, He was the image of his father, though they would not see eye to eye, still..</segment4>
		<segment5>He was a rock. He was the one the boy ran to. Cause' when he said the word &quot;I Love You&quot;. He knew that it was true</segment5>
		<segment6>And even in the worst of storms. There was an anchor in his world. He was a man, A man of his word.</segment6>
		<segment7>Clutching a strong belief in the bible, through all the sweetness in his life, and the bitterness of war, He knew what God had made him for..</segment7>
		<segment8>In the final days of summer, 1994, surrounded by his family and the presence of the Lord. He set out to find his future, the one he'd always known, He didn't want to leave his family, but he knew deep in his soul, The lord had called him home.. cause..</segment8>
		<segment9>He was the rock. He was the one the man ran to. And when he said the words &quot;forever&quot;. He knew that it was true</segment9>
		<segment10>He wasn't a saint. he is the one the saints bow to. Receiving a man, A man of his word..</segment10>
		<segment11>He was the one that I ran to. Cause when he says the word &quot;forever&quot;. I know his word is true</segment11>
		<segment12>He isn't a saint. He is the one the saints bow to. Come to teh man. The man of his word.    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
