<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Marathons </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Imagine the silence racing the timeless. Holding defences. Guiding the blind to exit the lights. Your following this but. We have the push it comes from the ocean. To follow the darkness. Suffer the most and surface the motion. Now do you understand</segment1>
		<segment2>We are sailing past your lies. Moving right across your eyes. We are sailing past these lies</segment2>
		<segment3>This is the true direction, This is where we set sail. The secret's coming out, No use in your resistance. This the way back home. We are the lost then found</segment3>
		<segment4>We are the ones called jaded and young. But we have direction. Shadows have come and in them we run. A quiet infection. It started with this the place of the fearless. Taking the dark and. We know the blood that. Spills like a flood. Now do you understand</segment4>
		<segment5>We are sailing past your lies. Moving right across your eyes. We are sailing past these lies</segment5>
		<segment6>This is the true direction, This is where we set sail. The secret's coming out, No use in your resistance. This the way back home. We are the lost then found</segment6>
		<segment7>Imagine the silence racing the timeless. We are the ones called. Holding defences. Guiding the blind to exit the lights. Your shadows have come. Following this but. We have the push that comes from the ocean. It started with this. To follow the darkness. Suffer the most and surface the motion. Now do you understand?</segment7>
		<segment8>This is the true direction, This is where we set sail. The secret's coming out, No use in your resistance. This the way back home. We are the lost then found</segment8>
		<segment9>This is the true direction. This is why we set sail. The secrets coming out</segment9>
		<segment10>We are sailing past your lies. We are sailing past these lies. Moving right across your eyes. We are sailing past these lies    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
