<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Me &amp; Becky </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Becky has a house on Abundant Live Boulevard. A good name, good family, and butterflies in here yard. Becky loves Jesus and really wants to make Him proud. She tears up in church and she sings her harmonies loud. She's got a Bible by the bed, a prayer journal, and a fish on her car. She makes sure to bow her head and give thanks in every restaurant. But is that enough?</segment1>
		<segment2>C'mon Becky, let's go for a ride. If I'm driving too fast then I apologize. But there's a world out there that we left behind. Full of souls as important as yours and mine. Looks like a reckless road, and a sacrifice. And I'm crazy scared it may cost our lives. But then I remember Jesus died. So c'mon Becky. Let's go for a ride</segment2>
		<segment3>I'm rolling up to Becky's house on my Sunday drive. I have to laugh to myself 'cause it looks exactly like mine. I smile and wave at all the happy people strolling by. We've got the same walk, same talk, and the same sparkle in our eyes. 'Cause we're thankful for the blessings, but maybe we could lay 'em aside. I get a feeling we might be missin' the time of our lives. So hop in and hold on tight</segment3>
		<segment4>C'mon Becky, let's go for a ride. If I'm driving too fast then I apologize. But there's a world out there that we left behind. Full of souls as important as yours and mine. Looks like a reckless road, and a sacrifice. And I'm crazy scared it may cost our lives. But then I remember Jesus died. So c'mon Becky. Let's go for a ride</segment4>
		<segment5>'Cause we're thankful for the blessings, but maybe we could lay 'em aside?. I get a feeling we might be heading for the time of our lives</segment5>
		<segment6>So hop in and hold on tight. C'mon Becky, let's go for a ride. If I'm driving too fast then I apologize. But there's a world out there that we left behind. Full of souls as important as yours and mine. Looks like a reckless road, and a sacrifice. And I'm crazy scared it may cost our lives. But then I remember Jesus died. So c'mon Becky. Let's go for a ride    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
