<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Meshach </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Hey, there's three real famous guys in the Bible you know. And the in-between guy's name is Meeeee-shach!. Meshach, yeah, yeah</segment1>
		<segment2>I read about them in Daniel one day. Look in chapter 1:7 babe. And then you can go get their names. They got treated harsh by the king of the world (go get their names). When they didn't bow down to his gold statue (go get their names). They got in a crisis and just about perished from burnin' up. Hey, king, your joke's not funny</segment2>
		<segment3>Well-a Meshach was an Israelite faced with. Mean King Neb'chadnezzar. Meshach, baby -- ah, Meshach, baby. Meshach, baby, Shadrach, Meshach, baby, Shadrach. Ah, babe, Abednego's last</segment3>
		<segment4>Simon says, kneel and pray fools. You must do as the law says!. Well, sittin' way back in the middle of a field. There's a 90-foot statue; ya gotta pray to that. Glitter on the statue didn't make the guys pray. Even if they got scorched, they would trust in Yahweh</segment4>
		<segment5>Well-a Meshach was an Israelite faced with. Mean King Neb'chadnezzar. Meshach, baby -- Meshach, baby. Meshach -- Neb'chadnezzar's mad. Meshach -- no scaredy cat</segment5>
		<segment6>Huffin' and hissin' guess he wasn't bluffin'. Nebuchadnezzar shoved 'em in one of the hottest ovens. But hold on kiddies. 'Cause everybody's movin' around and around and around and around. Nebby got confused and said, &quot;I thought we threw them in with. Ropes tied 'em up -- now guys how'd they get out?. There's four bodies movin' -- there's another dude in there and. Come here, Meshach -- we want you to come back!&quot;</segment6>
		<segment7>Often a crisis looks as big as a whale and you're about to get nailed. But God isn't far, He sees you now buddy. So come on and pray -- you're cool, stop running</segment7>
		<segment8>Well-a Meshach was an Israelite faced with. Mean King Neb'chadnezzar. Meshach, baby -- ah, Meshach, baby. Meshach, baby, Shadrach, Meshach, baby, Shadrach. Ah, babe, Abednego's last</segment8>
		<segment9>Wait, wait, wait on the Lord, baby! Talk a little louder soldier. Wait, wait, wait on the Lord, baby! I can't hear you!. Wait, wait! On the Lord, baby! Wait, wait! On the Lord!. Wait, wait! On the Lord, baby! Batman!. Girls, what?!! Same tune.. trust me. Meshach, baby, Shadrach (Ah, baby, trustworthy chaps, yeah). Meshach, baby, Shadrach (Ah, baby, trustworthy chaps). (Hope you learned a lesson standin' in the oven with a-Meshach)    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
