<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Miaminions </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Oh please, please, oh please. I'm begging on my knees. for a coin in the cup. I got a fatal disease. Could you help me get back on my feet?. Why don't you give me something you don't need?</segment1>
		<segment2>Oh girl, I won't hassle you long. But if you show me some love. I'm gonna sing you a song. I know the streetlights circle my home. I'm not a king of the world. But I'm a king of the bones</segment2>
		<segment3>And I'm falling asleep. To escape this dream</segment3>
		<segment4>Well they call me crazy. They say I'm alone. I'm not a king of the world. But I'm a king in the streets. I'm gonna rattle your bones. Don't call me lazy. Cause I'm a dangerous man. I'm not a king of the world. But I'm a king in the streets. I guess I'm good as dead</segment4>
		<segment5>I am the vermin's seed. I am the dirty thief. I've got the gutters key. You're all embarrassed of me. I've got blood on my shoes from another man. I killed while he was sleeping. please don't tell the feds. There's no mercy in their treatment</segment5>
		<segment6>Mercy, mercy, mercy. We take the pills. Take the pills. Mercy, mercy, mercy. It's twice the thrill</segment6>
		<segment7>And I'm falling asleep. To escape this dream</segment7>
		<segment8>They call me crazy. They say I'm alone. I'm not a king of the world. But I'm a king in the streets. I'm gonna rattle your bones. Don't call me lazy. Cause I'm a dangerous man. I'm not a king of the world. But I'm a king in the streets. I guess I'm good as dead</segment8>
		<segment9>Mercy, mercy, mercy. We take the pills. Take the pills. Mercy, mercy, mercy. Lean back and take the pills. Mercy, mercy, mercy. We take the pills. Take the pills. Mercy, mercy, mercy. Lean back and take the pills</segment9>
		<segment10>And I'm falling asleep. To escape this dream</segment10>
		<segment11>They call me crazy. They say I'm alone. I'm not a king of the world. But I'm a king in the streets. I'm gonna rattle your bones. Don't call me lazy. Cause I'm a dangerous man. I'm not a king of the world. But I'm a king in the streets. I guess I'm good as dead.     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
