<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Mind Your Head </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Verse 1: You wanna be in the headline. Your name in black and white. You wanna go for the big time. Can't shake the feeling. You wanna walk in the limelight. And take the road by storm. You wanna reach for the highlight. And be the new thing </segment1>
		<segment2>Pre-chorus 1: I told you from the start. There's nothing wrong with what you said. But deep inside my heart. I wanna tell you </segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus: Mind your head. Get out of bed. Don't realize your own demise. You gotta redefine your state of mind. So take aspirin. The word has said you gotta mind you head </segment3>
		<segment4>Verse 2: You wanna be with the best of ???. Somebody nobody heard of. Who made the big time. You wanna see what ya can do. When running side by side. You wanna know will ya get through. And make the headline </segment4>
		<segment5>. Pre-chorus 2: But if you want to learn. Then everything will be alright. Take on what's in the word. Don't let it feed you </segment5>
		<segment6>Chorus: Mind your head. Get out of bed. Don't realize your own demise. You gotta redefine. Your state of mind. So take aspirin. The word has said. You gotta mind you head. Get out of bed. Don't realize your own demise. You gotta re-define. Your state of mind. So take aspirin. The word has said. You gotta mind your head </segment6>
		<segment7>You gotta mind your head </segment7>
		<segment8>Bridge: I try to tell you how it is. But you still disagree. When will you ever see. How faithfullness should be </segment8>
		<segment9>Mind your head, realize </segment9>
		<segment10>Be in the headline. Go for the big time. Walk in the limelight </segment10>
		<segment11>Be in the headline. Go for the big time. Walk In the limelight </segment11>
		<segment12>Chorus: Mind your head. Get out of bed. Don't realize your own demise. You gotta redefine. Your state of mind. So take aspirin. The word has said. You gotta mind you head. Get out of bed. Don't realize your own demise. You gotta re-define. Your state of mind. So take aspirin. The word has said. You gotta mind your head. You gotta mind, you gotta mind, you gotta mind your head    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
