<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Monkey Scheme </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Here they come -- talkin' down at me -- I get the funniest looks cause -- I said I don't believe. They say we were monkeys -- They think they're sayin' something profound. But where's their missing link at? There weren't any bodies found. They built a man from a hog's tooth -- They called a lie the truth. And any time they get busted -- They sell you something new. They say we were monkeys -- I think that they've been monkeyin' around. Cause they're too busy changin' their books and their studies 'round. They're just tryin' to defend it -- they got a lot to re-explain. Where they've done excavation -- they keep uncoverin' mistakes. Any time -- or anywhere -- Just look over the boulders -- You'll see that man's been there. They say we were monkeys -- I think their heads are stuck in the ground. Cause they're too busy diggin' and putting the Bible down. SPOKEN: Java Man was the skull of a gibbon; Nebraska Man was the tooth of a pig and. The Piltdown Man was a lowdown sham; They built that man from an organutan. Ramapithicus wasn't complete; He's a fragment of jaw and a couple of teeth. Addition skeletons show us today that he isn't our relative -- only an ape. Australapithicus alias Lucy, The fossil of this is just vague and confusing. The wonderful knee bone they're proud to possess was 200 feet deeper -- a mile from the rest. Neanderthal Man was prob'ly deficient in Vitamin D or it might've been rickets. But he had religion and musical instruments, fire and tools and from you he's no different. They say we were monkeys but people came from dust in the ground. But they're too busy thinkin to look into what we've found. They're just kinda pretending, but I know why they seem afraid. If we come from creation, you need Gods son to be saved. They say we were monkeys but there was no evidence found. Still you'd better get ready -- They'll make it up anyhow.     </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
