<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Moonlight </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>So this is real, the window seal. I cannot heal, all the secrets are here now. All I've known, my cover's blown, the age's shown. You know they all fake they're home. Neon lights, the fade of light, the fear of heights</segment1>
		<segment2>. All alone, there's whispers of defences gone. All alone, there's whispers of defences gone</segment2>
		<segment3>This is the way this is the motion. Let go now. this is the breath this is the ocean. Let go now. this is the way this is the motion. Let go now. This is the breath this is the ocean. Let go now</segment3>
		<segment4>(Let go now)</segment4>
		<segment5>And so it's made the frozen sade has turned my gaze. The effect is in motion. Strength is gone, my breath is on, the last is drawn. You know that it will soon be gone. Still I'll wait in today and complicate. And all time is just frozen. I see through was never you. And what you said the hope is where His hand has bled. The complex and effects start. Breaking tide to beach the white and early night. And the water only from His side</segment5>
		<segment6>All in love, there's whispers of defence is gone. All in love, there's whispers of defence is gone</segment6>
		<segment7>This is the way this is the motion. Let go now. this is the breathe this is the ocean. Let go now. this is the way this is the motion. Let go now. This is the breathe this is the ocean. Let go now</segment7>
		<segment8>(Let go now)</segment8>
		<segment9>Just, just let go. Just, just let go. Just, just let go. Just, just let go</segment9>
		<segment10>This is the way this is the motion. Let go now. this is the breathe this is the ocean. Let go now. this is the way this is the motion. Let go now. This is the breathe this is the ocean. Let go now</segment10>
		<segment11>(Let go now)</segment11>
		<segment12>    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
