<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>My Boyfriend </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Ladies!. Let me hear you say.. B-o-y-f-r-i-e-n-d x2. Talkin' to my girl the other day. She told me how she's tired of dealin' with all his games. She went through his phone. And found that somethin's wrong. Like unknown names and numbers and pictures all in his phone. I said: &quot;Is that where you're supposed to be?&quot;. Cause' in you heart there's no peace. (Does he make you complete?). Alot of emptiness inside. &quot;Have you ever gave God a chance?&quot;. (Jesus can't be my boyfriend!) To be your man.. Don't miss out cause I didn't.</segment1>
		<segment2>He's my boyfriend. My best friend. My boo. He is(My everything)</segment2>
		<segment3>. He's my boyfriend. My best friend. My boo. Have you tried..(My everything)</segment3>
		<segment4>You seem to have a lot of problems. You're always hurting and fighting. Standin' strong and faithful. Afraid of being alone. But you can't love nobody else until you learn what true love is..</segment4>
		<segment5>&quot;Is that where you're supposed to be?&quot;. Cause' in you heart there's no peace. (Does he make you complete?). A lot of emptiness inside. &quot;Have you ever gave God a chance?&quot;. (As if you're lovin' someone else.) To be your man.. Don't miss out cause I didn't.</segment5>
		<segment6>He's my boyfriend. My bestfriend. My boo. He is(My everything)</segment6>
		<segment7>He's my boyfriend. My bestfriend. My boo. Have you tried..(My everything)</segment7>
		<segment8>Take sometime to breathe.. Just give your self somethime to breathe. No, I'm not sayin' be single. He is my boy friend.</segment8>
		<segment9>He's my boyfriend. My bestfriend. My boo. My everything</segment9>
		<segment10>And His name is Jesus. My savior, my redeemer, my everything.     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
