<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>My God </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Buddah was a fat man, so what!. Mohammed thought he had a plan, I guess not!. A hindu god is an, old cow!. You could be a god if ya, knew how!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. But He lives! </segment1>
		<segment2>My God is the only God. He's the only God that lives. He loves, He cares, He makes, He shares. And eternal life he gives. He took the pain and shook the chains. And rattled all of Hell. Now you may think I'm crazy. But only time will tell. Yo! </segment2>
		<segment3>Buddah was a fat man, so what!. Mohammed thought he had a plan, I guess not!. A hindu god is an, old cow!. You could be a god if ya, knew how!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. But He lives! </segment3>
		<segment4>There's a man over there standing on the street. He says I'm a god! but I think he's a freak. Many different man aren't just what they claim. A moonie a morman a man from Mars. A little off track but have nice cars </segment4>
		<segment5>Buddah was a fat man, so what!. Mohammed thought he had a plan, I guess not!. A hindu god is an, old cow!. You could be a god if ya, knew how!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. But He lives! </segment5>
		<segment6>My precious Jesus died upon the cross. My precious Jesus died to save the lost. But He live yes He lives my Jesus Lives. He walks He talks He loves He rocks. My Jesus lives </segment6>
		<segment7>Buddah was a fat man, so what!. Mohammed thought he had a plan, I guess not!. A hindu god is an, old cow!. You could be a god if ya, knew how!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. But He lives! </segment7>
		<segment8>There's one important thing that you should know. Jesus Christ paid the price. We all think it's nice. Spread His arms and died for man. But we're not doing all we can. We need to go to our work and our school. And tell all the people that Hey! God rules! </segment8>
		<segment9>Buddah was a fat man, so what!. Mohammed thought he had a plan, I guess not!. A hindu god is an, old cow!. You could be a god if ya, knew how!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. My God died on the cross!. But He lives!     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
