<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>My Own Little World </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>In my own little world it hardly ever rains. Ive never gone hungry, always felt safe. I got some money in my pocket, shoes on my feet. In my own little world. Population me </segment1>
		<segment2>I try to stay awake through Sunday morning church. I throw a twenty in the plate but I never give til it hurts. and I turn off the news when I dont like what I see. its easy to do when its. population me </segment2>
		<segment3>What if theres a bigger picture. what if Im missing out. What if theres a greater purpose. I could be living right now. outside my own little world, ooo </segment3>
		<segment4>. Stopped at the red light, looked out my window. I saw a cardboard sign said Help this homeless widow. Just above that sign was the face of a human. I thought to myself, God, what have I been doing?. So I rolled down the window and I looked her in the eye. Oh how many times have I just passed her by. I gave her some money then I drove on through. in my own little world theres. Population two, woah </segment4>
		<segment5>What if theres a bigger picture. what if Im missing out. What if theres a greater purpose. I could be living right now. outside my own little world, ooo. my own little world, ooo </segment5>
		<segment6>Wo-a-oh x3. yeah-ah </segment6>
		<segment7>Father break my heart for what breaks Yours. give me open hands and open doors. put Your light in my eyes and let me see. that my own little world is not about me </segment7>
		<segment8>What if theres a bigger picture. what if Im missing out. What if theres a greater purpose. I could be living right now </segment8>
		<segment9>I don't wanna miss what matters. I wanna be reachin' out. Show me the greater purpose. So I can start livin' right now. outside my own little world, (yeah)ooo. my own little world, (yeah),yeah, yeah. my own little world, ooo    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
