<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Never Wave My Flag </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Seems like I should run away. cause life has hitten me in the face. Hey, hey, but I'm here. And I'll never surrender to fear. We're treating . defeated no way. cause I can't, I can't. cause I can see it, I'm getting closer. The hardest part of this is almost over. And now I'm stronger, I'm a fighter. And only victory can satisfy his hunger.</segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus: I'll never wave my flag, never wave my. I'll never wave my flag, never wave my. I'll never wave my flag, never wave my. I'll never wave my flag, never wave my. Oh ..I'll be more then on. I'll be more then on, I keep warning. Never wave my flag.</segment2>
		<segment3>Seems like I should run away. cause life has hitten me in the face. My face, my face. But I'm so focused, I'm so driven. I gotta make the best out of this life for living. And be your . if I surrender, I won't surrender. I can't surrender.</segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus: I'll never wave my flag, never wave my</segment4>
		<segment5>I'll never wave my flag, never wave my. I'll never wave my flag, never wave my. I'll never wave my flag, never wave my. Oh ..I'll be more then on. I'll be more then on, I keep warning. Never wave my flag.</segment5>
		<segment6>I realize this is the day. cause I no longer feel afraid. I keep fight though the pain. cause I know something is gonna change. I see the haters standing around. So I know I gotta make account. You're ready for war, I'm stand in the ground. No matter the score, I'll never back down.</segment6>
		<segment7>I'll never wave my. I'll never wave. I'll never wave, wave, wave</segment7>
		<segment8>I'll keep holding on, I'll keep holding on, I'll keep holding on, I'll keep holding on, Never wave my flag, no!</segment8>
		<segment9>Seems like I should run away. cause life has hitten me in the face. Not today, not today.    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
