<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Never Take Friendship Personal </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>There's a hatchet got a knife. When I awoke there was nothing real in this life. But dreams are so intoxicating, (intoxicating). When you're doing this alone. Gun, rope, brick on the way. But words have no meaning when its you that says. I really do care, no baby I, I really do care!</segment1>
		<segment2>Innocence gone, never take friendship personal. If you can't hold yourself together. Why should I hold you now?. Innocence gone, never take friendship personal. If you can't hold yourself together. Why should I hold you now?</segment2>
		<segment3>Once a skeptic, now the critic. And you think that you finally found a place of your own. Amongst the cold and timid souls. Where only failure knows your name</segment3>
		<segment4>Look around for the closest to blame. But look no further than the hands beneath your arms. and now your 6 feet down, buried with, with your passing fame. And fame fame fame fame.</segment4>
		<segment5>Innocence gone, never take friendship personal. If you can't hold yourself together. Why should I hold you now?. Innocence gone, never take friendship personal. If you can't hold yourself together. Why should I hold you now?</segment5>
		<segment6>Oh oh oh you lie. Tell me something more than what you've tried to hide. If you can't find your self, then how can I expect to find you. Oh oh oh you cry. Tell me something more than what you tried. The greatest tragedy is not your death. But a life without reason, that your life had no purpose. (Life has no purpose!)</segment6>
		<segment7>Innocence gone, never take friendship personal. If you can't hold yourself together. Why should I hold you now?. Innocence gone, never take friendship personal. If you can't hold yourself together. Why should I hold you now?</segment7>
		<segment8>Innocence gone, never take friendship personal. If you can't hold yourself together. Why should I hold you now?    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
