<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Never Alone (Nunca Solo) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>In the middle of a crowded room alone. Surrounded by familiar faces of. All these strangers I know. Wonder how I got so far from home. Just wishin' I could find my way back to. The love and the life I let go </segment1>
		<segment2>There's so many places we've all been. When we'd give anything for a true friend. But I've come to know His arms are open. Waiting to hold me </segment2>
		<segment3>I'm so alive. (Vuelvo a vivir, todo mi ser, vuelve a sentir). For the first time in my life. There's a passion inside me. Lord, by Your side. (Mi corazon, hoy tiene amor sin condicion). My heart has found a home. Now I'm never alone </segment3>
		<segment4>Lying awake tonight. The noise of the day still echoes on. In the silence I hear. I open my heart and I close my eyes. I feel the peace come back to me. And I know He is near </segment4>
		<segment5>There's so many things that we can't see. We wonder and worry what will be. But I've come to know His heart is open. Wanting to show me </segment5>
		<segment6>I'm so alive. (Vuelvo a vivir, todo mi ser, vuelve a sentir). For the first time in my life. There's a passion inside me. Lord, by Your side. (Mi corazon, hoy tiene amor sin condicion). My heart has found a home. Now I'm never alone </segment6>
		<segment7>Por primera vez ya no me siento solo, With You in my heart I can fly. Above the darkness of a long and lonely night. I'm gonna breathe the air that brings me to life. I'll find any way to be near You. My one and only light </segment7>
		<segment8>Vuelvo a vivir. (Vuelvo a vivir, todo mi ser, vuelve a sentir). Por primera vez en mi. Siento una pasion surgir y. Mi corazon. (Mi corazon, hoy tiene amor sin condicion). Ha encontrado un nuevo hogar. And I'm never, never alone </segment8>
		<segment9>I'm so alive, You're by my side. For the first time in my life. There's a passion inside me. I'm not alone, no love has shown, I'm now my own. My heart has found a home. Now I'm never alone. Never alone.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
