<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>New Day </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Have you ever doubted what you're made of?. Have you ever fed your fear?. Have you ever seemed disconnected?. Has your laughter ever turned to tears?</segment1>
		<segment2>It's alright, it's alright. You're not the only one</segment2>
		<segment3>Have you ever made a silly faux pas?. Or kissed another dream goodbye?. Have you ever found out when time ran out. You needed one more try?. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah</segment3>
		<segment4>CHORUS. Oh yeah, it's OK, God brings in a brand new day. Another chance, another choice. Another hope, another possibility. All right, OK, no more time for yesterday. Open your eyes and you'll find. It's a new day, it's a brand new day</segment4>
		<segment5>So wake up, wake up from your bad dream. Ooo, you gotta clear your head. There is opportunity knocking. When you're hanging by a thread</segment5>
		<segment6>It's alright, a new sun's gonna rise!. Oh yeah, come on!</segment6>
		<segment7>CHORUS</segment7>
		<segment8>No more fear, it's a new day. No more worry, it's a new day. No more doubt, it's a new day. Just believe it, it's a new day!</segment8>
		<segment9>It doesn't matter where your life has been. Just trust in Him. And let a new day begin, come on!</segment9>
		<segment10>CHORUS</segment10>
		<segment11>Alright, OK. Don't you worry bout yesterday. It doesn't matter what you've done wrong. It's gone, gone, gone, gone, gone. Everything's gonna be alright. Another chance, another try. Open your eyes cause the sun is about to shine. Open your eyes and you'll find..</segment11>
		<segment12>It's a new day, it's a new day. It's a new day, come on, come on. It's a new day, it's a new day. It's a new day, come on, come on</segment12>
		<segment13>It's a new day, come on!    </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
