<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Nice Piece Of Art </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I've tried not to let anyone in until now. I guess conversations never allow. and I've been feeling like I'm on some sort of marry-go-round. And I know, I know, yeah I know, I know and. I've tried not to let anyone in until now. It took time for me to figure it out. and when I feel like I'm complacent with my head in the clouds. And I know, I know, yeah I know, I know. and every time I wonder what's real you make me feel.. </segment1>
		<segment2>You make me feel like a ? in this sweater. and I'm caught in that weather. and my ? weighing down. You make me feel like a complete work of art. when I'm just falling apart. A really nice piece of art </segment2>
		<segment3>Dear God, (art, art, art..). I hope you hear me (art, art, art..) </segment3>
		<segment4>And I've tried not to let anyone in until now. Misunderstandings are an easy way out. And I've been feeling all this pressure just to figure it out. And I know, don't know, yeah I know, don't know and. I know if I can stay strong I can make it. and try harder when I just can't take it (can't take it). And when everything around me feels so broken and jaded (broken and jaded). And I know, I know, yeah I know, I know. and every time I wonder what's real you make me feel.. </segment4>
		<segment5>You make me feel like a ? in this sweater. and I'm caught in that weather. and my ? weighing down. You make me feel like a complete work of art. when I'm just falling apart. A really nice piece of art </segment5>
		<segment6>(art, art, art..). It's kinda ?, but it's picking up slowly. I don't know, but I can if you show me. I guess sometimes it takes more than just fake conversations to feel like I know that. It's kinda hard when I'm planning for something. to get across this whole without jumping. I guess sometimes it takes more than just false information to figure out who we are </segment6>
		<segment7>You make me feel like a ? in this sweater. and I'm caught in that weather. and my ? weighing down. You make me feel like a complete work of art. when I'm just falling apart. A really nice piece of art.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
