<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Not Done Yet </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Superchick in the house tonight! </segment1>
		<segment2>It's been one of those days for a lot of days now, I need a day where the world can take care of itself. This isn't what I wanted, How I thought my life would turn out, And I wonder if it's like this from here on out. </segment2>
		<segment3>Sometimes life gets you, but we go on. Sometimes life gets you, we're still going on. </segment3>
		<segment4>We're not done yet, not going quietly into the night, Not me and my friends. We're not done yet, Don't take it too seriously, It's just life. We'll win in the end. </segment4>
		<segment5>And we walk on and on and on and on. And we walk on and on and on. </segment5>
		<segment6>It's been one of those days for too many days now, I did a thing that I didn't want to do again. I fell down in the place where I always fall down. And I want to give up and let it be, what a friend. </segment6>
		<segment7>Sometimes life gets you, be we go on. Sometimes life gets you, we're still going on. </segment7>
		<segment8>We're not done yet, Not going quietly into the night, Not me and my friends. We're not done yet, Don't take it too seriously, It's just life. We'll win in the end. </segment8>
		<segment9>And we walk on and on and on and on. And we walk on and on and on. </segment9>
		<segment10>It's been one of those days, but I don't care now, It was only a day, and tomorrow's ahead. I got this far, and I know that I can ride this one out, Though I want to lay down, but I won't quit yet. </segment10>
		<segment11>Sometimes life gets you, but we go on. Sometimes life gets you, we're still going on. </segment11>
		<segment12>We're not done yet, Not going quietly into the night, Not me and my friends. We're not done yet, Don't take it too seriously, It's just life. We'll win in the end. </segment12>
		<segment13>And we walk on and on and on. And we walk on and on and on. </segment13>
		<segment14>3x:We're not done yet, Not going quietly into the night, Not me and my friends. We're not done yet, Don't take it too seriously, It's just life. We'll win in the end. </segment14>
		<segment15>And we walk on and on and on and on. And we walk on and on and on.    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
