<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>No Telling Why </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Windows down radio blaring. Your hair down in your eyes and. You dance like no ones watching at all. Like a child</segment1>
		<segment2>Head back laughing, crying. The pedal down as we keep driving. You never ask are we there yet. Like a child</segment2>
		<segment3>And we drive. We drive on into the night. Yea we drive. Dont think twice not to say goodbye</segment3>
		<segment4>Your hands out, playing with the wind. As its kissin all your fingertips. And you smell the rain. As it starts pouring in (like we care)</segment4>
		<segment5>The clock reads 2 am. Its been so far. But we just started this. No telling where, why, or how far its been (like we care)</segment5>
		<segment6>We just drive. We drive on into the night. Yea we drive. Dont think twice not to say goodbye</segment6>
		<segment7>Yea we drive. We drive on into the night. Yea we drive. To find the morning light</segment7>
		<segment8>Come with me. Leave your hate, your fears. Don't look back. Leave the past behind</segment8>
		<segment9>Come with me. Bring your heart, your dreams. Don't look back. We don't need to hide</segment9>
		<segment10>In the morning light..</segment10>
		<segment11>In the morning light. Sit back, enjoy the ride</segment11>
		<segment12>In the morning light. Look up, hold on tight (hold on tight)</segment12>
		<segment13>Come with me. Leave your hate, your fears. Don't look back. Leave the past behind you</segment13>
		<segment14>Come with me. Bring your heart, your dreams. Don't look back. We don't need to hide</segment14>
		<segment15>Come with me. Leave your hate, your fears. Don't look back. Leave the past behind</segment15>
		<segment16>Come with me. Bring your heart, your dreams. Don't look back. We don't need to hide</segment16>
		<segment17>We dont need to hide..     </segment17>
	</english>
</song>
