<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Not Ready To Die </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>You've got a lot of nerve and I've got a lot of fingers to point. While you were busy building knowledge I was already right. I know a voice like yours is not a weapon at all. And even mine is not a chisel for a thickened skull. So you can chant your anthems to the deaf. And we can sit here and cry until there's nothing left. Or we can take our voices with our hands. Make like knives and make demands. We'll take our voices - with our hands. Make like knives - we'll make demands </segment1>
		<segment2>I'm burning bridges for the last time </segment2>
		<segment3>I'm breaking habits for the first time </segment3>
		<segment4>I saw my future today, it said I'm going away. But I still haven't sung the last line. On my way down.. I'm not ready to lay, not ready to fade. I'm not ready to die. And everyday of my life I can feel it getting harder to breathe. With every minute ticking by I'm getting ready to leave. I know a life like mine is not a reason to fret. But I've been busy making scars that you will never forget. If only thirty three years can save my life. I've had twenty three more to make things right. So when I'm taken to the sky and you're still here. You can clear your mind and dry your tears. When I'm taken home - and you're still here. Just clear your mind - dry your tears. I'm burning bridges for the last time. I'm breaking habits for the first time. I saw my future today, it said I'm going away. But I still haven't sung the last line. On my way down.. I'm not ready to lay, not ready to fade. I'm not ready to die. When I'm taken home - and you're still here. Just clear your mind - dry your tears. We'll take our voices - with our hands. Make like knives - we'll make demands. I'm not ready to lay, not ready to fade. I'm not ready to die     </segment4>
	</english>
</song>
