<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Now I Sing </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>can u just give me a second please. I would like to give my testimony. how the Lord has met my every need. how he saved me, made he holy. if you wanna know the reason why. I gave it all this lifes's no longer mine. How He made a way kept me alive, well listen close as I testify. you don't know like I know (no no). you can't tell it like I can tell it. everything the Lord has done for me so (yea yea yea). that you understand I'm just gonna say it. (What manner of love is this is that the father gives to us). how he saved my soul, I want the world to know</segment1>
		<segment2>So now I sing, I just want to sing his praise. Loving kindness everyday, faithfulness that comes my way. So now I sing, I'm gonna clap my hands. Please excuse me if I start to dance. Cause His love is true, His mercies new, He's been so good to me </segment2>
		<segment3>He didn't have to do it but I'm glad He did, (im so glad). Saved me from my sin. That old life is gone and new life lives within. (Of all the things that I could write a song). I knew I couldn't go wrong, If I sang of His goodness all day long. You don't know like I know, you can't tell it like I can tell it. Everything the Lord has done for me so, That you understand I'm just gone say it. (I cannot live my life without Him) I make no excuse. If I get a little crazy in Him I live and move </segment3>
		<segment4>So now I sing, just want to sing his praise. Loving kindness everyday, faithfulness that comes my way. So now I sing, I'm gonna clap my hands. Please excuse me if I start to dance. Cause His love is true, His mercies new, He's been so good to me </segment4>
		<segment5>So clap your hands this evening, come on y'all I said it's alright. move a little this evening, come on y'all I said it's alright. Who the son sets free, you know is free indeed. You're free you've got the need to be praisin </segment5>
		<segment6>So now I sing, just want to sing his praise. Loving kindness everyday, faithfulness that comes my way. So now I sing, I'm gonna clap my hands. Please excuse me if I start to dance. Cause His love is true, His mercies new, He's been so good to me </segment6>
		<segment7>So now I sing, just want to sing his praise. Loving kindness everyday, faithfulness that comes my way. So now I sing, I'm gonna clap my hands. Please excuse me if I start to dance. Cause His love is true, His mercies new, He's been so good to me </segment7>
		<segment8>you don't know like I know. you can't tell it like I can tell it. you don't know like I know. you can't tell it like I can tell it </segment8>
		<segment9>(What manner of love is this is that the father gives to us) </segment9>
		<segment10>you don't know like I know. you can't tell it like I can tell it. you don't know like I know. you can't tell it like I can tell it.     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
