<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Oh, Bravo </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I couldn't see beyond the corner to the stage. From my place between the cowboy and the clown. Mommy dressed me up and left me with a kiss. For the talent show now beginning. The curtain coming down. Just enough to hear them say,</segment1>
		<segment2>Oh bravo. You're the best. There is no one else. Oh bravo. Our applause is not enough. Can you hear us yell out, yell out. On and on we go. Bravo</segment2>
		<segment3>One by one they came and left us all amazed. Everyone so elegant. It made me feel so plain. The clown so colorful. The ballerina danced and twirled. And I thought, &quot;Clearly they're all better than my little song!&quot;. And they deserve to hear the praise</segment3>
		<segment4>Oh bravo. You're the best. There is no one else. Oh bravo. Our applause is not enough. Can you hear us yell out, yell out. On and on we go. Bravo</segment4>
		<segment5>Running off the stage with bitter tears of shame. Close my eyes and try so hard to make it go away. I just want to go home and tell my teddy bear, &quot;I failed, I failed!&quot;. I turned around the corner just to hear my daddy say,</segment5>
		<segment6>Oh bravo. You're the best. You're my only one. Oh bravo. That will always be enough. Look at me. You're song was beautiful, beautiful. And even if nobody ever know. Bravo</segment6>
		<segment7>Oh bravo. You're the best. There is no one else. Oh bravo. Our applause is not enough. Can you hear us yell out, yell out. On and on we go. Bravo</segment7>
		<segment8>Oh bravo. You're the best. There is no one else. Oh bravo. Our applause is not enough. Can you hear us yell out, yell out. On and on we go. Bravo</segment8>
		<segment9>Oh bravo. You're the best. There is no one else. Oh bravo. Our applause is not enough. Can you hear us yell out, yell out. On and on we go. Bravo    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
