<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>One </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Grievances reached no words to be said. Barrier breached now come lay your head. And she's found a new way her hands letting go, hurting so</segment1>
		<segment2>You've too much to say your new words heard old, letting go. Down on your knees it's a long extra mile, letting go. Giving your faith just for a smile</segment2>
		<segment3>Finding some way to go crawling back again. She wonders why, boy didn't run. Remembering two who had something special then. Sometime, someday there'll be only one</segment3>
		<segment4>Passages preached, notions of warmth. Elasticity reached allegiance near torn. And she's flying away to new foreign lands, hurting so</segment4>
		<segment5>Your searching for faults on grounds that you stand, letting go. Without her the dream it ceases to be, letting go. Tomorrow you'll wake and maybe you'll see</segment5>
		<segment6>Finding some way to move along again. We wonder why, why ever you've gone?. Remembering two, who had something special then. What time today, there'll be only one</segment6>
		<segment7>One understanding, one thought that she left you. One more that takes it, one less that makes you whole. One understanding, one thought that she left you. One more that takes it, one less that makes you whole</segment7>
		<segment8>She's seeking the truth, the words that she left, ohh. Riddled by ask and all out of breath. Resounding the voice, reconciled song, letting go. Created the choice, will you stand strong?</segment8>
		<segment9>Finding the way, pushing along my friend. Seeing the worth in all that you've done. Remembering two who had something special then</segment9>
		<segment10>Sometime, today there'll be only. Looks like today, there'll be only. Now on your way, you'll only be one    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
