<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>One Less </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>There's a child. Been abandoned out on the street. Now she's waiting for someone to be her miracle</segment1>
		<segment2>There's a wife. Somewhere halfway around the world. Begging God for a litte girl she can call her own</segment2>
		<segment3>Well, worlds collide. And colors fade. And a man and wifre. Brought their little girl home today</segment3>
		<segment4>And there's one less. One less. One less broken heart in the world tonight. Yeah, there's one less. One less. There's one less broken heart in the world tonight</segment4>
		<segment5>We are called. To the widows and the orphans. But it's easy to ignore their silent crys. Oh, but every single time. Somebody reaches into the darkness. Makes a choice to help the helpless. They let mercy save a life</segment5>
		<segment6>And there's one less. One less. One less broken heart in the world tonight. Yeah, there's one less. One less. Yeah, there's one less broken heart in the world tonight</segment6>
		<segment7>Well the truth is we are all the orphans. But love has left the 99 just to find the one</segment7>
		<segment8>So let worlds collide. Colors fade. Let your life. Be the miracle today</segment8>
		<segment9>One less. One less. One less broken heart in the world tonight. Tonight I know there's one less. One less. One less broken heart in the world tonight</segment9>
		<segment10>One less child without a home. One less birthday gone forgotten. One more soul rising from the bottom</segment10>
		<segment11>One less night alone. One less child without a home. One less birthday gone forgotten. One more soul rising from the bottom</segment11>
		<segment12>One less. One less. One less broken heart in the world tonight    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
