<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>One Shot </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>All around the world. Every boy, every girl's got one shot. Believers let me hear you shout. Hey!. Hey!</segment1>
		<segment2>You could find me. Living in the city of DC. Found my freedom in the rhythm of the backbeat. God placed a love inside that I could not control. Beside me, had a brother saying I could sing like Nat King. But all I wanted was to do the rock thing. To roll through every town and spread His love around. Just a little while then I found</segment2>
		<segment3>All around the world. Every boy, every girl's got one shot. To prove what they're all about. I'm gonna sing about my God. And it doesn't matter what's hot. Believers let me hear you shout. We say there's one way. When push comes to shove. We're gonna sing of His love</segment3>
		<segment4>Things change. Just like the Twitter that you update. Or your Facebook status on your front page. But there's no comment you can leave to change my mind. Maybe you're a student at the college of the ivy. Or filling up a pop machine with Hi-C. Anywhere you might be. You can help the world see. What His love's about. Believers let me hear you shout</segment4>
		<segment5>All around the world. Every boy, every girl's got one shot. To prove what they're all about. I'm gonna sing about my God. And it doesn't matter what's hot. Believers let me hear you shout. We say there's one way. When push comes to shove. We're gonna sing of His love</segment5>
		<segment6>Are we scared to stand out from the crowd?. Make a difference in our own town?. If we stay silent with our voices now. The rocks will cry out. Believers let me hear you shout</segment6>
		<segment7>All around the world. Every boy, every girl's got one shot. To prove what they're all about. I'm gonna sing about my God. And it doesn't matter what's hot. Believers let me hear you shout. We say there's one way. When push comes to shove. We're gonna sing of His love</segment7>
		<segment8>All around the world. Every boy and girl. All around the world. Every boy and girl. All around the world..    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
