<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>One Way </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It's been one way, take a look and see. Up to Heaven, the Bible says it plainly. False faith and philosophy can't get ya to Heaven -- come back to Jesus. He's the way and the living truth. You realize that all those false gods couldn't help you. Yes indeed, He's forgiven me, and He can still get you saved if you say you're sorry. Holy cow they got you hoodwinked with the pagan god thing. I think you're lookin' at also rans. But some of this superstition though it might be called religion. Finds find you sizzlin' with the devil in the fryin' pan. It's not like the Bible says it one time. More like 300 times it says there's only one avenue. First C'rinthians chapter 8:6, the Bible says this. You try to tell me that it's not true. I think you're makin' a mistake -- I'd like to take and wake and shake ya. Like to tell you how to find yourself the way there. Cause Jesus showed us and we know where every soul is gonna go. Unless n' they confess Him as their Lord and Savior. I cannot help it if I think there's one way and you're mad. Tryin' hard not to sin but you're still bad. There's a time to die and after the funeral. Then you'll understand what I mean when it's too real. I have a tendency to stand behind John 14. John 14:6 could be my favorite Bible verse. Its been one way, take a look and see, Deuteronomy says it pretty plainly. 5:7 the passage reads: &quot;You shall have no other gods before me&quot;. (You can) read Exodus halfway through. You read that line in chapter 20 'cause it's there, too. Yes, indeed, chapter 20, verse 3. Now, it's written in two places for you, and you saw it. Check into China  the Chinese Christians. They havent done zip but they're chained up in prison. Cause they read their Bibles with the lights on or cause they prayed once. Or cause they spoke on their religion. In America it's more like getting dandruff, they see you stand up. They snicker when they see you passin' by. They'd cure us all of all our bad flaws -- They wanna make laws. But if they did they'd have us sterilized. They get upset at anyone who tries definin' God above. They're so alarmed they always try to start attacking. Their attitude is that you're rude and that no truth is absolute anyway, babe. So let them think the wrong thing. I cannot help it if I think there's one way into Heaven. Kinda hard to ignore Matthew chapter 7. I can find the line in Acts chapter 4:12. Cannot be saved by the name of someone else. I have First Timothy to verify my beliefs, there's quite a bit to read but 2:5's the verse. Its been one way, take a look and see. Drop your guard and your pride and say I'm sorry. Bible says what you have to do. It says you just confess that Christ is Lord -- He'll come in you. Believe that He's risen, too, you'll realize you're born again, I wouldn't tease you. Yes, indeed, we can all be saved. But there will still be too many who won't say they're sorry. And still Jesus waits till we say we're sorry. And still Jesus waits so please say you're sorry. At least God don't speak in code like Hammurabi     </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
