<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Our God </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Water You turned into wine. Open the eyes of the blind. Theres no one like You. None like You. Into the darkness You shine. Out of the ashes we rise. Theres no one like You. None like You</segment1>
		<segment2>CHORUS. Our God is greater, our God is stronger. God You are higher than any other. Our God is Healer, awesome in power. Our God, Our God </segment2>
		<segment3>Into the darkness you shining. Out of the ashes we Rise. Theres no One like You. None like You.</segment3>
		<segment4>Our God is greater, our God is stronger. God You are higher than any other. Our God is Healer, awesome in power. Our God, Our God. Our God is greater, our God is stronger. God You are higher than any other. Our God is Healer, awesome in power. Our God, Our God </segment4>
		<segment5>BRIDGE. And if Our God is for us, then who could ever stop us. And if our God is with us, then what can stand against?. And if Our God is for us, then who could ever stop us. And if our God is with us, then what can stand against?. What can stand against?</segment5>
		<segment6>Our God is greater, our God is stronger. God You are higher than any other. Our God is Healer, awesome in power. Our God, Our God. Our God is greater, our God is stronger. God You are higher than any other. Our God is Healer, awesome in power. Our God, Our God </segment6>
		<segment7>And if Our God is for us, then who could ever stop us. And if our God is with us, then what can stand against?. And if Our God is for us, then who can ever stop us. And if our God is with us, then what can stand against?. Then what can stand against?. Then what can stand against?</segment7>
		<segment8>Our God is greater, our God is stronger. God You are higher than any other. Our God is Healer, awesome in power. Our God, Our God. Our God is greater, our God is stronger. God You are higher than any other. Our God is Healer, awesome in power. Our God, Our God     </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
