<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Outcast </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Since I can remember. Guess I been a problem. Never had a filter. Never been the popular one. To sugar coat what I know is undeniable. I just can't hide it. I wear it like a letter</segment1>
		<segment2>Everywhere I go. Everyone is talking. I can feel them staring. They hope I'm just pretending. And giving up my power. Caving into pressure. I'm not living for them. I live for something better</segment2>
		<segment3>I'm not good enough. I'm not what they want. But let me tell you what. I know who I am. So just throw me out. For not fitting in. I will stand my ground. And be an outcast</segment3>
		<segment4>So-o what if I'm an outcast. So-o what if I'm an outcast</segment4>
		<segment5>So what if I don't look the. Part I'm supposed to play. What if I don't follow. All the rules they make. They think I should be perfect. They love it when I mess up. No grace in case I blow it. A good girl shouldn't need it</segment5>
		<segment6>I'm not good enough. I'm not what they want. But let me tell you what. I know who I am. So just throw me out. For not fitting in. I will stand my ground. And be an outcast</segment6>
		<segment7>So-o what if I'm an outcast. So-o what if I'm an outcast. So slow and everybody's so fast. So-o what if I'm an outcast</segment7>
		<segment8>I try to play nice. I don't want to fight. But I won't be great. When it sounds like I'm right. Cause what I believe. Is what makes me strong. If I don't belong. I hold onto love</segment8>
		<segment9>I try to play nice. I don't want to fight. But I won't be great. When it sounds like I'm right. Cause what I believe. Is what makes me strong. If I don't belong. I hold onto love</segment9>
		<segment10>So-o what if I'm an outcast. So-o what if I'm an outcast. So slow and everybody's so fast. No matter what it costs. I'll be an outcast</segment10>
		<segment11>I'm not good enough. I'm not what they want. But let me tell you what. I know who I am. So just throw me out. I'm not fitting in. I will stand my ground. And be an outcast</segment11>
		<segment12>I'm not good enough. I'm not what they want. And let me tell you what. I know who I am. So just throw me out. I'm not fitting in. I will stand my ground. And be an outcast    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
