<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Overtake You </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Time. It's eating me alive. Unable to rewind. Sink deeper while I'm climbing. Never to arrive</segment1>
		<segment2>I gave you everything. But still you need to feed. And underneath it all I'm screaming out</segment2>
		<segment3>Just carry on. Just prove me wrong. I know that I'm dying right now. And it seems that I'm so far gone. But not for long. I'll just be strong and keep knowing. That now I will overtake you</segment3>
		<segment4>Just one that you can use. One risk but you can't lose. Play the victim while abusing. Anyone you choose</segment4>
		<segment5>Painful consequence. Of standing on your lies. I'm barely breathing but. I'm screaming out</segment5>
		<segment6>Just carry on. Just prove me wrong. I know that I'm dying right now. And it seems that I'm so far gone. But not for long. I'll just be strong and keep knowing. That now I will overtake you</segment6>
		<segment7>I know that I'm dying right now. And it seems that I'm so far gone. (Overtake you). I'll just be strong and keep knowing. That now I will overtake</segment7>
		<segment8>You'll come to get me, but. You'll end up dead. You'll come to get me, but. You'll end up dead. You'll come to get me, but. You'll end up dead. You'll come to get me, but. You'll end up dead</segment8>
		<segment9>Just carry on. Just prove me wrong. I know that I'm dying right now. And it seems that I'm so far gone. But not for long. I'll just be strong and keep knowing. That now I will overtake you</segment9>
		<segment10>You'll come to get me, but. You'll end up dead. You'll come to get me, but. You'll end up dead. (Overtake you). You'll come to get me, but. You'll end up dead. (Overtake you, overtake you). You'll come to get me. (Overtake you). You'll come to get me    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
