<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Overnight (feat. Sarah Chapman) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>So, you've handed in your resignation, Contemplating why nothing turns out right. A little fed up with all the disappointments, So what's the point in wasting any time?</segment1>
		<segment2>It's only temporary, So what's your hurry?. No need to worry, Don't you know that..</segment2>
		<segment3>CHORUS: If it all just happened overnight, You wouldn't know how much it means. Yeah. If it all just happened overnight, You would never learn to believe, What you cannot see, Oh, What you cannot see.</segment3>
		<segment4>I feel like my pace is at a standstill. Do I wait till it falls into my hands?. A long highway ahead, Getting started, Steady hearted is what I think I am.</segment4>
		<segment5>There's something to be said, For experience, Who knows what's ahead, Keep on going..</segment5>
		<segment6>CHORUS. If it all just happened overnight, You wouldn't know how much it means. If it all just happened overnight, You would never learn to believe. What you cannot see, Oh. What you cannot see..</segment6>
		<segment7>(Take it a day, a day at a time). One foot in front of the other, (Take it a day, a day at a time). No need to hurry, hurry. (Take it a day, a day at a time). It won't happen overnight. It won't happen overnight</segment7>
		<segment8>Have a little faith, (Have a little faith). Must appreciate, (Must appreciate). Every single day, Don't give up, no.</segment8>
		<segment9>Have a little faith, (Have a little faith). Must appreciate, (Must appreciate). Every single day, Don't give up, no.</segment9>
		<segment10>CHORUS. If it all just happened overnight, You wouldn't know how much it means. Yeah. If it all just happened overnight, You would never learn to believe. What you cannot see. If it all just happened overnight, You wouldn't know how much it means. If it all just happened overnight, You would never learn to believe. What you cannot see.</segment10>
		<segment11>Have a little faith, (Have a little faith). Must appreciate, (Must appreciate). Every single day, Don't give up, no.</segment11>
		<segment12>Have a little faith, (Have a little faith). Must appreciate, (Must appreciate). Every single day, Don't give up, no.    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
