<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Path to Sorrow </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Sitting here thinking back. On the better days, the days gone past. Before the change, the way things were. When everything was new and pure. When life was free and filled with hope. When everything was explained in full. Those days are near forgotten. The ache of today replaces them. What about tomorrow?. Will I have reached the goal?. Or died forgotten, With nothing to show?</segment1>
		<segment2>&quot;don't get your hopes up son, There are no guarantees in life but one. That eventually you'll die. That's a guarantee you cannot escape from.&quot;</segment2>
		<segment3>So i'm sitting here - all alone. It's always worse when no one's home. Why should I continue on. If death is the only final outcome?. To pursue some mythical success. That some have been fooled to think exists?. Only to meet frustration and die. Still they go on trying and trying and.. I refuse to live that lie. But then what is there but to die?. I knew I require some change. But every day comes up the same..fruitless</segment3>
		<segment4>Failure - so many say. I slow them down i'm in the way. Spineless - got me convinced they've reached security. Weakling - got me pegged. As if alone they've reached success. Hopeless - all I am, the difference between</segment4>
		<segment5>This world betrays. This world, it feasts upon me</segment5>
		<segment6>Failure - far too weak. Can't even stand on your own two feet. Spineless - you could never make it in this world of ours. Weakling - they scream at me. Inside your self is the strength you need. Hopeless - the strong survive the weak are devoured</segment6>
		<segment7>Failure - I feel defeat</segment7>
		<segment8>But I see now they're hiding something. Spineless - draw my attention far away from hope. Weakling - away from God, away from love. Shake their fists at him above. Hopeless - could it be? he shakes the world the lie they hold</segment8>
		<segment9>My loneliness is evidence of my failure. To stay would mean to pursue some goal. Which has eluded me so far. They say I need no one else, only myself. Unfortunately that way of life leaves me nothing but hell    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
