<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Pipe Dream </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Downhill downtrodden left a slave. New day on the verge to find the gray. Floors swing and slope downhill to bring. Middle grounds set on wavering. Two sides to flip and coax a brink. Dealt an empty hand. Opposed to delete any bridge to stand. Polarized this side. Shades display this trade. Off to buy halfway. Games that bore my days. End of my phase today. I'm not willing to meet in the middle. End tragedy solve the riddle. And dissipate ideals of indecision pipe. Pipedreams like these will</segment1>
		<segment2>Cease and die unleashed. Like my past removed replaced and now. My phases die this time. Gray fades to late. Phases die this time. Gray fades to late. My phases die this time. Gray fades to late. Phases die this time. Gray fades to late</segment2>
		<segment3>Unveiled my mask. What's right not balanced. You'r tripped by intent to stretch. Searches coerce a mesh. But find no chance to clench against. Facts still remain unbalanced. If that equates to remaining stagnant. I'm no longer the same as the halfway days. No time delays</segment3>
		<segment4>Cease and die unleashed. Like my past removed replaced and now. My phases die this time. Gray fades to late. Phases die this time. Gray fades to late. My phases die this time. Gray fades to late. Phases die this time. Gray fades to late</segment4>
		<segment5>You wanted to know why I'm different. Why I refise to open my mind. Cause that relative stance is inadequate. To fulfill what i need inside. Many souls on the brink of collapse. Inside the midst of these so-called nightmares. So willing to embrace those pipedreams so lost. And neglecting their only real chance. So willing to hing in the balance. Your state us si desperate, so blank, so empty. And left with this notion that doesn't hold water or weight. It's dark or it's light so decide and face. Dark. So decide and face. Light. So decide and face. Dark. So decide and face. Light. So decide.     </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
