<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Place to Be </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>John: Yep, too clean</segment1>
		<segment2>??? Voice: And here we go, here we go</segment2>
		<segment3>John: Alright, guys, we got one chance. once chance, folks, do do this. This is our chance to shine, and let's put it to rhyme, and let's put it to the mind, and let's put it to the test. God Bless. so here we go, check it-</segment3>
		<segment4>You know, uh, we are steppin to the party, the place to be. OK, the crowd is packed, and people lookin at we. like the mic's on the stand, Speedy, you know what to do. stepped on stage, hey you</segment4>
		<segment5>Speedy: Yo, greetings earthlings, i'm on a search for a team of elohim. fiends seen (indistinguishable mumbling). and i recite for, as I recite for Heavenly riches. plus to spread the Gospel. and poison ivy when it itches. which is wrote in Acts 1:8. never debate when i'm quotin the omnipotent. never promotin tooth decay by way of teeth nashin'. mics i'm clashin like the classic flights of Ben Franklin's kites. lightnings bolts of light strike men. that they might see my good works, then. Glorify He who rolls from earth to Heaven. yo, i think it's evident, Christ takes residence. in hearts of benevolence. when God is speaking, yo we give Him reverence. we can wash and rinse in fragrance (aw, i messed it up)</segment5>
		<segment6>John: Fragrance, ah, that's cool that's cool</segment6>
		<segment7>Speedy: Fragrance, ya like that? ah, that's ok, that's ok. what you think it is?</segment7>
		<segment8>John: But it's a Freestyle, I like that. place to be, the place to be, the place to be. because we step into the party the place to be. ok the crowd is packed and people lookin at we. Like the mic's on the stand, and Transcend know what to do, Alan know what to do, hey you hey you</segment8>
		<segment9>Um, i said it before, Transcend five-foot-four. walkin in, steppin in through Todd Collins' door. in the studio rockin from here to beat next to Monday. Tuesday kid, we might chill on Sunday, but Saturday we're eatin Grits in the morning at Shoney's. Transcend rockin it, but not for the money. Truly the skill, bustin it at will. like i said it before, send me the bill. for hip-hop is the one I truly love, God is truly above rockin, keepin it cool to the end of the -- Ahhh!</segment9>
		<segment10>John: Step into the party, the place to be. ok the crowd is packed and people lookin at we. Like the mic's on the stand and</segment10>
		<segment11>?????? Voice: John Reuben know what to do!. BG ??? Voice: Reuben you know what to do!</segment11>
		<segment12>John: right right right I know to do. and what they want me to do is come through. and have a little fun. John Reuben a little bit lanky. a little six-foot-one. havin' a good time everytime without a care. look at me i got crazy fluffy little jewish hair. because i'm a jewish kid, call me the messianic. everytime i grab the microphone it's lyrics like Tonic. 'cuz you take it in, and then you want a little more. what step through the door, hardcore metaphor, not speakin' when i'm tweakin'. yo these whack emcees they be reakin. but let's not talk about the whack, let's talk about myself for a minute. so get in it. John Reuben about to spin it. for the crowd to go infinite times, infinite rhymes. infinite line after line, from the top of the mind, each and every tile, style, pile, file (indistinguishable mumbling)</segment12>
		<segment13>step into the party the place to be. ok the crowd is packed and people lookin at we. like the mic's on the stand, and y'all know what to do, so we stepped on staaaage</segment13>
		<segment14>???? Voice: and what happened?</segment14>
		<segment15>John: On stage, and the mic was on. the mic was on. the mic was on. so i turned the microphone on and i said a little somethin'. a little somethin'. i said turned the microphone on and we said a little somethin'. it was the place to be, in the space to be, too much energy and nothin can we do wastefully. because creativity runs through my B-O-D-Y. Don't ask questions, i'm just stressin, then God Blessin' and addressin' the. (indistinguishable mumbling)</segment15>
		<segment16>alright peeps, we're outta here</segment16>
		<segment17>??? Voice: Beautiful</segment17>
		<segment18>??? Voice: Aw, Cue!    </segment18>
	</english>
</song>
