<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Plain White Rapper/Plain White Rapper in a Mini Van </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Check one, two, this song right here is dedicated to all the soccer moms all across the world. Can I get more cow bell on this please?(cow bell). I'm a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. And I'm sittin on 20's (you're a liar). Okay their really 18's but I keep them clean.</segment1>
		<segment2>I've got a red minivan from 1996 (Toyota prevy, uh, to be exact). The window's broke and you know I won't ever get it fixed (which is pretty pathetic, actually). I'm bumpin' Veggie Tales I ain't even got any kids (Yeah, so what? I listen to Veggie Tales, so what?). People think I'm nuts but I just told them this (so what'd you tell them? Whooo!)</segment2>
		<segment3>. I'm a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. And I'm sittin on 20 inch rims (oookay.). Okay their really 16's but I keep them clean.</segment3>
		<segment4>To all the soccer moms taking their kids to karate (come on, mmmhmm, mmmhmm). Keep sippin' on your mocha-choka-froka-locha-mocha-choka latties (soy low fat low chai mocha..starbucks). This song is dedicated to all you and everybody (Tweezy got love for the soccer moms). So put your hands up right now if you really wanna party (come on! Stick em up high! Here we go whooo!)</segment4>
		<segment5>I'm a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. And I'm sittin on 20 inch rims (stop lying). Okay their really 14's but I keep them clean. (you're such a liar)</segment5>
		<segment6>Once upon a time a turtle hit my car on interstate 75 (its a true story, this really did happen). And the poor little turtle crawled off of the road and he died (that's so sad!) (single teardrops). I stood there on the roadside and I wanted to cry (poor little turtle). Except for the fact that the stupid turtle made my engine overheat and the car almost fried (and it cost me three hundred dollars!). But I'm okay (yeah, breath in, breath out)</segment6>
		<segment7>. I'm a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. Just a plain white rapper in a minivan. And I'm sittin on 20 inch rims...    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
