<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Playing God </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I can't make my own decisions. Or make any with precision. Well maybe you should tie me up. So I don't go where you don't want me. You say that I've been changing. That I'm not just simply aging. Well how could that be logical?. Just keep on craming ideas down my throat. Woah</segment1>
		<segment2>You don't have to believe me. But the way I, way I see it. Next time you point a finger I might have to. bend it back. And break it, break it off. Next time you point a finger I'll point you to. the mirror</segment2>
		<segment3>If Gods the game that you're playing. Well we must get more aquainted. Because it has to be so lonely to be the only. one who's holy. It's just my humble opinion but it's one that I. believe in. You don't deserve a point of view. If the only thing you see is you. Woah</segment3>
		<segment4>You don't have to believe me. But the way I, way I see it. Next time you point a finger I might have to. bend it back. Or break it, break it off. Next time you point a finger I'll point you to. the mirror</segment4>
		<segment5>This is the last second chance. (I'll point you to the mirror). I'm half as good as it gets. (I'll point you to the mirror). I'm on both sides of the fence. (I'll point you to the mirror). Without a hint of regret I'll hold you to it</segment5>
		<segment6>I know you don't believe me. But the way I, way I see it. Next time you point a finger I might have to. bend it back. Or break it, break it off. Next time you point a finger I'll point you to. the mirror</segment6>
		<segment7>I know you won't believe me. But the way I, way I see it. Next time you point a finger I might have to. bend it back. Or break it, break it off. Next time you point a finger I'll point you to. the mirror.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
