<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Playing With Fire </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Pardon me for saying so. But you look more pitiful. Than I had ever imagined. Despite perfect fashion. And your photographs depict you so differently. I always thought you would be. Some sort of match for me</segment1>
		<segment2>So let's decide who can survive. Jumping feet and racing beats. Of hearts that don't ever slow. Then I'll write letters on white paper. Expressing my deep disappointment</segment2>
		<segment3>Dripping where I stand. From my watery hands. Hoping to get past the open bedroom door. Where her clothes on the floor. Remind me of our conversation. The feeling of slight hesitation. To turn out the light</segment3>
		<segment4>Fourteen days now (I'm not). Since we started (I'm not hiding). To complicate the situation (From this situation). I'm not hiding (I'm not). I'm just buying some time (I'm not hiding). For us to find the back door (From this situation)</segment4>
		<segment5>We will come out. When it's safe for us. When it's safe for us. When it's safe for us. Us. For us. All</segment5>
		<segment6>There's nothing left to say (Don't believe me). To excuse the way that I behaved (When I say it's over). I still feel him. Gripping like a stain (By the time you're gone). To this fabric (It's almost over). Torn at every seam. Thrown away</segment6>
		<segment7>I'm without regret. I will not forget. I'm without regret. I will not forget</segment7>
		<segment8>Why should I take all the blame for all my mistakes? (I'm without regret). You were there with every promise made to break (I will not forget). When did you become the one without regret? (I'm without regret). Kill me, burn me down, I swear I won't forget (I will not forget). When did you become the one without regret (Kill me, kill me). Kill me, burn me down, I swear I won't forget (Kill me, kill me)    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
