<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Pray Now </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Somebody once told me &quot;The Lord is not your roadie. &quot;You ain't the star so do it yourself.&quot;. I said, &quot;Look, it's kind of dumb. If if there's things that I need done. It's a shame not to call on the Lord's help.&quot;. Well, my prayers start comin' and they don't stop comin'. I read through the rules and I think I found somethin'. Didn't make sense not to get more done. I pray real hard cause the Heavenly Son. Showed what to do, said knock and seek. So what's wrong with praying and asking. You better go look in Luke, bro. 11:9 if you don't know. Pray now  it's a lost art  get your day underway. Pray now  get a jump start  get a move on  get faith. God is listenin' you know. Only you can start prayin' though. There's a cool case so you're prayin' gets bolder. You look it up Luke 18 yeah, let's go there. When the meanest of men met the widow. Judge he was, you know if you have the right scripture. But I see his patience is gettin' pretty thin. The woman gets annoyin' so he might as well give in. The world's like that  how about the Lord. God already likes ya  and you'll never get ignored. Pray now  it's a lost art  get your day underway. Pray now  fourth chapter  let me show ya  in James. God is listenin' you know  only you can start prayin' though. Somebody once asked Jesus give us the capacity. To get ourselves a faith that is great. He said, &quot;Well, why ya want help?. &quot;You could move a little hill yourself. &quot;If you would all use a little faith.&quot;. Well, my prayers start comin' and they don't stop comin'. I read through the rules and I think I found somethin'. Didn't make sense not to get more done. Pray it smart cause the Heavenly Son. Showed what to do, said knock and seek. So what's wrong with praying and asking. You'll never know if you don't go. You better try if you don't know. Pray now  it's a lost art  get your day underway. Pray now  get a jump start  get a move on  get faith. God is listenin' you know  only you can start prayin' though</segment1>
		<segment2>    </segment2>
	</english>
</song>
