<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Presence (My Heart's Desire) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I lift up my voice. To the king, the king of glory. I hold out my hands. To the one who is worthy. I long for your presence. I long, Lord I need your touch</segment1>
		<segment2>Come, oh Lord, and fill up my life. With the light of your presence. This is my heart's desire. Oh father, come and let your spirit abide. I long for your presence. This is my heart's desire</segment2>
		<segment3>I long to be washed. In the well of your mercy. I long to be warmed. By the fire of your glory. I long for your presence. I long for your healing touch</segment3>
		<segment4>Come, oh Lord, and fill up my life. With the light of your presence. This is my heart's desire. Oh father, come and let your spirit abide. I long for your presence. This is my heart's desire</segment4>
		<segment5>It's my desire</segment5>
		<segment6>(I wanna feel your presence). Lord, it's my desire. (I wanna feel your presence). Lord, you're my desire. (I wanna feel your presence). I wanna feel your presence. I wanna feel your presence. I wanna feel your presence - Jesus</segment6>
		<segment7>Come, oh Lord, and fill up my life. With the light of your presence. This is my heart's desire (this is my heart's desire, oh..). come and let your spirit abide. I long for your presence (presence..). This is my heart's desire (this is my heart's desire, oh..)</segment7>
		<segment8>Come, oh Lord, and fill up my life (fill up my life). With the light of your presence. This is my heart's desire (this is my heart's desire, oh..). Come and let your spirit abide. I long for your presence this is my heart's desire</segment8>
		<segment9>It's my desire</segment9>
		<segment10>Lord, you're my desire. Lord, you're my desire    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
