<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Prodigal Son </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>((Intro Tye Speaking))</segment1>
		<segment2>I cant believe this;. Im not supposed to be living like this, I messed up.</segment2>
		<segment3>((Verse 1)). Thought it was fun, Thought I could do what I want. And I, thought I was grown and could make it on my own, I thought no one really understands me. And, even though home, I feel so alone. I thought, like do what cha you feel like doing no one cares anyway. maybe then someone will notice you.</segment3>
		<segment4>((Hook 1)). Now how I end up where I am? I dont know. I never planned on being here (and now I see that the problem is). The devil tempted me and I was drawn away. But I have no desire to stay! Oh!!</segment4>
		<segment5>((Chorus)). Got to get out of here (Im coming home father). I got to get out of here. I wanna be with you</segment5>
		<segment6>((Verse 2)). Cant believe what I got myself in to, Thought I had everything under control, (guess not). I didnt realize the whole time, That the enemy had plans to destroy my life, (try to take me out). Father please wont you have mercy on me (please). Please forgive me and restore you joy.</segment6>
		<segment7>((Hook 2)). I cant imagine staying here until I die. I got to get back to your side (I wanna be with you father, now I realize). The devil tempted me and I was drawn away. But I have no desire to stay! Oh!!</segment7>
		<segment8>((Chorus)). Got to get out of here. I got to get out of here. I wanna be with you. (Father I know I messed up but Im asking you to please! Take me back)</segment8>
		<segment9>Got to get out of here (I repent father). I got to get out of here (Yah! Im coming home). I wanna be with you. (I wanna be with you Jesus, anyone want to be with the Lord? Here we go sing)</segment9>
		<segment10>Got to get out of here (Ohhhoohh). I got to get out of here. I wanna be with you (please take me back [x3] Im sick of this stuff)</segment10>
		<segment11>Got to get out of here (pleassse). I got to get out of here (Im sick of my old ways). I wanna be with you (I want to be with you, take me back Lord I am ready for change)</segment11>
		<segment12>Got to get out of here (pleassse). I got to get out of here (anyone going back to the father house with me). I wanna be with you (come on and go with me [x3] with me the Fathers house lets go)</segment12>
		<segment13>((Fading Out)). Hell take us back I know, hes faithful yall come on. Anybody want to go back to the father's house? You know you left his presence you know you left</segment13>
		<segment14>Copyright © Tye Tribbett    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
