<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Psum 14 </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>well sure my movie part it won't be played by Al Pacino. Well, I hope you're not thinking I'm exactly Mr. Clean, though. As a kid, was in sin, and no one knew it but me. And my Olan Mills portrait was Dorian Gray. Well, I know I'm not the one you thought you knew back in high school. You'd never know, I'd never show, I just was a shy dude. But let me set you straight, 'cause all of us need saved. My sin was always here but that's erased</segment1>
		<segment2>I don't want to praise my crimes. Because I know that that would be impropriety. I'm just a ball of slime. So come and get forgiven just like He forgave me -- act now</segment2>
		<segment3>Read God's truth in. Romans and Psalms we learn that all people fall. But what would you expect knowing David and Paul. Have you met 'em? Them fellas know how we need grace. They did bad deeds only God could erase. 'Cause David had an affair and murdered, he still repented. Turning Paul around it took devine intervention. Acts 9 it will confirm he messed up every church. He sinned till Jesus told him, &quot;Hey, that hurts!&quot;</segment3>
		<segment4>I don't want to list my crimes. Because I know the fragility of my peity. And I recall this this line. In chapter 1 verse 15 of First Timothy -- that's how</segment4>
		<segment5>Don't count on me to live with no sin. Don't count on me -- I'll do it again. Don't count on me -- but the point you're missin'. Don't count on me -- is I'm forgiven</segment5>
		<segment6>We're all just no good and we're nailed without Christ. Act fast and He won't get upset about nothin'. You can stand around and scorn and scoff like Waldorf the Muppet. But you can't blame anybody; ask Jimmy Buffet. 'Cause if you take no blame you'll be really on the hook. You're on the Ten Most Wanted in the devil's own book. That's why Psalm number 14:3 is important. Because it says we're all sinners addin' up more sins</segment6>
		<segment7>I don't want to praise my crimes. Because I know that that would be impropriety. I'm just a ball of slime. So come and get forgiven just like He forgave me -- act now. (list my crimes again) fragility of my peity. (list my crimes again) 15 of First Timothy -- that's how    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
