<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Puppet </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Gonna get this party started.. </segment1>
		<segment2>It's all around me, I can't wish this away, you so amaze me, you took my monster away,                                                      x2. and away, and away, and away..</segment2>
		<segment3>Wake me, c'mon and wake me up now I. want to cut off my strings and break, loose of your control of me, cut your strings and be free with me, .                                                                         x2</segment3>
		<segment4>Everybody, shake your body, lift your hands, stop frontin', you're just a puppet,                                              x2    </segment4>
		<segment5>To all the marionettes </segment5>
		<segment6>If ya gonna run, how fast ya gonna run?, And if ya gonna jump, how high ya gonna jump?, . all you perpetrators be walkin' round frontin', what?, you fakers afraid to stand for somethin'?.                                                                                               x2                                                                                     . why don't ya stand up n' break me off. somethin'? </segment6>
		<segment7>Ya wanna make it outta sight?, somebody wanna get live tonight?, we can hit that, flip that, settle the score, 'n' ain't nobody rock a crowd like this before, ya wanna make it outta sight?, somebody wanna get live tonight?, like an earthquake, let it shake, make the floor vibrate, Krutch y'all, back to set the record straight. </segment7>
		<segment8>All y'all people, listen, it's on, Krutch marauders we on a mission, hittin' ya with the ill ammunition, at war with the puppet master, .. I'll bring it on if I had to, rip it 'n' leave the whole scene shattered, like chik, chik, blaow!, what ya think of me now, I'm lettin' my dawgs out, makin' it loud so hear me shout, what?, we be comin' laced with bass, hit the place with no trace, when we rock the space,     </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
