<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Quasimodo </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>You can be right. And I'll be real. Oh, and it still won't be a pain. That you will have to feel. Cause I don't need your approval. To find my worth </segment1>
		<segment2>I'm trapped inside of my own mind. Afraid to open my eyes cause of what I'd find and I. Don't wanna live like this anymore </segment2>
		<segment3>There goes my pain. There goes my chains. Did you see them falling. Because this feeling. There has no meaning. There goes the world. Off of my shoulders. There goes the world. Off of my back. There it goes </segment3>
		<segment4>Does it scare you that I can. Be something different than you. Would it make you feel. More comfortable if I wasn't. Well you can't control me. And you can't take away from me who I am </segment4>
		<segment5>There goes my pain. There goes my chains. Did you see them falling. Because this feeling. There has no meaning. There goes the world. Off of my shoulders. There goes the world. Off of my back </segment5>
		<segment6>You can't change me. You can't break me </segment6>
		<segment7>There goes the world. Off of my shoulders. There goes the world. Off of my back </segment7>
		<segment8>Have you ever felt. Like your only comfort was your cage. You're not alone. I've felt the same as you </segment8>
		<segment9>Have you ever felt like your secrets give you away. You're not alone. I've been there too </segment9>
		<segment10>Cause everyone is looking. Everyone is laughing. But I think everyone feels the same. Everybody wants to feel okay. Everybody wants to. Everybody wants to feel </segment10>
		<segment11>There goes my pain. There goes my chains. Did you see them falling. Because this feeling. There has no meaning </segment11>
		<segment12>There goes the world. Off of my shoulders. There goes the world. Off of my back </segment12>
		<segment13>Cause I don't want it. I don't want it </segment13>
		<segment14>You can't change me. You can't break me </segment14>
		<segment15>There goes the world. Off of my shoulders. There goes the world. Off of my back. There it goes    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
