<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Rainy Day </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>On a rainy day. I feel like I can change the world. Cause somehow I know that it's all gonna be alright. And on a rainy day. I can feel my heart beating. And I can taste the tears falling from the sky</segment1>
		<segment2>On a rainy day. (won't You come and save the world?). On a rainy day. (I know You're looking down on me)</segment2>
		<segment3>Love. It keeps us hanging on. Even when all hope is gone. I believe that Your love rains down on me. Faith. It carries us away. It takes us to a place. Far above this world. And I can see you in the clouds. On a rainy day</segment3>
		<segment4>On a rainy day. I feel like I'm in tune. And I can clearly see how much I have to lose. And on a rainy day. I feel like I am free. Cause I know You did it all to rescue me</segment4>
		<segment5>On a rainy day. (won't You come and save the world?). On a rainy day. (I know You're looking down on me)</segment5>
		<segment6>Love. It keeps us hanging on. Even when all hope is gone. I believe that Your love rains down on me. Faith. It carries us away. It takes us to a place. Far above this world. And I can see you in the clouds. On a rainy day</segment6>
		<segment7>Won't You come and save the world?. Won't You come and save the world?. Won't You come and save the world for You and me?. Won't You come and save the world?. Won't You come and save the world?. Won't You come and save the world for You and me?</segment7>
		<segment8>Love. It keeps us hanging on. Even when all hope is gone. I believe that Your love rains down on me. Faith. It carries us away. It takes us to a place. Far above this world. And I can see you in the clouds, yeah. Like a rainbow shining down. On a rainy day. Yeah, on a rainy day. On a rainy day. (Won't You come and save the world?)    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
