<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Real Life </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I still see the kid in me. Building castles by the sea. And skipping rocks across those ocean waves. Still building buoy rafts. And sailing on the Kachemak. And running wild across Alaskan plains</segment1>
		<segment2>And all my yesterdays don't seem so long ago now. And all those early years will always seem like home somehow</segment2>
		<segment3>And it was real life. And it was real good. It was a place I took for granted 'cause I just never understood. And there was real pain. There were real tears. But the way my Mama loved me somehow carried all those years. It was real life. Oh it was real life</segment3>
		<segment4>I still see the kid in jeans. But now he's standing next to me. Never thought that I'd have boys to raise. I don't have it figured out. It still feels like playing house. And it's something I am learning everyday</segment4>
		<segment5>And all of my todays seem like they're rushing by so fast. And every time I look around I pray that it will last</segment5>
		<segment6>And it's real life. And it's real good. And sometimes I take it all for granted even though I never should. And there is real pain. And there are real tears. But the way my baby loves me somehow carries all these years. And this is real life</segment6>
		<segment7>When I'm old and turning grey. And my boys have moved away. When it's time for me to say goodbye. I hope I leave a legacy. I hope that God is proud of me. I hope that I leave something good behind</segment7>
		<segment8>And all my yesterdays are flashing right before my eyes. And I'm standing in God's presence when I finally realize</segment8>
		<segment9>This is real life. This is real good. It's a place I took for granted 'cause I just never understood. And there'll be no pain. And there'll be no tears. 'Cause the way my Father loves me makes me grateful I am here. This is real life. This is real good. It's a place I took for granted 'cause I just never understood. There'll be no pain. There'll be no tears. 'Cause the way that You have loved me is the reason I am here. This is real life. Oh this is real life. Oh this is real life. This is real life    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
