<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Redemption </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>We've made a costly mistake tonight,</segment1>
		<segment2>As we fed ourselves to the lion's den. We lowered our guard and fell on our swords, And you call this a war.</segment2>
		<segment3>You've taken so much more than pride. (you've gotta be kidding me).</segment3>
		<segment4>You've taken so much more than pride. (everything in time will burn).</segment4>
		<segment5>This is do or die, look a promise in the eye, I hope to God you're comfortable enough to live a lie.</segment5>
		<segment6>This is do or die, look a promise in the eye, I hope to God you're strong enough to live with compromise.</segment6>
		<segment7>We've made a costly mistake tonight. There's a heavy price for this treason.</segment7>
		<segment8>So we covered our eyes and forgot our names, And you call this a war.</segment8>
		<segment9>You've taken so much more than pride. (you've gotta be kidding me). You've taken so much more than pride</segment9>
		<segment10>(everything in time will burn).</segment10>
		<segment11>This is do or die, look a promise in the eye, I hope to God you're comfortable enough to live a lie. This is do or die, look a promise in the eye,</segment11>
		<segment12>I hope to God you're strong enough to live with compromise.</segment12>
		<segment13>What a disaster with no one at fault, Everyone's screaming, &quot;God save us all&quot;.</segment13>
		<segment14>Come on courageous child, You have to trust in this. Find what you've always wanted, You have to trust in this. Come on courageous child, You have to trust in this. Find what you've always wanted, You have to trust in this.</segment14>
		<segment15>This is do or die, look a promise in the eye, I hope to God you're comfortable enough to live a lie.</segment15>
		<segment16>This is do or die, look a promise in the eye, I hope to God you're strong enough to live with compromise.     </segment16>
	</english>
</song>
