<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>renegade </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>We are renegades, we shoot to kill, We shoot to kill, we shoot.. There's no stopping us, no holding us back.</segment1>
		<segment2>This is the trick of our trade, this is exactly what we do best.</segment2>
		<segment3>It's just a matter of time, it's just a matter of time, What goes around, comes around. It's just a matter of time, it's just a matter of time,</segment3>
		<segment4>What goes around, comes around.</segment4>
		<segment5>We are renegades, we shoot to kill, We shoot to kill, we shoot.. There's no stopping us, no holding us back. This is the trick of our trade, this is exactly what we do best.</segment5>
		<segment6>We are renegades, we shoot to kill, We shoot to kill, we shoot.. There's no stopping us, no holding us back. This is the trick of our trade, this is exactly what we do best.</segment6>
		<segment7>. Move as fast as you can, move as fast as you can, Outrun, outrun what you've become. Move as fast as you can, move as fast as you can, Outrun, outrun what you've become.</segment7>
		<segment8>. Forgiveness, sweet forgiveness, you know I won't forget this one. Wait patiently til morning comes. My God, my God, what have I done?. Forgiveness, sweet forgiveness, you know I won't forget this one.</segment8>
		<segment9>Wait patiently til morning comes. My God, my God, what have I done?</segment9>
		<segment10>We drew these lines to cross them. We knew exactly what to do. We broke our own defenses.</segment10>
		<segment11>Hold fast, hold fast.</segment11>
		<segment12>We are renegades, we shoot to kill, We shoot to kill, we shoot.. There's no stopping us, no holding us back. This is the trick of our trade, this is exactly what we do best.</segment12>
		<segment13>We are renegades, we shoot to kill, We shoot to kill, we shoot.. There's no stopping us, no holding us back. This is the trick of our trade, this is exactly what we do best.     </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
