<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Retro Love </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Its been awhile now Ive been searching thinking about. Sin and drought, up and down spinning round, round, round. Round, Round I havent found it, truths alive dont doubt it. Pounding down the doors &amp; hallowing ow, ow, ow. Slouched like a youth I found God in the room. He said yo I know you, I got a girl for ye dude. Am I high, am I dead, am I alive, is this real. Can I touch can I feel, pinch me, oww yeah, Sat me down daps &amp; pounds, showed me style. Told me how, hold a second thats my girl. I think Ive figured out that a </segment1>
		<segment2>Im down with ye, down with ye. Ill hit the town with ye. Can I get some love yo hommie show me love </segment2>
		<segment3>Im down with ye, down with ye. Ill stick around with ye. Can I get some love yo hommie show me love </segment3>
		<segment4>I, I, I want to show ye. I think Im ready for ye. Just let the party music play. Im down with ye down with ye. I got that sound for ye. Just let the music play </segment4>
		<segment5>I see it clear now her and I Cali style. She is fine, she is mine, likes it when I drop a rhyme. Chilling by the beach home. Surfing or on skateboards. Doesnt hurt that shes model. Run way girl, Makes me holla. Well grow our family tree. Little Manas Melanies. Living free sipping drinks. Coke and Ice bubble teas. God is watching over this. Blessings is so obvious. Call it bliss, call it crisp. This is how I want to live. Its retro automatic, the love is so dynamic. Im dancing like an addict </segment5>
		<segment6>Im down with ye, down with ye. Ill hit the town with ye. Can I get some love yo hommie show me love </segment6>
		<segment7>Im down with ye, down with ye. Ill stick around with ye. Can I get some love yo hommie show me love </segment7>
		<segment8>I, I, I want to show ye. I think Im ready for ye. Just let the party music play. Im down with ye down with ye. I got that sound for ye. Just let the music play </segment8>
		<segment9>But if you dont think your down with me, Thats cool cause we can still be friends at least. And a, we could just play Monopoly youll see. Youll get to know me uh huh, youll get to know me, know me. But I, I think you really might be right. I think you might just be the guy for me, and you and maybe youll give me a ride, home </segment9>
		<segment10>This is my song, glad you all came along, sing it now. Sing it loud.     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
