<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Rock Medley: Sight Unseen/It Is Finished/Think Twice/I Am on the Rock </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>For so long I was depending upon. My senses and fences, I tried to ride on. And trusting in things that can never be seen. Was always a crutch on which others must lean. Thinking if I could see I would believe. Then somebody said believe and you will see</segment1>
		<segment2>Sight unseen, sight unseen. You have to take it sight unseen. Blinded by the darkness only faith can come between. Sight unseen, sight unseen</segment2>
		<segment3>In the heat of early morning on a hill they call the Skull. The roaring of the angry mob had settled to a lull. All eyes were cast upon the man whose hands and feet were bound. They watched him cry in anguish when they heard the hammer pound</segment3>
		<segment4>They watched the bloody woven thorns with which his head was crowned. They watched the bloody cross of wood be dropped into the ground. The soldiers gambled for His clothes, they watched them win and lose. They saw the sign above his head that said King of the Jews</segment4>
		<segment5>(It is finished) And the sky grew black as the night. (It is finished) And the people scattered in fright. The work had been done, redemption had been won. The war was over without a fight. It is finished</segment5>
		<segment6>You can think of times when you had the right chance. You could make a choice when nobody could see. You could think of ways of defending your deeds. Justify the way that you wanted to be</segment6>
		<segment7>Wait just a minute. Wait just a minute</segment7>
		<segment8>Hey, did you ever think twice. Something inside says stay away. Hey, did you ever think twice. When there's still time you can go the other way. Hey, did you ever think twice. If you don't bother, gonna pay the price. Hey, did you ever think twice </segment8>
		<segment9>The earth is shakin'. It's like a bad dream. This world is crumblin'. Comin' apart at the seam but. I am on the rock</segment9>
		<segment10>Everywhere i'm tunning it's only bad news. This bomb is tickin' and we're getting to the end of the fuse. I am on the rock</segment10>
		<segment11>I am on the rock, the sure fundation. I am on the rock. I am on the rock, his revelation. Though the winds may blow. And though the floods may grow. I shall not be moved, 'cause i am on the rock</segment11>
		<segment12>We wait since the day He ascended. He said He would come again. Some think it will be such a long time. Some they the know just when. We live like there's no tomorrow. We wait with out lamps of oil. We watch for the midnight hour. The day we cease our toil. When the trumpet sounds and the bridegroom comes</segment12>
		<segment13>The wedding's gonna be so royal. So we gotta keep staying loyal. 'Cause our feet are gonna leave this soil. When we burn the midnight oil. When we burn the midnight oil</segment13>
		<segment14>Smell the burning powder?. There's danger in the air. A voice from deep inside is telling you, 'you must beware'. Then enemy is watching. Every step you take. To find his opportunity in every choice you make</segment14>
		<segment15>And it's no game. When someone lives without His grace. And who's to blame. When it blows up in your face</segment15>
		<segment16>It's a mine field - you'd better follow Him through. God knows the way - you'd better stick like glue. It's a mine field - better stay on His heels. 'cause the enemy kills and the enemy steals. So keep your head down and keep you eyes peeled. 'cause life is.. Life is a mine field</segment16>
		<segment17>Son of the morning - highest of all. You had so much going till you took the fall. Had a place in the glory but you wanted it all. Impossible odds but you had the gall. It seemed so unlikely that you would rebel. Such a worthy opponent that you knew so well. But you went down fighting when you heard the bell. Took a third down from heaven when you went to hell</segment17>
		<segment18>This means war - and the battle's still raging. War - and though both sides are waging. The Victor is sure and the victory secure. But till judgment we all must endure. This means war! </segment18>
		<segment19>(It is finished) And the sky grew black as the night. (It is finished) And the people scattered in fright. The work had been done, redemption had been won. The war was over without a fight. It is finished    </segment19>
	</english>
</song>
