<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Rockin' Around The Christmas Tree </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Rockin' around the Christmas tree. At the Christmas party hop. Mistletoe hung where you can see. Everybody tries to stop </segment1>
		<segment2>Rockin' around the Christmas tree. Let the Christmas spirit ring. Later we'll have some pumpkin pie. And we'll do some caroling </segment2>
		<segment3>You will get a sentimental feelin' when you hear. Voices singing let's be jolly. Deck the halls with boughs of holly </segment3>
		<segment4>Rockin' around the Christmas tree. Have a happy holiday. Everyone's dancing merrily. In the new old fashioned way </segment4>
		<segment5>You will get a sentimental feelin' when you hear. Voices singing let's be jolly. Deck the halls with boughs of holly </segment5>
		<segment6>Rockin' around the Christmas tree. Have a happy holiday. Everyone's dancing merrily. In the new old fashioned way </segment6>
		<segment7>Jingle bell, jingle bell, jingle bell rock. Jingle bells swing and jingle bells ring. Snowin' and blowin' up bushels of fun. That's the jingle bell rock rock rock </segment7>
		<segment8>Jingle bell, jingle bell, jingle bell rock. Jingle bells chime in jingle bell time. Dancin' and prancin' in Jingle Bell Square. In the frosty air </segment8>
		<segment9>What a bright time, it's the right time. To rock the night away. Jingle bell time is a swell time. To go gliding in a one-horse sleigh </segment9>
		<segment10>Giddy-up jingle horse, pick up your feet. Jingle around the clock. Mix and mingle in the jingle bell rate. That's the jingle bell rock </segment10>
		<segment11>What a bright time, it's the right time. To rock the night away. Jingle bell time is a swell time. To go gliding in a one-horse sleigh </segment11>
		<segment12>Jingle bell, jingle bell, jingle bell rock. Jingle bells swing and jingle bells ring. Snowin' and blowin' up bushels of fun. That's the jingle bell rock </segment12>
		<segment13>Mix and mingle in the jingle bell rate. That's the jingle bell. That's the jingle bell. That's the jingle bell rock.     </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
