<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Rolling Stone </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Sitting on the front porch, Waiting for you to come home. Visions of reuniting in my head. Only bitter-sweet memories, no holidays, no Christmas trees. Broken promises I've got instead.</segment1>
		<segment2>How I used to wonder, 'Where did I go wrong?. How you could have stayed away so long?'. Thank God for my mother, Her's was no easy song. Thank God that He showed me how to get along.</segment2>
		<segment3>My papa was a rolling stone. Abandon us and left us 'lone. And how he broke my heart and hope; had me loose my faith. Somebody knows what I've been through. I've understood, I've been there too. So let me introduce you to my father, Father.</segment3>
		<segment4>Your story sounds alot like mine. It's a story heard a thousand times. Someone hurting leaves in disaray. Don't you know that God made you more valuable than they ever knew?. You know you can live past their mistakes.</segment4>
		<segment5>Oh, how I used to wonder 'How could all this be?. Someone that you loved so much just turns their back and leaves.'. Oh, you need the lover of you soul and. He is able to take care of you annd. He will never leave.</segment5>
		<segment6>Your papa was a rolling stone. Abandoned you and left you 'lone. And how he broke your heart and hope. He had me loose my faith. I'm seeing what you're going through. I understand, I've been there too. So let me introduce you to my father, Father.</segment6>
		<segment7>I was lost and out of controle. Then He found me and saved my soul. Let me lead you to the one I know. He can make you whole.</segment7>
		<segment8>No longer I wonder, Solid ground under my feet. I know what my life is worth, No longer incomplete. I just want to tell you, You are truly loved, By the Maker of the Heavens, the Creator of the Earth. You know He's got His hands on you and. That is more than enough.</segment8>
		<segment9>My papa was a rolling stone. Abandoned us and left us 'lone. And how he broke my heart and hope; had me loose my faith. Somebody saw what I've been through. They understood, They've been there too. They gladly introduced me to my father, Father.</segment9>
		<segment10>Your papa was a rolling stone. Abandoned you and left you 'lone. And how he broke your heart and hope. He had me loose my faith. I'm seeing what you're going through. I understand, I've been there too. So let me introduce you to my father, Father.</segment10>
		<segment11>Tell me what you're going through. I understand, I've been there too. So let my introduce you to my father, Father.</segment11>
		<segment12>God..</segment12>
		<segment13>.     </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
