<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Santa Claus Is Thumbing To Town </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It was the night before Christmas, And up at the North Pole, Everybody's going crazy;. Everything's out of control.</segment1>
		<segment2>The toy shop is on fire, The toys melting on the shelves, And you can hear Mrs. Claus scream, &quot;One can never trust those elves!&quot;</segment2>
		<segment3>Unless something drastic happens fast, Say hello to the ghost of Christmas past. Because, Rudolph's puking boughs of holly!. Old Saint Nick ain't all that jolly. And the sleigh's in the shop. 'Cause it's broken down, But Christmas won't stop. 'Cause Santa Claus is thumbing to town. Santa Claus is thumbing to town. Santa Claus is thumbing to town. Santa Claus is thumbing to town</segment3>
		<segment4>Very much to his disliking, Santa spends all night hitch-hiking. With a sign that reads, &quot;Ho ho slow down,&quot;. Santa Claus is thumbing to town.</segment4>
		<segment5>Every car just drove right past him, And sped right out of sight. Santa never got to ask them. To drive around the world in just one night.</segment5>
		<segment6>So Kris Kringle started walkin'. Through the snow without his sleigh, Shed a tear for every stocking. That would be empty Christmas day.</segment6>
		<segment7>Unless something drastic happens fast, Say hello to the ghost of Christmas past. Because, Rudolph's puking boughs of holly!. Old Saint Nick ain't all that jolly. And the sleigh's in the shop. 'Cause it's broken down, But Christmas won't stop. 'Cause Santa Claus is thumbing to town (uh-oh!). Santa Claus is thumbing to town (uh-oh!). Santa Claus is thumbing to town (uh-oh!). Santa Claus is thumbing to town (uh-oh!)</segment7>
		<segment8>Very much to his disliking, Santa spends all night hitch-hiking. With a sign that reads, &quot;Ho ho slow down,&quot;. Santa Claus is thumbing to town, Santa Claus is thumbing to town.    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
