<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Santa Clause Is Coming To Town </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Oh yeah! Do-do-do-oh! Santa Claus is coming to town! </segment1>
		<segment2>Oh! You better watch out. You better not cry. You better not pout I'm telling you why. Santa Claus is coming to town </segment2>
		<segment3>He's making a list. Checking it twice. Gonna find out who's naughty or nice. Santa Claus is coming to town </segment3>
		<segment4>He sees you when you're sleeping. He knows when you're awake. He knows if you've been bad or good. So be good for goodness sake! </segment4>
		<segment5>So! You better watch out. Oh! You better watch out. You better not cry. You better not pout, I'm telling you why. Santa Claus is coming. Santa Claus is coming. Santa Claus is coming to town! </segment5>
		<segment6>Do-do-do-oh! </segment6>
		<segment7>Yeah, oh yeah! Santa Claus is coming to town! </segment7>
		<segment8>Oh! You better watch out. You better not cry. You better not pout, I'm telling you why. Santa Claus is coming to town! </segment8>
		<segment9>He's making a list. Checking it twice. Gonna find out who's naughty or nice. Santa Claus is coming to town </segment9>
		<segment10>He sees you when you're sleeping. He knows when you're awake. He knows if you've been bad or good. So be good for goodness sake! </segment10>
		<segment11>Oh! You better watch out. You better not cry. You better not pout, I'm telling you why. Santa Claus is coming. Santa Claus is coming. Santa Claus is coming to town! </segment11>
		<segment12>Oh- you better watch out!. You better not cry!. You better not pout!. I'm telling you why! </segment12>
		<segment13>Santa Claus is coming to town! </segment13>
		<segment14>(spoken) Merry Christmas to All and to all a goodnight. Wow! Jump5! yeah baby!    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
