<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Saved By Love </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Laura loves her little family. She's the kind of woman. Who loves them with her life. But sometimes in the evening. When the world rests on her shoulders. With four walls closing in. She'll close her eyes. It's not like she misses being younger. Though she never was in Vogue magazine or on T.V. But her husband loves her dearly. And morning shows her clearly. Kiss her little baby girl. Laura, she's the queen of the world</segment1>
		<segment2>Can't imagine ever leaving now. Now that she's been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love, Listen to her quiet heart singing loud. Larua, she's been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love. I know that she's been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love. Saved by love</segment2>
		<segment3>There's nothing quite like my family's love to warm me. Nothing short of death's gonna ever leave me cold. Still at times it's lonely. But through it all it only. Makes me love Jesus more. This is what he came here for</segment3>
		<segment4>I can't imagine ever leaving now. Now that I've been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love, He's gone and turned my crazy world back around. And I've been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love. I know that I've been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love. Saved by love</segment4>
		<segment5>Oh I'm never leaving now. Now that I've been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love, He's gone and turned my crazy world back around. And I've been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love. Amy, she's been saved by love, Saved by love, saved by love. Saved by love</segment5>
		<segment6>I'm saved by love, That's right, There's nothing I can say. Nothing I can do. Nothing I can say. We're all just saved by love. Nothing you can say. Nothing you can do. Only love can say. Only love can do    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
