<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Say Goodbye </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>To the voice to the liar in the mirror. Saying you can't ever change. To the guilt that's sittin on your shoulder. Always keeping you locked in chains. To the past that you can't undo. To the pain that you're walkin through. To the small and the big mistakes. This is what love wants to say</segment1>
		<segment2>Say goodbye. Say goodbye. To the one that used to be. Say goodbye. Say goodbye. Everyday is a brand new mercy. Hello. Hello. This is where it starts now. Hello. Hello. Everything can turn around</segment2>
		<segment3>In a moment, here's your moment. You can say goodbye</segment3>
		<segment4>There is grace that you can't imagine. There is love that you can't out run. There is peace that you can hold onto. When your world is comin undone. You don't have give into the fear. Don't have to have let your story stop here. And when the hand tries to pull you back. You don't have to back, you don't have to go back</segment4>
		<segment5>Say goodbye. Say goodbye. To the one that used to be. Say goodbye. Say goodbye. Everyday is a brand new mercy. Hello. Hello. This is where it starts now. Hello. Hello. Everything can turn around</segment5>
		<segment6>In a moment, here's your moment. You can say goodbye</segment6>
		<segment7>To everything that breaks you down. It doesn't have to define you now. Jesus came to take it all away</segment7>
		<segment8>Say goodbye. Say goodbye. To the one that used to be. Say goodbye. Say goodbye. Everyday is a brand new mercy. Hello. Hello. This is where it starts now. Hello. Hello. Everything can turn around</segment8>
		<segment9>In a moment, here's your moment. You can say goodbye</segment9>
		<segment10>Say goodbye. Say goodbye. You're not the one you used to be. Say goodbye. Say goodbye. Everyday is a brand new mercy. Hello. Hello. This is where it starts now. Hello. Hello. Everything can turn around</segment10>
		<segment11>In a moment, here's the moment. Where you say goodbye</segment11>
		<segment12>Say goodbye. Say goodbye. Say goodbye. Say goodbye    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
