<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Say the Words </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Solomen once wrote. Better is open rebuke. Than hidden love. So say the words</segment1>
		<segment2>VERSE 1-Silence is golden. But these are the words that the world needs to hear. Terms of compassion will cause a reaction. As love draws them near</segment2>
		<segment3>B VERSE- But still we choose to hide. Behind the face of pride. Pretending we are blind to the calling. This is my point and case. If hate can be erased. With such a simple phrase. Why are we stalling</segment3>
		<segment4>CHORUS- Say the words. Say the words. Say I love you. Say the words I long to hear. Say the words. Say the words. Say I love you. Say the words. I long to hear</segment4>
		<segment5>TURN AROUND- Ya gotta say it. Ya gotta say it, say it. Ya gotta say it. Ya gotta say it, say it</segment5>
		<segment6>VERSE 2- Some just assume we already know. Of the love that they feel. Some have a heart-felt emotion. But never the words to reveal</segment6>
		<segment7>B VERSE- I think we all relate. So why are we afraid. To let our convey what we're feeling. There is a world in need. With hungry souls to feed. And love an intercede. If we're willing</segment7>
		<segment8>REPEAT CHORUS. REPEAT TURN AROUND</segment8>
		<segment9>RAP- The word love. Well, it was once over-used. Back in the '70s the word was abused. But I refuse to let love be diluted. We can't allow physical lust to intrude it. Or pollute it because there ain't no excuse. For the greatest gift of all ot be abused. So chose to lose the pride that may tug at you. Don't be afraid of the words &quot;I love you&quot;</segment9>
		<segment10>REPEAT CHORUS</segment10>
		<segment11>Choose to lose the pride that may tug at you. Don't be afraid of the words &quot;I love oyu&quot;</segment11>
		<segment12>REPEAT CHORUS    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
