<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Search Me Lord </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Chorus: Search me, Lord. Search me, Lord. (Here's what I want You to do). Shine the light from heaven on my soul. If You find anything that shouldn't be. Take it out and strengthen me. 'Cause I wanna be right. I wanna be saved. And I wanna be whole</segment1>
		<segment2>Repeat Chorus:</segment2>
		<segment3>While I'm down here praying. Lord, search my heart.. While I'm down here praying. Lord, search my heart.. While I'm down here praying. Lord, search my heart.. Because You know. Whether I'm right or wrong</segment3>
		<segment4>Repeat Chorus:</segment4>
		<segment5>Every day, every way. I wanna be right. I wanna be saved. I wanna be whole</segment5>
		<segment6>I'm calling on You, Jesus. (You're the only one that can save me, Jesus). I don't wanna live this way. I want You to make me over again</segment6>
		<segment7>In my mind, my heart. My soul, yes, God, every part. The way that I walk, and I talk. The way I live and the way that I give. You know my thoughts. You know the secret of every fault. (Every part of me You know, Good God)</segment7>
		<segment8>Good God, I want You to make me clean. Make me whole deep down within. I just wanna be right..</segment8>
		<segment9>Everyday that i'm living, Lord. Everything that I'm trying to do</segment9>
		<segment10>I want You to wash me in Your blood. Take away my every blot and stain. My iniquities, make them whiter. Whiter than snow right now, I pray</segment10>
		<segment11>Getting down on my knees. And I'm crying from my heart. Good God, I don't wanna live this way. So help me, help me out today</segment11>
		<segment12>Jesus, I need You. Come on, take control of my life. Please, take away my sin. Only You can do it, Lord. I trust You with my whole heart. I believe You're gonna do it for me..     </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
