<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Selling The News </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Welcome to the Holy City; the silver screen.  Built with a lens and a low self esteem.  A teenager's plea for meaning and memes.  We're selling the news</segment1>
		<segment2> See, opinions are easier to swallow than facts.  The greys instead of the whites and the blacks.  If you shoot it too straight it won't come back.  We're selling the news</segment2>
		<segment3> See, money speaks volumes louder than words.  And virtues with wings, maybe not quite at first.  But salaries are paid by the ads not the verbs.  We're selling the news</segment3>
		<segment4> See, all men are equal; all is for sale.  A powerful dog has been chasing his tail.  The lowest common denominator prevails.  We're selling the news</segment4>
		<segment5> I wanna believe you, I wanna believe.  But everything is in-between.  The fact is fiction, the fact is fiction</segment5>
		<segment6> I wanna believe you, I wanna believe.  But everything is in-between.  The fact is fiction.  Suspicion is the new religion</segment6>
		<segment7> America listens as the story is told.  With the eye on the truth as the story unfolds.  But the ratings determine which story was sold.  We're selling the news</segment7>
		<segment8> Begging the question, mongering fears.  Stroking the eyes and tickling ears.  The truth is seldom just as it appears.  We're selling the news</segment8>
		<segment9> I wanna believe you, I wanna believe.  But everything is in-between.  The fact is fiction, the fact is fiction</segment9>
		<segment10> I wanna believe you, I wanna believe.  But everything is in-between.  The fact is fiction, the fact is fiction</segment10>
		<segment11> I can see your talking heads.  On the television set.  On the Internet they said.  The fact is fiction</segment11>
		<segment12> Suspicion is the new religion</segment12>
		<segment13> Substance, oh, substance, where have you been?.  You've been replaced by the masters of spin.  Who make good looking books and write history in.  We're selling the news</segment13>
		<segment14> The lines start to blur; I get so confused.  I get shiny new models mixed up with the blues.  I get binary code mixed up with abuse.  The facts are simply one option to choose</segment14>
		<segment15> When nothing is sacred, there's nothing to lose.  When nothing is sacred, all is consumed.  We're still on the air, it must be the truth.  We're selling the news</segment15>
		<segment16> I wanna believe you, I wanna believe.  But everything is in-between.  The fact is fiction, the fact is fiction</segment16>
		<segment17> I wanna believe you, I wanna believe.  But everything is in-between.  The fact is fiction, the fact is fiction</segment17>
		<segment18> I wanna believe you, I wanna believe.  But everything I see is green.  The fact is fiction</segment18>
		<segment19> Suspicion is the new religion    </segment19>
	</english>
</song>
