<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Selling Out Ain't Easy </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I've been feeling kind of sick to my stomach. Its just a gimmick but the kids seem to love it. And if youre patient you can witness the sell-out. Im not a killer but Hollywood's gonna drown</segment1>
		<segment2>And if youre feeling original. Dont let it go to your head. Its all been done before. Youre not the first one. Youre not the first one</segment2>
		<segment3>And theres a rumor creeping into my ears. That we've been changing how our image appears. And Ill be the first one, not the last one. To tell you images in mirrors arent as big as you hear. Until those who doubt. A bitter taste lingering in my mouth. Im not a trophy, Im just a show fiend</segment3>
		<segment4>Hold out your hand now baby close your eyes. Im gonna take you on a journey tonight. They say Im addicted to the spotlight (Oh no). Ive got a feeling they may be right. Hold out your hand now baby close your eyes. I'll take you on a journey if the feeling's right. They say Im addicted to the spotlight (Oh no). Ive got a feeling they may be right</segment4>
		<segment5>And you leave the people wondering. You leave the children wanting a popular attitude. You wont admit its to flatter you. And if youre feeling original. Dont let it go to your head. Its all been done before. Youre not the first one. Youre not the first one</segment5>
		<segment6>Again and again and again and again..</segment6>
		<segment7>Hold out your hand now baby close your eyes. Im gonna take you on a journey tonight. They say Im addicted to the spotlight (Oh no). Ive got a feeling they may be right. Hold out your hand now baby close your eyes. I'll take you on a journey if the feeling's right. They say Im addicted to the spotlight (Oh no). Ive got a feeling they may be right. Ive got a feeling they may be right</segment7>
		<segment8>And Ive found the key. The spotlight fiend. And Im breaking you down to your shaking knees. And Ive found the key. The spotlight fiend. And Im breaking you down to your shaking knees.     </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
