<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Set It Off </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>To all the people in the house tonite, Can ya feel it?. To those who live under the street lights at night, Can ya feel it?. Come on and check this out, We bout to set this off. Here come the drums </segment1>
		<segment2>When I let loose, I come out blazin', I maintain mannin' all stations, Fully prepared for all situations, We blow tracks like shrapnel, with the rap skill, Shoot to kill, not for thrills, I got an iron grip. That's the sound we make, no mistake keep the floor warm, From town to town and state to state, And yo, we rock da set like an earthquake. Hold it tight too, and too, I just saw, Strapped to my knife boots.. We bump tracks like a fifteens the flavors me, And chill like light when it flows through my brain stream, Ready to fit the script twice when I get nice, Equally precise, hits you open like head lice, </segment2>
		<segment3>This time around we're here to let it be known, Thousand Foot be the kings of this microphone, This time around we're hear to let it be known, Thousand Foot be the kings of this microphone now. </segment3>
		<segment4>Out to all the people in the house tonight, We're gonna keep on rockin' 'till the broad daylight, So just listen to the sounds comin' through this mic, We're gonna do this right, do this right. </segment4>
		<segment5>Now set it off!!. Just set it off, right!. Set it off, Just set it off, right! Come on!. Set it off, We just set it off, right!. Set it off!. We just set off, right!. (Play it for yah radio) </segment5>
		<segment6>Fire it up like NASA, Rockin' it to ya'll, ghetto blaster, You're quick we're faster, We got the skills to out last ya, My mentality stays open, And if everything's cool, I'm hopin', To leave this microphone smokin'.. Hope your ready, My whole team can rock steady, Makin' noise with my boys, And watchin' out for poison, My main objective is to stand for what I believe, Maybe hear the sounds of the guillotine, </segment6>
		<segment7>We drop, hit, electrify, And to all the weak minded till the next in line, Here we made it in our accord, Ready to spawn, Used to go on and on, But now we just drop bombs, </segment7>
		<segment8>This time around we're here to let it be known, Thousand Foot be the kings of this microphone, This time around we're hear to let it be known, Thousand Foot be the kings of this microphone now. </segment8>
		<segment9>Just keep on rockin' and don't stop, Keep rockin' and don't stop.. Just keep on rockin' and don't stop, Keep rockin' and don't stop.. Just keep on rockin' and don't stop, Keep rockin' and don't stop.. Just keep on rockin' and don't stop, Keep rockin' and don't stop.    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
