<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Set Me Up </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Right in front of me dropping another game. Now I watch your face as your eyes look down. Away from my glance. Backstabbed as I hear the cracks drop smack. I count the ways your little whispers swell to greet my daze. Underground, so down, your scene above me. But now I see so clearly. I'm not down, I never could be. And it's long past time for me to show you</segment1>
		<segment2>Speak my mind in response to your condescending way. Of placing me below your feet. &quot;It's not what you know, it's who you know&quot;. But all I know now is you live for the show&quot;. Smiles in my face with smirks in your eyes. And I understand what it means to be. &quot;Ligit&quot; in your eyes, not I. Nor none of my &quot;attempts&quot; to be on the inside. I'm not down, I never could be. And it's time, this time I'll show you</segment2>
		<segment3>Set me up. Knocked down. Knocked down from your clique, you. Understand how you rejected me. I look at your face and weep for your &quot;scene&quot;</segment3>
		<segment4>So I ask myself what needs to be said. What now, what light can I shed?. As I battle to fight down the angry thought. That's swelling to escape my head. So it's plain as day and you can see. that I have a right to explain my self to you. So don't look away or turn away or laugh away. Because your &quot;scene&quot; is dead today. We can't brign ourselves back down to this level. Because you are no better than me. Down with all that took us away from standing as one and living as one. Am I so different from you that you cannot dispel with your status. and look at my face?. Am I so distant from you that I cannot break free from this stereotype today?. Am I so separate from you that you cannot regard me as equal. and clean this stain?    </segment4>
	</english>
</song>
