<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Ships In The Night </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>She dont know what she wants to be. With all the pictures in the magazines. Holding hands when shes mad at me. Cause she dont wanna go dont wanna go. I met her at anthropology. Her purple boots and her golden dreams. Standing there like a Tennesse Queen. Singing dont look at me dont look at me</segment1>
		<segment2>Singing Oh Oh wont you help me sing this song. Singing The EEE EEE she dont ever wanna go to sleep</segment2>
		<segment3>. Singing Hey Mama dont want no drama just a kiss before I leave (Woo Ohhhh). Hey lady dont say maybe youre the one that I can believe (Woo Ohhhh). Hey lover dont want no other. Finger for my ring (Woo Ohhhh). Hey mama hey hey mama (X4). Oh Oh O O O O Oh. Oh Oh O O Oh </segment3>
		<segment4>I could see it in her Cherokee eyes. Those baby browns and her golden thighs. What you doing for the rest of your life. Cause I dont wanna go, dont wanna go</segment4>
		<segment5>Singing Oh Oh wont you help me sing this song. Singing EEE EEE EEE she's playing like a mystery</segment5>
		<segment6>Singing Hey Mama dont want no drama just a kiss before I leave (Woo Ohhhh). Hey lady dont say maybe youre the one that I can believe (Woo Ohhhh). Hey lover dont want no other. Finger for my ring (Woo Ohhhh). Hey mama hey hey mama X4. Oh Oh O O O O Oh. Oh Oh O O Oh O O O-Oh </segment6>
		<segment7>We couldnt be more opposite. Im hard to please and your hard to get. Youre Mississippi and Im Oregon. Youre sun tanned and Im porcelain</segment7>
		<segment8>Singing Hey Mama dont want no drama just a kiss before I leave (Woo Ohhhh). Hey lady dont say maybe youre the one that I can believe(Woo Ohhhh). Hey lover dont want no other. Finger for my ring (Woo Ohhhh). Hey mama hey hey mama X4. (alright). Oh oh, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh oh    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
