<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Signs Of Life </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Come in base, I've landed my ship on a planet here in space. This is the one they say is inhabited by the human race. And I'm going out to look around and see what's here. And I'll tell you what I find. Confirmation on the inhabitants, they're running everywhere. Their technology is beyond what I've seen anywhere. But I'm trying to communicate, but they don't hear me. Seems like for all I'm finding, I can't find the most important thing</segment1>
		<segment2>Where are the signs, where are the signs of life. The love that proves there is a beating heart inside. Where are the signs, where are the signs of life. The compassion and concern, that make this world turn. Where are the signs of life</segment2>
		<segment3>Now I've got crayons rolling around in the floorboard of my car. Bicycles all over my driveway, bats and balls all over my yard. And there's a plastic man from outer space sitting in my chair. The signs of life are everywhere. But I've got questions rolling around in the corners of my mind. And if it's true, I live in a world where hope has all but died. And if I really have a living love alive in me. How am I letting it be known, how am I letting it be seen?</segment3>
		<segment4>These are the signs, these are the signs of life. The love that proves there is a living faith inside. These are the signs, these are the signs of life. The compassion and concern, that make this world turn. These are the signs of life. Signs of Life</segment4>
		<segment5>These are the signs, these are the signs, these are the signs of life. The love that proves there is a living faith inside. These are the signs, these are the signs, these are the signs of life. The compassion and concern. Thats gonna make this world keep turning. These are the signs of life. A love thats flowing from the heart. Where the grace of God has left its mark. These are the signs of life. The reaching out of a servants hand. The giving that makes no demands</segment5>
		<segment6>These are the signs. This is loving proof of the faith inside. These are the signs of life.     </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
