<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Sioux Lane Spirits </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Daddy, she has your eyes. And when she grins you can only realize. The guilt she manifests so deep inside you. That your thin veneer of catechism can no longer hide. The voice you hear, her secret pain. As she digs the shiv into her placid veins</segment1>
		<segment2>Now she has your eyes. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. But she can't yet realize. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. Your ever wayward eyes. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. Will be her demise. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted</segment2>
		<segment3>You slipped into another, forbidden. Took her for the ride, you've ridden. Hoping to let her deep inside your disdain. What was it that drove your feign. Into another's arms, into another's bed. When all the while your young one waits up in dread. What was it? Was it something she did?. What was it? Was it something she said?</segment3>
		<segment4>Now she has your eyes. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. But she can't yet realize. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. Your ever wayward eyes. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. Will be her demise. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted</segment4>
		<segment5>Writhe and burn father you were (6x)</segment5>
		<segment6>She dances in the moonlight. Collecting drops of the earthy dew. Celebrating her exit.  From the benign sense of self she once knew. Raising her heavy glass. (Raising her heavy glass). Her cup now spills on her skirt. And as she cuts her knees in the dirt. She prays for the hourglass to flip and reverse</segment6>
		<segment7>Now she has your eyes. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. But she can't yet realize. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. Your ever wayward eyes. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted. Will be her demise. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted</segment7>
		<segment8>Now she has your eyes. Something you wanted, you wanted, something you wanted, you wanted (2x)</segment8>
		<segment9>Writhe and burn father you were (2x)    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
