<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Socially Acceptable </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1> [its okay, its all right]</segment1>
		<segment2>Its okay, its alright. Yeah, here we go. Dct is in the house boy. Its okay, its alright</segment2>
		<segment3>Whatcha thinking, doing the things you do. Whose opinion are ya listening to?. Justifying, you turn it all to gray. Synchronizing to societys ways</segment3>
		<segment4>Society has gotten to be all outta whack. And dont bother with excuses whether white or. black. To blame it on a color wont get a result. Because history reveals to me how ethics were. lost. In reality our decency has taken a plunge. &quot;in God we trust&quot; is an american pun. Funny how it happened so suddenly. Hey yo fellas, kick the melody..</segment4>
		<segment5>(chorus). Socially acceptable, its okay, its all right. Socially acceptable, its okay, in whose sight. Socially acceptable</segment5>
		<segment6>Times are changing, with morals in decay. Human rights have made the wrongs okay. Somethings missing, and if youre asking me. I think that something is the g-o-d</segment6>
		<segment7>To label wrong or right by the peoples sight. Is like going to a loser to ask advice. And by basing your plans. On another mans way of living life. Is creating a brand of ethics. Sure to be missing the punch. No count morals that are out to lunch. Theyre sliding away cause everything is okay. It was taboo back then but today ya say, &quot;what the hey&quot;</segment7>
		<segment8>(repeat chorus)</segment8>
		<segment9>Yeah, yeah, yeah. Here we go, here we go. A come on, a come on. Here we go, here we go. A come on, a come on. Here we go, here we go. A come on, a come on. Here we go, here we go. A come on, a come on</segment9>
		<segment10>Everybodys doin it. Whos doin it. Everybodys doin it. Yo, whos doin it. Everybodys doin it. Whos doin it. Everybodys doin it. Yo, yo, yo, whos doin it. Ohhhh, alright. Ohhhh, come on</segment10>
		<segment11>(bridge). We gotta back to the principles found in the. word. A little g-o-d could be societys cure. From the state that were in cause again were. slipping. So pray for america cause time is ticking</segment11>
		<segment12>(repeat chorus 2x)</segment12>
		<segment13>Socially respectable. Socially acceptable. Socially respectable    </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
