<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Soft Skeletons </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Dear little girl, so much hurt for such a young age. Trapped inside a pretty little lie. Your bodies betrayed. </segment1>
		<segment2>Don't fix your eyes on a fix you rely on. Fixed her eyes on a fix she relies upon. </segment2>
		<segment3>Stand unafraid, all the good souls stand on unafraid. </segment3>
		<segment4>When life starts to burn, and the pain returns. I just wish that I could heal the hurt you feel tonight. There's life in your veins. These needles are chains to hold you down. How can you expect to win this war?. Too afraid to fight. Are you too afraid to fight? </segment4>
		<segment5>Dear little one, there was so much pain. Time you can't replace. Trapped inside, too afraid to cry. And now hands and bruises cover face. </segment5>
		<segment6>Don't fix your eyes on a fix you rely on. Fixed her eyes on a fix.. </segment6>
		<segment7>When life starts to burn, and the pain returns. I just wish that I could heal the hurt you feel tonight. There's life in your veins. These needles are chains to hold you down. How can you expect to win this war if you're too afraid to fight? </segment7>
		<segment8>Stand unafraid. All the good souls stand unafraid. Stand unafraid, all the good souls stand unafraid. </segment8>
		<segment9>When life starts to burn, and the pain returns. I just wish that I could heal the hurt you feel tonight. There's life in your veins. These needles are chains to hold you down. How can you expect to win this war if you're too afraid to fight?. When life starts to burn, and the pain returns. I just wish that I could heal the hurt you feel tonight. There's life in your veins. These needles are chains to hold you down. How can you expect to win this war if you're too afraid to fight?.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
