<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Somewhere Down The Road </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>So much pain and no good reason why. You've cried until the tears run dry. And nothing here can make you understand. The one thing that you held so dear. Is slipping from your hands, and you say</segment1>
		<segment2>Why, why, why. Does it go this way. And why, why, why. And all I can say</segment2>
		<segment3>Is somewhere down the road. There'll be answers to the questions. And somewhere down the road. Tho' we cannot see it now</segment3>
		<segment4>Somewhere down the road. You will find mighty arms reaching for you. And they will hold the answers. At the end of the road</segment4>
		<segment5>Yesterday, I thought I'd seen it all. I thought I'd climbed the highest wall. Now I see the learning never ends. And all I know to do is keep on walking. Walking 'round the bend singing</segment5>
		<segment6>Why, why, why. Does it go this way. And why, why, why. And all I can say</segment6>
		<segment7>Is somewhere down the road. There'll be answers to the questions. And somewhere down the road. Tho' we cannot see it now</segment7>
		<segment8>Somewhere down the road. You will find mighty arms reaching for you. And they will hold the answers. At the end of the road</segment8>
		<segment9>Oh, keep on walking</segment9>
		<segment10>Why, why, why. Does it go this way. And why, why, why. And all I can say. All I know to say now</segment10>
		<segment11>Somewhere down the road. There'll be answers to the questions. And somewhere down the road. Tho' we cannot see it now</segment11>
		<segment12>Somewhere down the road. You will find mighty arms reaching for you. And they will hold the answers. At the end of the road. Oh, they will hold the answers. At the end of the road</segment12>
		<segment13>Oh, keep on walking, oh</segment13>
		<segment14>Oh, walking down the road. Walking down the road</segment14>
		<segment15>Somewhere down this lonely road. I can't see you know. Down the road, the lonely road. Somewhere down, somewhere down    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
