<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Sometimes You Can Forget Who You Are </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Every day I get a little closer to, The things that I wanna, say with my life, In no particular order. I'd like to make some sort of mark, So that the world knows I was here.. </segment1>
		<segment2>And I've been thinkin' about, How I could scream it out loud, Or paint a picture somehow, A thousand miles long. And I've been tryin' 'till now, These walls are freakin' me out, Just need to let it all out, And reach out, Because sometimes, you can forget who you are</segment2>
		<segment3>I'm tired of trying to make it, I've spent so many nights, Tryin' to get it all right, oh-oh-oh. I'm sick and tired of waiting, For someone to see, and start believing in me, Oh-oh-oh. But I know I'm not out here on my own.. </segment3>
		<segment4>Every year I get a little farther from, Old misconceptions, that take the place, Of mistakes and lessons, There's things I've learned from, Things I've been burned from, It's part of who I am</segment4>
		<segment5>And I've been thinkin' about, How I could scream it out loud, Or paint a picture somehow, A thousand miles long. And I've been tryin' 'till now, These walls are freakin' me out, Just need to let it all out, And reach out, Because sometimes, you can forget who you are</segment5>
		<segment6>I'm tired of trying to make it, I've spent so many nights, Tryin' to get it all right, oh-oh-oh. I'm sick and tired of waiting, For someone to see, and start believing in me, Oh-oh-oh. But I know I'm not out here on my own.. </segment6>
		<segment7>There's been a lot of people, Think I'm goin' no where, Times that by ten, for every time I felt like turnin' around, But everytime you said push on. And keep your head up, Kept me on track from letting myself get fed up</segment7>
		<segment8>I'm tired of trying to make it, I've spent so many nights, Tryin' to get it all right, oh-oh-oh. I'm sick and tired of waiting, For someone to see, and start believing in me, Oh-oh-oh. But I know I'm not out here on my own..    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
