<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Something Big </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>[Verse 1:]. Hey hey hey hey everybody. I got something to say. I met this man named Jesus. And I ain't never been the same. You know my heart's been changed, My mind's been changed. I'm nothing like I was. Cause I was stuck on stupid. But now I'm filled with love</segment1>
		<segment2>[Chorus:]. You know something big done happened to me. (Something big done happened to me). And I gotta tell the world about it. (I gotta tell the world about it). Cause if I keep it to myself. (If I keep it to myself). How you gon' find out about it. (How you gon' find out about it). Jesus took the worst of me. (Jesus took the worst of me). And helped me get myself together. (And helped me get myself together). The greatest man in history. (The greatest man in history). And can't nobody do it better. (Can't nobody do it better)</segment2>
		<segment3>Oh noooo</segment3>
		<segment4>[Verse 2:]. If your soul is sinking. And feeling like your lost. Don't know who to turn to. Then let's go to the cross. Jesus bled, and Jesus died, And Jesus took the fall. For all your wrong. And all my wrong. Jesus pitied all</segment4>
		<segment5>[Chorus:]</segment5>
		<segment6>[Bridge:]. Tell me what you know about Jesus. He's alright. Anybody know about Jesus. He's alright. Tell me what you know about Jesus. He's alright. Hey, what ya'll know about Jesus. He's alright</segment6>
		<segment7>[Chorus:]</segment7>
		<segment8>[Vamp:]. Now help me say hey, hey, hey. Everybody lift your voice and say. Hey, hey, hey. Put your hands together say. Hey, hey, hey. If God's been good somebody say. Hey, hey, hey. Come on put them hands together. Put them hands together. Put them hands together. Put them hands together. Come on, come one, come on, come on.     </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
