<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>So Sweet </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Verse 1: As I look at the life of Jesus. and compare my life to Jesus I fall short. though I know that I would like to please Him. as may reasonable service and worship Him with my whole heart. and I think I speak for all believers. when I say we need Jesus to lead us or we will fall apart. cause ever since Adam fell from eating. fruit from the tree our deeds have been evil thats why we love the dark. and great men throughout Biblical history. officially can see we are sinners and need a new start. and if your fire is dwindling and you need a rekindling. get rid of that hindering and get this new spark. I thank the Father for Jesus He didnt leave us. as heathens He made us His sheep and placed in us a new heart. now were just simply receiving and believing. what Hes achieving and achieved that evening bleeding upon the cross</segment1>
		<segment2>Hook: (Dawn Dia) Hes so sweet the way He loves me and holds me so closely and toasty Hell never let me go and so I gotta serve Him give Him the props deserved live life by His word and Hes so sweet He gives me favor and flavor taste of my Savior a taste that should savored fo sho I gotta love Him and trust Him live my life for Him Hes so sweet</segment2>
		<segment3>Verse 2: And I can even hear them angels rejoice in that angelic voice when the prodigal son returned to the fathers house its so amazin it make me picture the Fathers love for the lost now nothin but praises are comin out my mouth look at this life and begin to forsake it and chase after His heart like David after salvation without a doubt cause the only escape from the sin nature is the sacredness of salvation just start takin the narrow route this opportunity is in unity with the tri-unity of His nature for you indeed just to holler out I see my sin and I need a Savior to take me away from myself to mold and shape me at the Potters house begin to make me like Jesus and then Ill take it.     </segment3>
	</english>
</song>
