<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Speechless </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>My words fall like drops of rain. My lips are like clouds. I've said so many things. Trying to figure you out. As mercy opens my eyes. my words are stolen away. At this breathtaking view of your grace</segment1>
		<segment2>And I am speechless, I'm astonished and amazed. I am silenced by your wondrous grace. You have saved me. You have raised me from the grave. And I am speechless in your presence now. I'm astounded as I consider how. You have shown us. A love that leaves us speechless</segment2>
		<segment3>So what kind of love can this be. That will trade heaven's throne for a cross. To think that you still celebrate. For finding just one who was lost. To know you rejoice over us. The God of this whole universe. It's a story too great for words</segment3>
		<segment4>And I am speechless, I'm astonished and amazed. I am silenced by your wondrous grace. You have saved me. You have raised me from the grave. And I am speechless in your presence now. I'm astounded as I consider how. You have shown us. A love that leaves us speechless. We are speechless</segment4>
		<segment5>Oh, how great is the love. The Father has lavished upon us. That we should be called. The sons and the daughters of God</segment5>
		<segment6>We are speechless. (We stand in awe of your grace). so amazed. (We stand in awe of your mercy). You have saved us. (We stand in awe of your love). from the grave. (We are speechless)</segment6>
		<segment7>We are speechless, I'm astonished and amazed. I am silenced by your wondrous grace. You have saved me. You have raised me from the grave. And I am speechless in your presence now. I'm astounded as I consider how. You have shown us. A love that leaves us speechless</segment7>
		<segment8>We stand in awe of your cross. We stand in awe of your power. We are speechless. We stand in awe of your grace. We stand in awe of your mercy. We stand in awe of your love. We are speechless </segment8>
		<segment9>    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
