<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Start Jumpin' </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Everybody in the place state jumpin' </segment1>
		<segment2>Everybody in the place start jumpin'. Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump </segment2>
		<segment3>Get up get on your feet </segment3>
		<segment4>Everybody dancin' along. (Everybody in the place start jumpin'). Sun up till the sun goes down. Everybody singin' the song. (Start Jumpin'). It starts in your heart </segment4>
		<segment5>It's keepin' us movin' yeah. We're all together now. So come on everybody go. Chorus </segment5>
		<segment6>Start Jumpin' (Hey) </segment6>
		<segment7>To the sound of the music pumpin' (Ho). Throw your hands in the air get thumpin' (Hey). And I want you to go jump, jump, Start, jump, start, start jumpin'. To the sound of the music pumpin' (Ho). Throw your hands in the air get thumpin' (Hey). And I want you to go jump, jump, Start, jump, start, start jumpin'. Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump. We're dancin' day and night </segment7>
		<segment8>Gonna keep it movin' along. (Everybody in the place start jumpin'). Don't let life pass you by. The groove is where you belong. (Start Jumpin'). Now is the time </segment8>
		<segment9>So capture the moment yeah. We're all together now. So come on everybody go. Chorus </segment9>
		<segment10>Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, </segment10>
		<segment11>Everybody in the place start jumpin'. Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Everybody in the place start jumpin'. Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Everybody in the place start jumpin'. Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, Jump, We're gonna reach up high go side to side </segment11>
		<segment12>We're gonna raise the roof. Throw your hands up. Then I wanna see you bounce. Jumpin' up and down everybody in the house. Stand up (Stand up). We're all just the same. Get down (Get down). We're gonna do it again. Everybody in the room. Everybody out there. Everybody everywhere. Throw your hand in the air. It starts in your heart </segment12>
		<segment13>It's keepin' us movin' yeah. We're all together now. So come everybody go. Chorus 2x </segment13>
		<segment14>Everybody in the place start jumpin' Start jumpin'.     </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
