<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Stationary Stationery </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Do they not have pen or paper where you are?. 'Cause I haven't heard from you in ages. I relive each memory. From time to time. With notes exchanged. With all the scented pages. It's comin back. It's all comin back to me now</segment1>
		<segment2>Tell me everything turned out alright. 'Cause I'm well and we said. That we'd meet tonight. Does he treat you like you want. Does he ask to take your hand. Does he believe in dreams we talked about. Though with no music we dance</segment2>
		<segment3>I thought you said that you'd come find me. I thought you said you'd be home by now. I heard you say that you'd come back here. So I wrote to remind you somehow..</segment3>
		<segment4>Dance by yourself and. Think of me when you do. I'm not sure you understand. What this means to me. What you do to me. I'm willing to prove. That you're the one. I regret to slip away. Now I know it was only you. That I've been searchin for. And missin all this time</segment4>
		<segment5>I thought you said that you'd come find me. I thought you said you'd be home by now. I heard you say that you'd come back here. So I wrote to remind you somehow..</segment5>
		<segment6>I thought you said that you'd come find me. I thought you said you'd be home by now. I heard you say that you'd come back here. So I wrote to remind you somehow..</segment6>
		<segment7>Let the past be past. Let's start today. And let us both do. I need to see your face. Tell me where to be. I'll tell you why we shouldn't be. (I'll tell you why we shouldn't be)</segment7>
		<segment8>I thought you said that you'd come find me. I thought you said you'd be home by now. I heard you say that you'd come back here. So I wrote to remind you somehow..</segment8>
		<segment9>I thought you said that you'd come find me. I thought you said you'd be home by now. I heard you say that you'd come back here. So I wrote to remind you somehow..    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
