<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Stay in the Light </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Well you can tell by the way I used to walk. I was once a man with no time for God. Knew about the risen Lord. But didn't check Him out till I got bored. And then I saw the light; I got saved. I used to look for other ways. But given time, I'd understand. I knew the Bible had the plan. Whether you're in trouble or livin' in a bubble. You stay in the light, say in the light. Even when you're shaken you're never God-forsaken. Just stay in the light, stay in the light. Ah, ah, ah, ah stay in the light, stay in the light. Ah, ah, ah, ah stay in the light. Well, the Bible was divinely inspired. And if you can't believe it, you need to try. Got the things of Heaven all can use. And a plan for man where you just can't lose. You now, it's all right, it's O.K. He'll let you be your stubborn way. But Jesus Christ is comin', man. I know your times are in His hands. Whether you're in trouble or livin' in a bubble. You stay in the light, say in the light. Even when you're shaken you'll never fall to Satan. If you stay in the light, stay in the light. Ah, ah, ah, ah stay in the light, stay in the light. Ah, ah, ah, ah stay in the light. I'm gonna show ya Psalm hundred-nineteen. The Bible is your lamp. I'm gonna show ya the Bible is your lamp. So stay in the light!. Well you can tell by the way I used to walk. I was once a man with no time for God. And you may doubt that it's for sure. But I'm a Christian now since I'm reborn. And now, it's all right, it's O.K. And you may look for other ways. You need the light to understand. So use your Bible as your lamp. Whether you're in trouble or livin' in a bubble. You stay in the light, say in the light. Even when you're shaken Ephesians 5 verse 8 says . Just stay in the light, stay in the light. Ah, ah, ah, ah stay in the light, stay in the light. Ah, ah, ah, ah stay in the light. I'm gonna show ya Psalm hundred-nineteen. The Bible is your lamp. I'm gonna show ya the Bible is your lamp. So stay in the light!</segment1>
		<segment2>.     </segment2>
	</english>
</song>
