<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Stressed Out </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Intro: The pressures of life got me thinking again. What ticked you off today, your boss, girlfriend, that same idiot at school? </segment1>
		<segment2>This world makes me upset like a bomb threat, my palms sweat I wanna get off it locked down Like an alcoholic cant give it up, Take what you get in life sip lick it up. Cause yo Ive gone crazy dear God can you save me I need a solution Im hallucinating lately. Something gone wrong in my brain chasm assault. And battering embarrassing this world I aint cherishing. You shot the heroin I lacked the parenting, Inherit the kingdom like the sin syndrome. Vision blurry focus in on your brokenness loneliness stuck up in societys hopelessness </segment2>
		<segment3>Take me home God, I wanna quit my job, I hide in camouflage let loose in dialogue, If its working out I wish youd hear me now if so Ill trust in you without a doubt. </segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus. Cause every time cause every time I get Stressed Out!!!. Cause every time cause every time I get Stressed Out!!! </segment4>
		<segment5>I wonder what would happen if I really spoke mind to every individual critical situation with you. You thought I was a quiet person, now its not for certain smiling in your face really cursing. If it wasnt for Christ I might of react detached make you see black send you into relapse, I relax And check my posture pray to my God father, got a lot of stress try to find a place to rest. I never let the chemicals wrestle with my blood vessels, push ethical take care of your medical its Evident the pressures of life have got me thinking again I sin frequent again, I isnt drinking it in. I separate hate give my heart an x-ray, check the next day before it escalates, severance pay was Not an option kick me out cause my droors are dropping. Got this talent locking, and Im stress talking. </segment5>
		<segment6>I cant take it I got to get out. The stress is to hot, Im a jet out. I cant take it yall I got to get out. The stress is too hot, Im a jet out </segment6>
		<segment7>Im not lost Ive just got some issues, Im not artificial cause Im just being real with you. Its just one of those days you dont say, tick me off start a fire like foreplay. Ill visuals my lifes circumstance trapped like circus ants nervous and Im. Stressed check my third eye serve the most high. So why you caught up blame how youre brought up. What you done with your life show your product. I remain speechless not the same fetus reborn with an attitude receive how I speak this. Why you need a joint or else you sleepless stress it plus you un-rested. Quest for life in Christ I dont regret it, Its Babylon, stress guns and nylons, They dead two buildings I pray for Gods children.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
