<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Studying Politics </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It's like a pencil with erasers at both ends. I want it all but we're dealing in process. And these activities that you have engaged in. This is the politics of seeing you dance with him. We began with concluding remarks. Break up the pieces and examine the parts. Your words always cut when their cliche. But here's my knife because I came for the buffet</segment1>
		<segment2>[Chorus]. This is the way it goes. With you a part of it. Nervously saying words. That are so tightly fit. A mark beneath the chin (Uh Uh). I've caught you once again. It's in the way you sell every word and phrase. And leaving me to know how much the meaning weighs. Saying that but meaning this (Uh Uh). Using hands for emphasis. (Oh Ho) [x7]</segment2>
		<segment3>You'd like to think that you're the best part of me. But I confess there is nothing left of you here (nothing left of you here). These parallels and silly games. Hide your face and say the name. Say the name (say the name)</segment3>
		<segment4>[Chorus]. This is the way it goes. With you a part of it. Nervously saying words. That are so tightly fit. A mark beneath the chin (Uh Uh). And I've caught you once again. It's in the way you sell every word and phrase. And leaving me to know how much the meaning weighs. Saying that but meaning this (Uh Uh). Your tears for emphasis</segment4>
		<segment5>(Ahhhh). There's that smile again (there's that smile again). You fake it and I follow you right in. What a fool again. To fall for it each time</segment5>
		<segment6>[Chorus]. This is the way it goes. With you a part of it. Nervously saying words. That are so tightly fit. It's in the way you sell every word and phrase. And leaving me to know how much the meaning weighs. This is the way it goes. With you a part of it. Nervously saying words. That are so tightly fit. It's in the way you sell every word and phrase. And leaving me to know how much the meaning weighs. (Oh Ho) [x5]</segment6>
		<segment7>[Outro]. Black Dress and your eyes are telling white white lies. White white lies. Black Dress and your eyes are telling white white lies. White white lies.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
