<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Take A Step (1, 2, 3) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It was on a Tuesday night. When I saw you passin' by. When you came my way in your eyes. I could see the pain inside. Then you looked at me and tried to smile. I asked what's wrong?. You said my life </segment1>
		<segment2>So I asked can we talk about.. Every little thing that's on your mind. Every little thing that makes you cry. Let me tell you all about.. Every little thing that's on my heart. God's given me a brand new start. It's as easy as.. </segment2>
		<segment3>1, 2, 3, take a step toward me. I can see you're hurting. You could be so free. In a flash you could start all over. Let me know if you wanna go there. We're just hanging out. We can talk about it </segment3>
		<segment4>You said that's cool, but not for you. And you walked away. I tried my best, I gave my all. What else could I say?. As you crossed the street. By chance you meet an angel in disguise. Supernatural meeting of modern times </segment4>
		<segment5>She knew. Every little thing that just occured. Every little way you've been disturbed. Every little thing that has been wrong. Faith in God has kept her strong. Just take a step </segment5>
		<segment6>1, 2, 3, take a step toward me. I can see you're hurting. You could be so free. In a flash it could all be over. Let me know if you wanna go there. We're just hanging out. We can talk about it. 1, 2, 3, take a step with me. I can see you're hurting. He can set you free. In a flash you could start all over. Let me know if you wanna go there. We're just hanging out. We can talk about it </segment6>
		<segment7>You know what you gotta do. Don't wanna confuse, but you gotta choose. You know you got nothing to lose. Don't refuse, don't refuse, yeah. You know what you gotta do. Life's already got you singing the blues. You know you've got nothing to lose. Don't refuse, take a step. It's so simple, so what you waitin' on? </segment7>
		<segment8>1, 2, 3, take a step toward me. I can see you're hurting. You could be so free. In a flash it could all be over. Let me know if you wanna go there. We're just hanging out. We can talk about it. 1, 2, 3, take a step with me. I can see you're hurting. He can set you free. In a flash you could start all over. Let me know if you wanna go there. We're just hanging out </segment8>
		<segment9>.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
