<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Tell Me Something Good </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Hey what you got you don't know. Anything that I'm gonna say right now. Cuz I'm not so sure why I'm here and why I wanna. Keep on hanging 'round right now. Not that I do it now or any day. Sometimes I just get burned out. About lots of things and well just doubt</segment1>
		<segment2>So tell me something good you got it and. Why am I so misunderstood cuz I wanna know this. Cuz I'm confused and do I break into two. So tell me how about you</segment2>
		<segment3>Hey what you got something bad and I want it. Even though I know its wrong. But I won't be blessed cuz I know this so I can't have that. So I like a show I gotta be strong. Man I don't wanna be able to breathe. Be able to see what's become. of the wars of this world. and the wars from my tongue</segment3>
		<segment4>So tell me something good you got it and. Why am I so misunderstood cuz I wanna know this. Cuz I'm confused and I bruise yes I do so tell me how about you. So tell me something good you got it and. Why am I so misunderstood cuz I wanna know this. Come on baby and race me and maybe we can find ourselves</segment4>
		<segment5>I wanna be I wanna be like that mountain. I wanna stand taller and bigger than rest. See I just wanna be it a guy who wins all the time. I wanna be a big star a king and rule my own life. And God I know that it's wrong. So please just make my heart right. Inside and destroy my pride</segment5>
		<segment6>So you can tell me something good you got it and. Why I am so misunderstood cuz I wanna know this. Cuz I'm confused and I bruise yes I do so tell how about you. So please just tell me something good you got it and. Why am I so misunderstood cuz I wanna know this. Come on baby and race me and maybe we'll just find ourselves</segment6>
		<segment7>Hey what you got something bad and I want it. Even though I know it's wrong    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
