<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>That's What I Believe [Live] </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Lord, You promised if I keep my mind on You, You'd keep me in perfect peace </segment1>
		<segment2>Choir. (Yes you would, you'd keep me in perfect peace) </segment2>
		<segment3>With a sincere heart if I called upon Your name. You'd never turn away from me </segment3>
		<segment4>Choir. (No, no you'd never turn away from me) </segment4>
		<segment5>Said you'd give me everything I need </segment5>
		<segment6>Choir. (You'd give me everything i need) </segment6>
		<segment7>I came for deliverance. Deliverance I'll receive. You said You'd deliver me. And that's what I believe </segment7>
		<segment8>So now every promise is mine, Lord (It's mine). I claim it (Oh yes, I know It's mine). By faith I receive it it's mine (It's mine). Won't leave here like I came ; I'm never gonna be the same. I know (It's mine). By faith I believe I believe (Oh yes, I know It's mine). Reach out and receive now (It's mine). Won't leave here like I came; I'm never gonna be the same. You can be saved just say </segment8>
		<segment9>I came for salvation, Lord. Salvation I'll receive. You said You would save me, Lord. And that's what I believe </segment9>
		<segment10>I came just to hear Your word. Your word will I receive. You said You world send Your word. And that's what I believe </segment10>
		<segment11>So down in my heart I know (It's mine). I do believe it ( Oh, yes. I know it's mine). I heard all your promises (it's mine). Won't leave here like I came; I'm never gonna be the same. I know, I know (It's mine) </segment11>
		<segment12>Healing (Oh, yes. I know it's mine). The provision for me (It's mine). Won't leave here like I came; I'm never gonna be the same. Yes (It's mine). You need to know (Oh yes. I know It's mine). Believe all the promises (It's Mine). Won't leave here like I came; I'm never gonna be the same </segment12>
		<segment13>Somebody help me say (It's mine). Come on and help me say (Oh yes. I know it's mine). Somebody help me say (It's mine) </segment13>
		<segment14>I came for your healings Lord. Your healings I'll recieve. You said you would heal me Lord. And that's what I believe </segment14>
		<segment15>I came for deliverance. Deliverance I'll recieve. You said you would deliver me. And that's what I believe. (I believe, I believe). And that's what I believe. (I believe, I recieve). And that's what I believe. (Lord I look down no doubt I no). And that's what I believe. (That's what I believe). And that's what I believe     </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
