<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>That's What You Get </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>No sir. Well I don't wanna be the blame, not anymore. It's your turn to take a seat. We're settling the final score</segment1>
		<segment2>And why do we like to hurt so much?</segment2>
		<segment3>I can't decide. You have made it harder just to go on. And why, all the possibilities. Well I was wrong</segment3>
		<segment4>That's what you get when you let your heart win, woah. That's what you get when you let your heart win, woah. I drowned out all my sense with the sound of its beating. And that's what you get when you let your heart win, woah</segment4>
		<segment5>I wonder. How am I supposed to feel when you're not here?. Cuz I've burned every bridge I ever built. When you were here</segment5>
		<segment6>I still try</segment6>
		<segment7>Holding on to silly things, I never learn. Oh why, all the possibilities. I'm sure you've heard</segment7>
		<segment8>That's what you get when you let your heart win, woah. That's what you get when you let your heart win, woah. I drowned out all my sense with the sound of its beating (beating). And that's what you get when you let your heart win, woah</segment8>
		<segment9>Hey, make your way to me, to me. And I'll always be just so inviting (so inviting). If I ever start to think straight. This heart will start a riot in me. Let's start, start - hey!</segment9>
		<segment10>Why do we like to hurt so much?. Oh, why do we like to hurt so much?. That's what you get when you let your heart win, woah</segment10>
		<segment11>That's what you get when you let your heart win, woah. That's what you get when you let your heart win, woah. Now I can't trust myself with anything but this. And that's what you get when you let your heart win, woah    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
