<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Art of Falling Off </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Intro: I can't do it anymore, it's just me and the pen now</segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus: I know the pressure's in the air. A half a million spent and yet you act like you don't care. Cause I've seen and read just how easy it is. Just throw a rap onto a beat and that's the record biz. I know..</segment2>
		<segment3>Come my way, come my way. Up in the place, my label wants a hit song. So I can blow up like Mase. And that's easy right?. Just put a little rap upon the beat. And just freak it until it's tight. Throw a hook on it. Boom there you go. Cast it into the lake of consumerism. And bloom it's that easy. It's like 1,2,3, bingo check my new single. Look at Pigeon John as he sings and dance. They don't even understand that I have wet my pants. With a demented grin I just shake their hands. Then go back to the studio and wait for chance</segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus</segment4>
		<segment5>I know the pressure's in the air. A half a million spent and yet you act like you don't care. Cause I've seen and read just how easy it is. Just throw a rap onto a beat and that's the record biz. And now I'm falling. Don't know what to do now. And now I'm falling. Where the heck is my crew now. And now I'm falling</segment5>
		<segment6>Oh and what am I to do?. When my head's drained and dry. With no point of view?. I'll just..well forget it, I'll just do what I did. To get me in the first place when I was I kid. I'll make a song about cheerleaders, Cadillacs, Silverlake, White girls, jealousy which then turns to hate, Trader Joe's, ex-girlfriends, and cheap clothes. Swingers at three and never do forget &quot;Oooh Weee&quot;. And plus insecurity is the key. When they're marketing me to society. And I'm broke but that's good for publicity. Cause it shows the human side of buying my cd</segment6>
		<segment7>Chorus    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
