<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Bitter Uprising </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>If you listen to the sound of the hope. In the children's voices asking questions. You'll know how blindness is a blessing. But I know your type, you're always right, your tongue controls your mind. But I guess life's the lesson </segment1>
		<segment2>If they said 40 years I would die before. I let them take the love that I have paid for with my tears. And now the time has come to cut our tongues out. And commit ourselves as you did in your memory </segment2>
		<segment3>We'll tear down the walls and let them know. We could have it all, we could have some hope. This city could be ours by nightfall </segment3>
		<segment4>Do you hear the war drums beating?. Are you truly happy doing nothing, darling?. I need to find the center. Because love is something right, it's not cooked up overnight. In sticky situations you try. But less is more forever </segment4>
		<segment5>If they said 40 years I would die before. I let them take the love that I have paid for with my tears. And now the time has come to cut our tongues out. And commit ourselves as you did in your memory </segment5>
		<segment6>We'll tear down the walls and let them know. We could have it all, we could have some hope. This city could be ours by nightfall, nightfall. We'll tear down the walls and let them know. We could have it all, we could have some hope. This city could be ours by nightfall </segment6>
		<segment7>The minute I was born, you stole my heart. The minute I was born, you stole my heart. The minute I was born, you stole my heart. The minute I was born, the minute I was born </segment7>
		<segment8>Tear down the walls and let them know. We could go all night, we could just stay home. This city could be ours by nightfall, nightfall. Tear down the walls and let them know. We could have it all, we could have some hope. This city could be ours by nightfall    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
