<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Beautiful Letdown </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>It was a beautiful letdown. When I crashed and burned. When I found myself alone, unknown and hurt. It was a beautiful letdown. The day I knew, That all the riches this world had to offer me will never do. </segment1>
		<segment2>In a world full of bitter pain, and bitter doubts, I was trying so hard to fit in, Fit in, until I found out </segment2>
		<segment3>I don't belong here (I don't belong). I don't belong here (I don't belong). I will carry a cross and a song. Where I don't belong. I don't belong </segment3>
		<segment4>It was a beautiful letdown. When you found me here. Yeah, for once in a rare blue moon. I see everything clear. I'll be a beautiful letdown. That's what I'll forever be. And though it may cost my soul. I'll sing for free </segment4>
		<segment5>We're still chasing our tails. In the rising sun. In our dark water planet still spinning. In a direction no one wins. No one's won. </segment5>
		<segment6>See, I don't belong here (I don't belong). Well, I don't belong here, I don't belong. I will carry a cross. With a song where I don't belong. I don't belong. I don't belong here (I don't belong). No, I don't belong here, I don't belong. I'm gonna set side. And set sail. For the kingdom come, kingdom come. Your kingdom come. Won't you let me down, yeah. Let my foolish pride forever let me down </segment6>
		<segment7>Ah, Easy living, you're not much like the name. Easy dying, you look just about the same. Would you please take me off your list. Easy living please c'mon and let me down </segment7>
		<segment8>We are a beautiful letdown. Painfully uncool. The church of the dropouts. The losers, the sinners, the failures, and the fools. What a beautiful letdown. Are we salt in the wound. Hey, let us sing one true tune </segment8>
		<segment9>I don't belong here (I don't belong). It feels like I don't belong here, yeah. It goes like I don't belong here. I don't belong (I don't belong). Won't you let me down (I don't belong). C'mon and let me down (I don't belong). You always let me down (I don't belong). So glad that I'm let down (I don't belong). C'mon and let me down (I don't belong). Cuz I don't belong here. Won't you let me down!    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
