<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Center </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I got a feeling as a matter of fact. It's like my whole world just came under attack. And I hear a voice tellin' me to turn back. 혩Cause I must be onto somethin'. It happens every single time I get close to. Everything I know is good and right and so true. It's like somebody doesn't want me to love You. And I must be onto somethin'</segment1>
		<segment2>So help me hold on. Help me be strong. 혩Cause I don't wanna move unless You move me</segment2>
		<segment3>I wanna know how it feels to be. Standing in the center of Your will for me. I wanna know what surrender means. Keep me in the center of Your will for me</segment3>
		<segment4>Keep me in the center</segment4>
		<segment5>God forbid I start to think I'm on a roll now. 혩Cause I do believe there is a battle for my soul now. And I can feel the world fighting for control now. I must be onto somethin'. So help me hold on just a little bit longer. 혩Cause all this struggle's gonna do is make me. stronger. This is the everyday prayer of my heart. I just wanna stay where You are</segment5>
		<segment6>I wanna know how it feels to be. Standing in the center of Your will for me. I wanna know what surrender means. Keep me in the center of Your will for me</segment6>
		<segment7>Lord, help me hold on. Help me be strong. I don't wanna move unless You move me. Yeah, yeah, oh</segment7>
		<segment8>I wanna know how it feels to be. Standing in the center of Your will for me. (The center of Your will). I wanna know what surrender means. (I surrender, I surrender). Keep me in the center of Your will for, will for me</segment8>
		<segment9>Keep me in the center. I wanna know. I surrender, I surrender. I wanna know. You gotta help me, Lord, oh</segment9>
		<segment10>Help me hold on</segment10>
		<segment11>Help me hold on    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
