<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Concept Says </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Follow them, bowing out. Throw me the flag, I'll take the opportunity. Stuck in the moment. I'd pay the price if there's a possibility</segment1>
		<segment2>I've been caught in the standard. I dragged it through the gutter. And what I left there doesn't mean a thing. Follow them, bowing out. I'll pay the price if there's a possibility</segment2>
		<segment3>I won't stay here. I won't stay here. I won't stay here. I've got to make the most of mine</segment3>
		<segment4>Now we hold the key. And no doubt we always have. Don't you remember telling me. That's there a lifetime to make these mistakes</segment4>
		<segment5>And when it's almost over. We'll wish we would've made more. And when the storm is over. We wish we would've made more</segment5>
		<segment6>I won't stay here. I won't stay I'll take the opportunity. Flat out I'll stick it out. Senses awake, accept responsibility</segment6>
		<segment7>Taking it farther. I'll weed right through the clutter. What's left behind there doesn't mean a thing. Follow them, bowing out. I'll pay the price if there's a possibility</segment7>
		<segment8>Never easy to mend. When all the pieces stand so far away</segment8>
		<segment9>. Well, I've been spending a long time looking in. Feel the pulse and it's aggravating. Push and pull while the concept stays</segment9>
		<segment10>And I can't get a peace of mind. And my head keeps racing. And I can't get a peace of mind. And my head keeps racing</segment10>
		<segment11>I fear my options are running out. Why isn't it getting easier to cope without?. To cope without?. And I can't get a peace of mind. And my head keeps racing</segment11>
		<segment12>Inventory, I throw it away. I'd rather mistake, I'd rather not stay</segment12>
		<segment13>I won't stay here. I won't stay if there's a possibility. I won't stay here. I won't stay if there's a possibility</segment13>
		<segment14>I won't stay here. I won't stay, I'll take the opportunity. I won't stay here. I won't stay, I'll take the op, the opportunity    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
