<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Definition Of Me (featuring Blanca from Group 1 Crew) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Everybody's got an opinion. Of what they want me to be. Everybody's got a condition. That I may never meet</segment1>
		<segment2>So tired of looking in the mirror. It always says the same thing. I want to be about something different. Something more than the mirror can see</segment2>
		<segment3>Like joy, peace. Alive in me. When it comes to my identity</segment3>
		<segment4>I want the love. I want the light. I want the beauty. On the inside. I want the one that you can't see. To be the definition of me. More than the face. More than the girl. More than the voice. More than the world. I want the truth that I believe. To be the definition of me</segment4>
		<segment5>Pretty is cool for a minute. But it always fades away. Trends are hot for a second. They'll be gone the very next day</segment5>
		<segment6>So before you get lost in the moment. Lets get one thing clear. Only love will last forever. That's the reason that we're here </segment6>
		<segment7>It's up to you cause everybody's looking. Who do you want them to see?</segment7>
		<segment8>Chorus</segment8>
		<segment9>They say Im cute with the boots. And the trendy attire. You kinda reminiscent of a younger Mariah. But do they see beyond what I got, what I rock. Theyd be shocked if they knew it was my soul that was hot. Hot boys dont affect my own self respect (no!). And neither do the magazines and vanity tests. Yo Disa make a list. Whos fly and whats next. Start it off with love, joy, peace, and end it with blessed. Muah!</segment9>
		<segment10>Chorus</segment10>
		<segment11>. (Featuring Blanca from Group 1 Crew) / (1 Peter 3:3-4, Philippians 3:7-11)     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
