<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The End Has Only Begun </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>We walk in your footsteps. Though I've had my ups and downs. And I'll stand in the silence. Until I figure it out</segment1>
		<segment2>One might fall and the other will stand. And one might give where the other won't bend. The night is bright as the sun</segment2>
		<segment3>I'm never gonna know. Never gonna look back. Never gonna know where we would have ended up at. The end has only begun</segment3>
		<segment4>So stop counting the hours. Live out in the world. Cause I've been chasing the answers. And they don't want to be found</segment4>
		<segment5>One might fall and the other will stand. And one might give where the other won't bend. The night is as bright as the sun</segment5>
		<segment6>I'm never gonna know. Never gonna look back. Never gonna know where we would have ended up at. The end has only begun</segment6>
		<segment7>Well the day. Tonight feels like a million miles away. And these times just won't change. Life just stays the same. I'd give anything to see the light of day</segment7>
		<segment8>Cause I've been too far away. To hear you whispering</segment8>
		<segment9>They say one might fall and the other will stand. And one might give where the other won't bend. The night is as bright as the sun</segment9>
		<segment10>I'm never gonna know. Never gonna look back. Never gonna know where we would have ended up at. The end has only begun</segment10>
		<segment11>Well the day. Tonight feels like a million miles away. And these times just won't change. Life just stays the same. I'd give anything to see the light of day</segment11>
		<segment12>What you do. No one can decide it's up to you. And who you are is what you choose. These times when the world falls apart. Make us who we are    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
