<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Great Golden Gate Disaster </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Outside you there's a remedy. Inside you is an enemy. This twist (this twist) of irony. Can I say you were ever a friend to me?. (Just like we promised). And you know it was never a lie. The fallen son that bought our freedom. Is the I, the I that had to die</segment1>
		<segment2>Outside you there's a remedy. A destiny in identity. Is it the shot heard round the world, or just one more apology?. You wrote us off for so long, so. so long. We burned that bridge instead. And now we've got a song</segment2>
		<segment3>Oh, yeah. You'd better think again. 'Cause it's long overdue. Oh, yeah. And there's so many more of us. Than there are of you</segment3>
		<segment4>Now I can release you (I can release you). Apart from anything to your corruption. (We sing this dedication). As justice comes in many forms. This is no exception. The hero, truthless is lying prostrate. (And this is our redemption)</segment4>
		<segment5>Outside you there's a remedy. A destiny in identity. Is it the shot heard round the world, or just one more apology?. You wrote us off for so long, so. so long. We burned that bridge instead. And now we've got a song</segment5>
		<segment6>Oh, yeah. You'd better think again. 'Cause it's long overdue. Oh, yeah. And there's so many more of us. Than there are of you</segment6>
		<segment7>The contract on my head. Isn't worth the paper, isn't worth the pen. Isn't worth the plastic promise. When the units aren't moving. But we know (we know) we know. Our hearts are beyond prices. These words erupting from swollen tonsils. Will devour your clever devices</segment7>
		<segment8>(These words are my gift to you). My gift to you, these words. (These words are my gift to you). My gift to you, these words. (These words are my gift to you). My gift to you, these words. (These words are my gift to you). For everything, you put us through</segment8>
		<segment9>Oh, oh, oh, yeah (2x)</segment9>
		<segment10>I used to want to change the world. In brotherhood, us two. But now my friend I only want to save it. From you</segment10>
		<segment11>I bid farewell to those lonely days. Breaking my back for you to siphon my veins. The masters will now return. To the (hands of the slaves). And we'll spin them reel to reel. So that every single time you hear. This soundtrack of the voiceless. You'll know the end is drawing near. Can I say you were ever a friend to me? No (3x). Now, you know, now, you know.     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
