<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Godhead </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Verse 1: God eternally exists/ as being three in His personages/ Father, Son, and Holy Spirit and each person is/ fully God and there is only one God who subsists/ so chew on this/ cause this is meat and Im certain of this/ His prerogative could have been to conceal Himself/ but we serve a God who has chose to reveal Himself/ to be certain of who we servin lets search the text/ because its urgent that we worship Him for who He is/ the topic of the Trinity should evoke some emotion/ for those who are chosen/ and also for those who oppose it/ examine close Hes distinctive in His entities/ thats why we contend for the Trinity in serenity/ we have no Christianity if God is not triune/ in that case we are were saved by whom/ then creation was made by whom/ then redemption was made by whom/ the consummation will take place by whom</segment1>
		<segment2>Hook: Pastor Joe. /T-R-I-N-I-T-Y/ Its the trinity/ its the trinity/ oh blessed trinity</segment2>
		<segment3>Verse 2: If we could peer in the past and see a system called dynamic monarchianism/ another system modalistic monarchianism/ before the session we gone focus on one of the isms/ modalistic monarchianism/ get to the core or the center where the belly is/ popularized by a guy named Sabellius/ trying to fight for the position of monotheism/ traditionally held by Jewish in they religion/ and thats true but he started trippin in his position/ and said that God manifested Himself in different/ modes at different times this is real twisted/ thats why a bishop named Athanasisus had resided/ in a meeting in Nicea in 325/ A.D. where they debated was Jesus God/ and if He was, was He the Father the first time/ Jesus the second/ and Holy Spirit the third time/ while affirmed that the Father is God/ that the Son is God/ and the Holy Spirit is God/ good that aint gone solve it/ cause the problem is this/ its the simultaneousness/ that he denied</segment3>
		<segment4>Verse 3: Modalism is back and its now packaged as Oneness Pentecostalism/ and its growing in numbers now like the cost of living/ and when they hear this Ill be labeled a Pharisee/ but the Assemblies of God already labeled it heresy/ in the 20th century when it first emerged/ and ever since its birth its been hurting the church/ in conclusion a myriad of questions I ask/ cause its confusing and steering away at the masses/ I pose to you question number 1/ you mean to tell me that the Father is the Son/ well who was He praying to in the garden of Gethsemane/ I guess youll say He was prayin to His deity/ so you sayin that His human side/ is prayin to His divine side/ that is Father/ In that case then there are two beings/ in the person of Christ is that what you are seeing/ no thats not the scriptures thats confusion/ and it takes stabs at the hypostatic union/ and thats that the one Jesus/ is 100% man and 100% God/ not 100% Father and 100% Son.     </segment4>
	</english>
</song>
