<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Houseplant Song </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Once I read a book. And this is what it said. If your music has a beat. Then you're gonna wind up dead. It doesn't really matter if it's Christian or not. If it's syncopated rhythm then your soul is gonna rot. And this book was called &quot;Ha! Your Gonna Burn&quot;. And in the second chapter I went on to learn</segment1>
		<segment2>[CHORUS:]. Take two houseplants. And put them to the test. Set them both in front of speakers. And let the music do the rest. The first one you play Mozart. Or something lovely like that. The second one you play that Petra Or that MegaDeth. Doesn't really matter what kind of rock it is.</segment2>
		<segment3>So I took my two houseplants. And I put them to the test. Set them both in front of speakers. To let the music do the rest. I powered up my Pioneers. To let the music roar. But twenty minutes later. Someone's knocking at my door. I opened up my door. And there my neighbor stood. He said, &quot;Man I'd like to get some sleep. If you think I could&quot;. I said, &quot;Man, can't you see here. I've got this moral dilemma that I got to get clear.&quot;. He said, &quot; What kind of moral dilemma. Could you have at this time of night. That could make me so angry. That I just want to fight!?&quot;. So I pointed to the page in that open book. That had a picture of a potted plant. And I said, &quot;Go have a look.&quot;. And he read</segment3>
		<segment4>[CHORUS]</segment4>
		<segment5>First of all he said, &quot;That's Wagner that you're playing. I've never heard of Petra. And isn't MegaDeth all dead.&quot;. And secondly, emphatically, He asked me, &quot;What's the sense of hanging out with houseplants. when, hey, I live right across the fence.&quot;. And I thought to myself. You know, that's a good point. So I took my two houseplants, and. I put them both back outside. And me and my neighbor. Well, we went out for a drive. We talked about all the things. That really matter most. Like life and love and happiness. And then the Holy Ghost. And now my two houseplants. They sit out in the sun. As for me and my neighbor. Well our friendship has become. A meaningful relationship. That's headed straight to heaven. But as for now. We like to sit around and listen to Audio Adrenaline. Cranked to eleven!    </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
