<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Hunted </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I'm hiding in my secret place. Built up in my mind. Searching for the rest that I can never find. My wrists held with metal. Shackled to the floor. Torture like this I've never seen before. I dream about revenge. And how sweet it will be. When you're locked up in this cage. Staring back at me. The colors fade to black darker than my sin. I cannot give up now I cannot just give in. I'm wrestling with a beast. I cannot see his face. He spits on me and does not care. He puts me in my place. His dictatorship is vile. His kingdom built on pain. Pure evil poured on everyone. Is how he plays his game</segment1>
		<segment2>Psychotic, deranged, crazy, insane. Poke me with a stick I'm locked up in this tiny cage. You have me I'm yours treat me how you will. With hate and fear until emotion I don't feel. You bellow and laugh, turn your head away. And with a snap of the chains. Now you become the prey. The shifting of your eyes. The shadows my disguise. Stumbling while you run. But you can never hide. The terror begins, the hunt is on. The tables seemed to turn. I hear the scary song. Or is it just the score. Of this movie gone astray. You've had my soul on layaway. And now you're gonna pay</segment2>
		<segment3>Darkness and evil surround me. As the hunt begins. Good vs. evil. Me and you round one of Armageddon. I'm coming your way so hurry. Releasing Gods fury. One Judge no jury. Your demise you'll meet so worry. My sworn enemy by any means I'm. gonna Bring you Representing heaven. In this life or death game. Maintain my cool though. My heart's like an engine. You had your turn now it's time for. mine, Revenge and Rage controls my body. Your tears are running down. But it is only fitting that. You're the hunted now. So I'll hunt you down with the. Wrath of God within me. Not here to take your life. Though you can give it up freely. Hear me in the night as I make you go insane. As my non-stop chantin' starts. To seep into your brain</segment3>
		<segment4>Dear God, I beg for mercy. On the souls that tortured me. I ask that they be shown. The grace that You've shown me</segment4>
		<segment5>The end is upon you. I'll release my anger on you. I'll destroy you then you will know that. I am the LORD!</segment5>
		<segment6>For decades and decades. You've hunted us down. Body count rising or descending to the ground. The concrete jungle closes. The silence surrounds. The only thing heard is. Your heart as it pounds. Sweat pours from your skull. Afraid to turn around. Looking over your shoulder. What was that sound?. Sick of it all no more you can take. The running's slowed down. Your spines about to break. My sights lined up you don't have a clue. Should I make my move, what should I do?. The chase is almost done. The oppression forgot. I've escaped with my life by the grace of God.    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
