<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Lost Get Found </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Hello my friend. I remember when you were. So alive with your wide eyes. Then the light that you had in your heart was stolen. Now you say that it ain't worth stayin'. You wanna run but you're hesitatin'. I'm talkin' to me</segment1>
		<segment2>Don't let your lights go down. Don't let your fire burn out. 'Cause somewhere, somebody needs a reason to believe. Why don't you rise up now?. Don't be afraid to stand out. That's how the lost get found. The lost get found</segment2>
		<segment3>So when you get the chance. Are you gonna take it?. There's a really big world at your fingertips. And you know you have the chance to change it. There's a girl on the streets, she's cryin'. There's a man whose faith is dyin'. Love is calling you</segment3>
		<segment4>Don't let your lights go down. Don't let your fire burn out. 'Cause somewhere, somebody needs a reason to believe. Why don't you rise up now?. Don't be afraid to stand out. That's how the lost get found. The lost get found</segment4>
		<segment5>Why do we go with the flow. Or take an easier road?. Why are we playin' it safe?. Love came to show us the way. Love is a chance we should take. I'm movin' out of the way</segment5>
		<segment6>Don't let your lights go down. Don't let your fire burn out. 'Cause somewhere, somebody needs a reason to believe. (Stand out). Don't let your lights go down. Don't let your fire burn out. (Stand out). 'Cause somewhere, somebody needs a reason to believe. Why don't you rise up now?. Don't be afraid to stand out. That's how the lost get found. The lost get found</segment6>
		<segment7>So when you get the chance. Are you gonna take it?. There's a really big world at your fingertips. And you know you have the chance to change it</segment7>
		<segment8>Copyright © Britt Nicole    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
