<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Next Big Thing </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>You're the next big thing. The next big thing. They're gonna wanna shake your hand. and take a picture with your band. Everyone will shut their mouths. 'cause they wanna hear you out. And they're gonna know your name. 'cause your the next..</segment1>
		<segment2>There's no way of knowing just where you were going. I'll take you for every last second and moment. &quot;So pleased to meet you&quot;, is how they will greet you. while they're looking over your shoulder. I've seen all the faces; been millions of place. It's taken a lot not to lose all my patience. For every good thing comes a whole lot of heartache. I've tried hard to learn from all of my mistakes</segment2>
		<segment3>Hold me back because I lose my control. and you can say goodbye to all the days of old</segment3>
		<segment4>You're the next big thing. The next big thing. They're gonna wanna shake your hand. and take a picture with your band. Everyone will shut their mouths. 'cause they wanna hear you out. And they're gonna know your name. 'cause your the next big thing</segment4>
		<segment5>Everybody put your hands up. Uh huh. Now here you are. with few more friends and a nicer car. but do you really know what the meaning of life is?</segment5>
		<segment6>You've got the gift to make a wish. Will you ever give in to it to make a difference?. Now the kids that come to your shows. see your face everywhere you go</segment6>
		<segment7>There's no way of knowing just where you were going. I'll take you for every last second and moment. &quot;So pleased to meet you&quot;, is how they will greet you. while they're looking over your shoulder. I've seen all the faces; been millions of place. It's taken a lot not to lose all my patience. For every good thing comes a whole lot of heartache. I've tried hard to learn from all of my mistakes</segment7>
		<segment8>Hold me back because I lose my control. and you can say goodbye to all the days of old</segment8>
		<segment9>'Cause you're the next big thing. The next big thing. They're gonna wanna shake your hand. and take a picture with your band. Everyone will shut their mouths. 'cause they wanna hear you out. And they're gonna know your name. 'cause your the next big thing</segment9>
		<segment10>'Cause you're the next big thing. The next big thing. They're gonna wanna shake your hand. and take a picture with your band. Everyone will shut their mouths. 'cause they wanna hear you out. And they're gonna know your name. 'cause your the next big thing</segment10>
		<segment11>    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
