<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Next Great Awakening </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19,segment20,segment21,segment22</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I see you in the valley. Transferring death for life. I see an army coming. They all bear your light</segment1>
		<segment2>I am not bound to reason. I live in violent love. This world can not define me. My hearts set above</segment2>
		<segment3>For me to live it Christ. For me to die is gain. I am not shrinking back. I'll never be the same</segment3>
		<segment4>Four walls can not contain me. I know I've been possessed. I know that God is love. And there's no failing love. So I am fearless</segment4>
		<segment5>Come, love is overtaking me now.</segment5>
		<segment6>Ch 1: This is the sound. of a revolution.</segment6>
		<segment7>This is the sound. of a prophet's cry.</segment7>
		<segment8>This is the sound. of a reformation.</segment8>
		<segment9>This is the sound. of a warrior bride.</segment9>
		<segment10>This is the sound. of a giants falling.</segment10>
		<segment11>This is the sound. that you can't ignore.</segment11>
		<segment12>This is the sound. of a rebel rising.</segment12>
		<segment13>This is the sound. of an open door.</segment13>
		<segment14>Ch2: God, release the sound. Release the movement. I'm laying down everything</segment14>
		<segment15>God, you promised nations. I want the nations. I'm not gonna settle, now. I, I hear the cry. I hear the longing. This is the sound of freedom</segment15>
		<segment16>I stand in the gap. I stand here praying. For the next. Great Awakening</segment16>
		<segment17>(Ch 1)</segment17>
		<segment18>Revival's not an epic or a mission</segment18>
		<segment19>Revival's not program. or a play</segment19>
		<segment20>Revival is not a slogan. Revival is a man. His name is Jesus</segment20>
		<segment21>(Ch 2)</segment21>
		<segment22>    </segment22>
	</english>
</song>
