<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Poor and the Prevalent </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Ive got to put a stop to all this, to all this being separated and then cut off. Ive got to put a stop to all this. Separate then fall</segment1>
		<segment2>We could floatover the world and decide for ourselves if we will ever return. If only our dreams were fires to ignite, then we could let the whole world burn </segment2>
		<segment3>You said this was over when you suffocate the truth and trade for nothing. (Save us, the kisses and the distances are clinging to my weaknesses). Somebody help me here cause I cant steer the wrong words away. (Ive seen this, tasted, a killer to my worries and then caught me without my defense)</segment3>
		<segment4>Theres a death inside, and its yours and mine. So count up your identities, invented for the frequencies of need</segment4>
		<segment5>Does it depend on circumstance or excuse. My inheritance of the abuse. The importance of new. My choice of the two. The truth is that I choose you</segment5>
		<segment6>You said this was over when you suffocate the truth and trade for nothing. (Save us, the kisses and the distances are clinging to my weaknesses). Somebody help me here cause I cant steer the wrong words away. (Ive seen this, tasted, a killer to my worries and then caught me without my defense)</segment6>
		<segment7>Theres a death inside, and its yours and mine. So count up your identities, invented for the frequencies of need</segment7>
		<segment8>Ive got to put a stop to all this, to all this being separated and then cut off</segment8>
		<segment9>Im crushed, broken, begging for this. Outside of you, but this severance?. Torn from my hands, I still taste it. Torn from my hands with my consent</segment9>
		<segment10>Cowards and Princes can sometimes look the same. Just blink and they change. They change, Ive changed, weve changed too    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
