<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Party Song </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I know you like the party, but the party never stops. I know you like the party, but the party never stops. Well I know you, I know you, I know you.</segment1>
		<segment2>I know you want to be here, so you just let go. And no one is ever going to tell you no. But I want to, because I know you, I know you.</segment2>
		<segment3>But you party on, party on. Get your party on, get your party on.</segment3>
		<segment4>This is my last advice, leave with me 'cause you could die tonight. I've got this, I've got this. I've got this so go ahead home. The drugs you use as a place to hide. This will end bad if you don't get this right. I've got this, I've got this, I've got this I don't need you.</segment4>
		<segment5>You got kicked out of your mother's house. You stole money from her purse. She finally found you out. You should be ashamed. Don't sit there judging me. What a waste. You would be the same if you could see. So let's have another drink.</segment5>
		<segment6>And will party on, party on. Get your party on, get your party on.</segment6>
		<segment7>This is my last advice, leave with me 'cause you could die tonight. I've got this, I've got this. I've got this so go ahead home. The drugs you use as a place to hide. This will end bad if you don't get this right. I've got this, I've got this, I've got this, I don't need you.</segment7>
		<segment8>February is still as scary, the month your father died. A little girl in a shrinking world, looking for her place to run and hide.</segment8>
		<segment9>I know you like the party, but the party never stops. I know you like the party, but the party never stops. Well I know you, I know you, I know you.</segment9>
		<segment10>But you party on, party on. Get your party on, get your party on.</segment10>
		<segment11>This is my last advice, leave with me 'cause you could die tonight. I've got this, I've got this. I've got this so go ahead home. The drugs you use as a place to hide. This will end bad if you don't get this right. I've got this, I've got this, I've got this, I don't need you.    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
