<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Real Sin Savior </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>May I have your repentance please? May I have your repentance please?. Will you tell Him &quot;Save me&quot; and please stand up?. I repeat: will you tell Him &quot;Save me&quot; and please stand up?. We're gonna have to prod them here. Y'all act like you never seen a nice person before, you oughta hope in the Lord. Your panting tongue is just thirstin' for more. You started lookin' around searchin' cause you're. Uncertain you're sure you know where you're goin' eternally. If you return to God .. oh wait, no wait, we're sinning. We couldn't get saved with the things we did, can we?. And Dr. J. says -- nothing you did is such a grave sin it costs you salvation. Ha Ha  Heavenly livins above every man. &quot;Chick-a-chick-a-chick-a he's crazy! I'm sick of them born agains. Walkin' around askin' if you know God  speakin of You Know Who. Yeah, but there's no proof though&quot;. Yeah, probably got a couple of you who think I lack proof. But no worse than what's goin' on in America's classrooms. Sometimes I wanna get on TV and just spread the truth. But can't -- but the school can tell me we come from evolution. &quot;My mama was a fish -- my mama was a fish. &quot;And if we're monkeys you might as well forget original sin!&quot;. And that's the message that we deliver to little kids. And expect them not to question on their own if God exists. Of course they're gonna wonder if the Lord's fake by the time they hit fourth grade. They got the Easter Bunny and Santa don't they? We ain't shinin' examples. Well some of the scandals are caused by people posin' as evangelists. But if Jesus loved His enemies and Pharisees. Then there's no reason that you can't get another chance and believe. But if you feel a slight chill, I got the anti-freeze. This is not a fantasy, it's important and it's free. I've sinned greatly, but Christ's for real, baby. It's a wonder He saved me and just didn't hate me. So won't you tell Him &quot;Save me,&quot; please stand up, please stand up, please stand up. Yes, I've been crazy, yes, I've been real shady. Always wanted Him to save me, but just didn't say it. So won't you tell Him &quot;Save me,&quot; please stand up, please stand up, please stand up. Will Smith don't gotta discuss the Christian path to salvation. Well, I do -- it affects him and affects you too. You think I give a care of he likes my parodies. Half of you kiddies won't even look at me, let alone stare at me. But J., what if we pray? Wouldn't we be weird?. Why? Would you guys reject Christ just to fit with your peers. So you can live in fear for the next 60 years? This ain't imaginary, better get prepared. The price of sin yes it costs us dearly with death first. And when that part is over if you ain't saved it gets even worse. Little chance they'll put me now on MTV. Yeah, it's true, but I think he'd scare all the kids -- ree ree!. I said now's when they oughta know and John 3:3. It shows the whole world how they need born again to be free. I'm singin' you little girls and boys spoofs -- all you do is ignore me. Though I have been sent here to inform you. And there's a million of us just like me you judge like me. Were just like triple fudge ice cream; we're just quite sweet. You watch Saul in Acts 9:3, you just might see you're just like him, you're not fightin' me. I've sinned greatly, but Christ He still saved me. From a hundred temptations and death, sin and Hades. So won't you tell Him &quot;Save me,&quot; please stand up, please stand up, please stand up. Yes, my sinned shamed me, yet I've been healed lately. God the Father forgave me from messin' with Satan. So won't you tell Him &quot;Save me,&quot; please stand up, please stand up, please stand up. I'm like a breath mint you listen to but I'm only givin' you. Things you thought about in your head with my religious group. The only difference is I got the call to say it in front of y'all. And I don't gotta be Paul -- the Book I quote has it all. I just get out a Bible and read it and whether you like it you need it. As sure as I can see that better than 90 percent of you happen to doubt me. Then you wonder how can kids give up their values I tell you it's funny. Cause at the place I'm goin' when I'm buried. I'll see the only person in the world I know whos worthy. He's the first and last and I'm J. Jackson I'm the worst. And I'm a jerk and Jesus knows that but my braggin' wasn't workin'. And every single person needs a sin savior urgently. You could be working on a burglary or sittin' in a nunnery. Or keepin' part of the law perfectly screamin' &quot;I don't sin that much&quot;. Puttin' Christians down sayin' &quot;It's just a crutch&quot;. So if you're still waiting please stand up 'cause this wonderful singer's time is eaten up. And it's time to get off your behind and out of the row. Come on down -- now is your chance -- how do I know?. I've sinned greatly, but Christ He still saved me. From a hundred temptations and death, sin and Hades. So won't you tell Him &quot;Save me,&quot; please stand up, please stand up, please stand up. Yes, my sinned shamed me, yet I've been healed lately. God the Father forgave me from messin' with Satan. So won't you tell Him &quot;Save me,&quot; please stand up, please stand up, please stand up. Hahaha - I guess theres a sin Savior for all of us  Lets all stand up    </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
