<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>There He Is </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>If you're searching for joy. And you haven't found it yet. I wanna know</segment1>
		<segment2>Who is the man who said He could save. Who took my dark clouds away. And who said that they would bring joy to my day. And who said they'd wash all my sins away. Now who touched my heart and changed my life. And who is this One that sacrificed. Well, who heard my prayers in the middle of the night. And when I was blind who opened my eyes</segment2>
		<segment3>[Chorus:]. Oh, there He is. Reach out and touch Him. There He is. Call out His name. There He is. Don't be afraid. There He is. Look up in the sky. There He is. It's a bird it's a plane. There He is. No it's Jesus. There He is. Coming to save me. There He is. Hallelujah</segment3>
		<segment4>Now who told the Son to set me free. Who laid down and died on calvary. And who said the homeless was the same as me. Who took solid ground and placed my feet. And who gave the purpose and reason to sing. Who gave the music melody. When trouble was chasing who parted my sea. Somebody talk to me where is this He</segment4>
		<segment5>[Chorus]</segment5>
		<segment6>If you are young man strugglin'. Or a younger seekin'. You don't have to search no more. Just look to the arms of Jesus. You can get Him for yourself. You don't need nobody else. Jesus fall to your knees and pray</segment6>
		<segment7>And you looking for Jesus, searching for Jesus</segment7>
		<segment8>[Chorus]</segment8>
		<segment9>There He is. Wherever I go. There He is. Wherever I turn. There He is. He's all around. There He is. Reach out and touch Him. There He is. He's right there. There He is. And He's guaranteed to answer. There He is. All of your prayers. There He is. I can feel Him. There He is. Whoa yeah. There He is. He's changing your life right now. There He is. Oh yes He is. There He is. There He is. There He is. When troubles come. There He is. Just close your eyes. There He is. And lift your head. There He is. Towards the sky. There He is. Just call on Him. There He is. And you shall find. There He is. He was there. There He is. All of the time. There He is. If your friends are around. There He is. Then you somewhere by yourself. There He is. Call on His name. There He is. He will be right there. There He is. No matter what the problem. There He is. Or the situation. There He is. My Jesus can fix it. There He is. With no hesitation. There He is. If your money is gone. There He is. And you need some help. There He is. On your dying bed. There He is. You're not by yourself. Everywhere you turn. Everywhere you turn. Everywhere you turn. Everywhere you turn. Everywhere you go. Everywhere you go. All around. And when you walk. There He is. When you talk. There He is. And when you cry. There He is. Go down on your knees and call on Him. Jesus reach out and touch and believe He's right there. There He is. And you can do all things through Christ Jesus that strengthens you. There He is.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
