<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Rest Is Up To You </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19,segment20,segment21</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I was just about. to quote Mark Twain. when I realized that. it's all in vain.</segment1>
		<segment2>A twist of fate, a twisted look of pain. To defeat the wheat, go against the grain.</segment2>
		<segment3>I know. I know. I know. I know</segment3>
		<segment4>I know what you've been through. But there's only so much one can do. Now the rest is up to you.. the rest is up to you.</segment4>
		<segment5>The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you.</segment5>
		<segment6>The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you.</segment6>
		<segment7>Your mentor's become. your tormentor. Give him the money, but is it for rent or. will you get burnt for the countless time?</segment7>
		<segment8>Your head starts to hurt. You just close your eyes.</segment8>
		<segment9>I know. I know. I know. I know</segment9>
		<segment10>I know what he did to you. But there's only so much on can do. The rest is up to you.. the rest is up to you.</segment10>
		<segment11>The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you</segment11>
		<segment12>The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you. The rest is up to you</segment12>
		<segment13>This speech is merely words. It's even worse because it rhymes. Give me a minute or your time, I'll have a minute of your time.</segment13>
		<segment14>And I can't make this click. And I can't tattoo your mind. But you know this ain't no trick. Take it or leave it all behind.</segment14>
		<segment15>The rest is up to you (the rest is up to you). The rest is up to you (the rest is up to you). The rest is up to you (the rest is up to you)</segment15>
		<segment16>(Gave my advice, done all I can). The rest is up to you. (It's your life, it's in your hands). The rest is up to you. (Why don't..). The rest is up to you</segment16>
		<segment17>Why don't you try to slow down?. Slow things down. Slow things down.</segment17>
		<segment18>'Cause I know you're hurting. So put down your burdens. Crucify your doubts and just reach out</segment18>
		<segment19>Reach out to Jesus. Embrace him. Turn your life around to face him.</segment19>
		<segment20>You'll find mercy, you'll see. grace, love, and beauty. defined in his. face.</segment20>
		<segment21>You'll find mercy, you'll see. grace, love, and beauty. defined in his. face.    </segment21>
	</english>
</song>
