<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Runaways </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Come closer now. I know your desire is to be desired. Steal a kiss and call us friends. Distance is a theif in which you conspire</segment1>
		<segment2>Time and time and time will tell. Time will tell or tear us apart. You're miles and miles and miles away. Silence reveals where we really are</segment2>
		<segment3>You only stayed to break my heart. I can tell it by the way you runaway, Runaway girl. You only stayed to break my heart. I can tell it by the way you runaway, Runaway girl. Runaway, runaway girl</segment3>
		<segment4>It's clearer now. You're no where into giving. giving into, giving into me. It's your fault. You're like a rare disease. I know you're in love with love. I believe</segment4>
		<segment5>Time and time and time will tell. Time will tell or tear us apart. You're miles and miles and miles away. Silence reveals where we really are</segment5>
		<segment6>You only stayed to break my heart. I can tell it by the way you runaway, Runaway girl. You only stayed to break my heart. I can tell it by the way you runaway, Runaway girl. Runaway, runaway girl</segment6>
		<segment7>Do you expect me to wait here?. All alone in my thoughts and fears. My whole life could flash before your eyes. Hope one day that you realize. This isn't the way it's supposed to be. This is who I crown now without me. Your regrets from us built up inside. Great space for you; love buried alive. Buried alive</segment7>
		<segment8>You only stayed to break my heart. I can tell it by the way you runaway, Runaway girl. You only stayed to break my heart. I can tell it by the way you runaway, Runaway girl. Runaway, runaway girl</segment8>
		<segment9>I only stayed to break your heart. You can tell it by the way I walk away, Runaway girl. I only stayed to break your heart. You can tell it by the way I run away, Runaway girl    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
