<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>These Days </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I never liked Mondays or bad news. Or breakin in new shoes. And mornings when I can't find my phone. Nobody likes traffic or short nights. Or situps or long flights. But sometimes that's just the way it goes. It's funny what you use to help me grow..</segment1>
		<segment2>So I'll learn to love these days. Life along the way. In the middle of the crazy. God your love is so amazing. Through the ups and downs. You're the only hope I've found. The Lord you meet me in the madness</segment2>
		<segment3>I'll learned to love these days. I'll learned to love these days</segment3>
		<segment4>I can see a silver linin. When the sun's not shinin'. Even when you choose to bring the rain. Oh, but I'm trustin your leadin'. 'Cause your Lord of all my joy and all my pain</segment4>
		<segment5>So I'll learn to love these days. Life along the way. In the middle of the crazy. God, your love is so amazing. Through the ups and downs. You're the only hope I've found. The Lord you meet me in the madness</segment5>
		<segment6>I'll learned to love these days. I'll learned to love these days</segment6>
		<segment7>I could wait the hundred years. You gave me here the days when you near. The days when I was out there. Lookin for what comes next. Oh, cause every minute, every hour, everyday. Is such a gift and I can say. I'm thankful for each day</segment7>
		<segment8>So I'll learn to love these days. Life along the way. In the middle of the crazy. God, your love is so amazing. Through the ups and downs. You're the only hope I've found. The Lord you meet me in the madness</segment8>
		<segment9>So I'll learned to love these days. I'll learned to love these days. I'll learned to love these days. I'll learned to love these days    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
