<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Shindig (Off To College) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>So far so good it looks like, the time is almost near, Everything looks ship shape now and, Everyone will soon be here. Tommy brought his champion ring and, Sara brought her new stilettos, Brian brought his Beastie Boys and, His brand new tuxedo rental</segment1>
		<segment2>And so Hey, let's dance the night away, And bang, bang, the boogie like Kid Rock said, I don't know who you are, You dance just like a star, In a video show, I wonder who you are?. Do you hear me tho?</segment2>
		<segment3>Tonight might not be the best time, That we've ever had, But it may be the best time ever, To realize what we have. So let's, pull out those Pink Floyd records, And how about some old Def Leppard?. Turn it to ten, then we'll do it all again, Oh-oh, because it's now or never</segment3>
		<segment4>And so Hey, let's dance the night away, And bang, bang, the boogie like Kid Rock said, I don't know who you are, You dance just like a star, In a video show, I wonder who you are?. Do you hear me tho?</segment4>
		<segment5>Hey, let's dance the night away, And bang, bang, the boogie like Kid Rock said, I don't know who you are, You dance just like a star, In a video show, I wonder who you are?. Do you hear me tho?</segment5>
		<segment6>Gotta keep it coastin', Dip like in the ocean, Move, like Kylie Minogue, When she did the locomotion</segment6>
		<segment7>Hey, let's dance the night away, And bang, bang, the boogie like Kid Rock said, I don't know who you are, You dance just like a star, In a video show, I wonder who you are?. Do you hear me tho?</segment7>
		<segment8>Hey, let's dance the night away, And bang, bang, the boogie like Kid Rock said, I don't know who you are, You dance just like a star, In a video show, I wonder who you are?. Do you hear me tho?    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
