<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Terrible Secret </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>pave these streets with open arms. it's always you we're waiting on. the skin, the taste, the drug, the need. I'm asking (telling you) don't leave. erase the lines that we have drawn. it's always you we're waiting on. and waiting on and waiting on. and on and on and on and on</segment1>
		<segment2>these are our words, that fill these mouths. but all the letters of the alphabet could never spell it out. These palms and frames that we tear through. To cling to something that is bigger than the failed attempts at you. wait wait wait, I don't wanna see. wait wait wait, I am not the person anyone would want to be</segment2>
		<segment3>the perfect shoes with matching clothes. it is the lie we're always told. But nothing masks the shallow touch. like saying words that cost so much. while you're an addict to the need. to find yourself a way to breathe. the sex, the purge, the pain, the look. to replace feelings that we took. these are our words, that fill these mouths. but all the letters of the alphabet could never spell it out. These palms and frames that we tear through, to cling to something that is bigger than the failed attempts at you</segment3>
		<segment4>perfection, it's perfection. but never quiet enough, and never could disguise. the drugs to make it stay, the wanting in your eyes. the money that you've spent but you're still an accident.</segment4>
		<segment5>We are more than words that fill our mouths. drink with eyes that tell us the answers that we need. these are our words, that fill these mouths. but all the letters of the alphabet could never spell it out. These palms and frames that we tear through, to cling to something that is bigger than the failed attempts at you. wait wait wait, I don't wanna see. wait wait wait, I am not the person anyone would want to be</segment5>
		<segment6>waiting here til you leave..    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
