<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Voyager Of Beliefs </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I have 2 brothers and a sister, and a mother, And a father who taught us that we should. All love one another, We go to church on Sunday, In a little green hyundai, Have some grape juice and crackers, Then we start again on Monday</segment1>
		<segment2>And it's all fine, and it's all well, I really want to find what I believe for myself, 'Cause when you're gone, And I'm still here, I won't have you to tell me that I should be there</segment2>
		<segment3>I'm tired of making excuses(oh oh oh), Need to decide for myself.. </segment3>
		<segment4>What if I stumble? What if I fall?. When I'm on my way to You, What if I need You? Who do I call?. How do I know I'll get through?. Because I don't wanna ride the fence anymore. I wanna stand up, and shout it, And let it be known</segment4>
		<segment5>I have 2 fathers, and a sister and a brother, And a mother who taught us that we should. All do unto others, My homeroom teacher, always talks about her preacher. And she says she talks to God, But I don't know if I believe her</segment5>
		<segment6>And it's all fine, and it's all well, I really want to find what I believe for myself, 'Cause when you're gone, And I'm still here, I won't have you to tell me that I should be there </segment6>
		<segment7>I'm tired of making excuses(oh oh oh), Need to decide for myself.. </segment7>
		<segment8>What if I stumble? What if I fall?. When I'm on my way to You, What if I need You? Who do I call?. How do I know I'll get through?. Because I don't wanna ride the fence anymore. I wanna stand up, and shout it, And let it be known</segment8>
		<segment9>And you can tell me, That I can't make a difference 'cause I'm just one, But one is all it takes to start it. And you can tell me, That I can't change the world, Because I'm too young, But I won't stand here and be your target. And you can push me, And try to knock me down, but I won't listen, 'Cause I've got nothing left to lose and, You can hate me, for everything I'm not, But it won't change this, 'Cause now that I'm here, I'm not moving</segment9>
		<segment10>I'm tired of making excuses(oh oh oh), Need to decide for myself.. </segment10>
		<segment11>What if I stumble? What if I fall?. When I'm on my way to You, What if I need You? Who do I call?. How do I know I'll get through?. Because I don't wanna ride the fence anymore. I wanna stand up, and shout it, And let it be known    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
