<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>The Weakest </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Point the gun (in your way). Just pretend that it is time (it is time). Say the word and I will fire. Sometimes I get so tired. Of the ride (it never stops). This word is worth then my life {than my life). Say the word and I will die</segment1>
		<segment2>There's no peace for passing of this new sickness. That I have introduced. To everyone around me saying. That I'm the cause of all their crime. And when they're drunk. I pour the wine</segment2>
		<segment3>Let's leave this place. To say that we escaped. Well say that there's no difference between right and wrong tonight. We'll leave no trace of friends that we have made. So they can find us. And take what is ours</segment3>
		<segment4>Point the gun (in your way). Just pretend that it is time (it is time). Say the word and I will fire</segment4>
		<segment5>Take me far from. This less than perfect design. My contributions only go so far. Without monetary game for my heart</segment5>
		<segment6>Let's leave this place. To say that we escaped. We'll say that there's no difference between right and wrong tonight. We'll leave no trace of friends that we have made. So they can find us and take what is ours</segment6>
		<segment7>Running with the scissors pointed at your heart from your hand. Is that your plan?. I don't have time for questions concerning your future position</segment7>
		<segment8>Let's leave this place (if all that was this time). To say that we escaped (decisions that were mine). We'll say that there's no difference between right and wrong tonight. We'll leave no trace of friends that we have made. So they can find us and take what is ours</segment8>
		<segment9>Put on your coat (it's time to go [x2]). Decemary is what I want. Taking every inch too. Loosing pressure is not a choice. When I'm running with you. Giving up the fight. I could never stop. It is dedication. My gift to you    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
