<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>This Life </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>this is not my home. (this is not my space). this is not my style. (this is not my place)</segment1>
		<segment2>Can't get comfortable. (cant get settled in). I simply dont belong. (cant get used to this)</segment2>
		<segment3>But I'm here right now. (I can hear You say). make the most of Me. (this wont go to waste). If Im out of my mind. (yeah its all for Christ). if Im making sense. (then get it right)</segment3>
		<segment4>every moment is a chance to. let Your light break through</segment4>
		<segment5>this life (oh oh oh ). this life was meant to shine. this life (oh oh oh ). this life was meant to shine</segment5>
		<segment6>I dont have to stall. (I dont have to wait). dont have to bide my time. (till I make my escape). cuz heavens in my heart. (I won't settle for less). I will lift Your name. (by the life I live)</segment6>
		<segment7>every moment is a chance to. let Your light break through</segment7>
		<segment8>this life (oh oh oh). this life was meant to shine. this life (oh oh oh). this life was meant to shine</segment8>
		<segment9>its in my heart. its in my soul. I'll live everyday. just to make You known</segment9>
		<segment10>cuz this life (oh oh oh). this life was meant to. meant to shine</segment10>
		<segment11>hold your heads up high. this is our moment to rise. we were meant to shine. not just survive</segment11>
		<segment12>hold your heads up high. this is our moment to rise. we were meant to shine. not just survive</segment12>
		<segment13>hold your heads up high. this is our moment to rise. we were meant to shine</segment13>
		<segment14>this life (oh oh oh). this life was meant to shine. this life (oh oh oh). this life was meant to shine</segment14>
		<segment15>its in my heart. its in my soul. I'll live everday. just to make You known</segment15>
		<segment16>cuz this life (oh oh oh). this life was meant to. meant to shine</segment16>
		<segment17>its in my heart. its in my soul. I'll live everyday. just to make You known</segment17>
		<segment18>cuz this life (oh oh oh). this life was meant to. meant to shine. oh oh oh </segment18>
		<segment19>we were meant to shine yeah!    </segment19>
	</english>
</song>
