<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>This Is Your Life </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Why you sitting at home, waiting for the phone to ring. Waiting for someone to hand your dreams to you. You know you got to keep it moving. If you don't get up then you'll be losing. Don't deny do you think it's gonna fall out the sky. Nothing's really happening and you're wondering why. How are you going to make it if you never try?. Nobody said it was gonna be easy. But you gotta do what you gotta do. Put on your best foot and step forward. Knowing that God will see you through. So when you get tired and you feel a little faint. Know somebody's watching you and will help you on your way.</segment1>
		<segment2>CHORUS: This is your life God knows what it's meant to be. Know you've got a destiny; time is now so won't you see. This is your life no more waiting to begin. Have some faith and know you'll win. You can make it in this thing called life. yeahhhhhhhh get up now. Somebody said you'll never make it. &amp; That's the thought you're keeping. Don't let that be the reason why you're sleeping'. Time is of the essence &amp; you better believe, That you can do anything so get up, get up. Get up follow your dreams don't you dare give up, No matter how hard it seems you only get it once, Getting by is not enough so take a chance and live this life</segment2>
		<segment3>CHORUS</segment3>
		<segment4>Hey yeah, get up now, hey yeah, get up now. Hey yeah, yeah yeah yeah hey yeah, get up now. Hey yeah get up now ey yeah, yeah yeah yeah</segment4>
		<segment5>(Oooh) I know you don't like the way things seem to be. But you can change it all so easily. Trust that God has got a plan for you to go the way, You know, you should so you can make it if you just believe.</segment5>
		<segment6>CHORUS</segment6>
		<segment7>Hey yeah, get up now, hey yeah, get up now. Hey yeah, yeah yeah yeah hey yeah, get up now. Hey yeah get up now yeah, yeah yeah yeah. This is your life.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
