<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>This, This </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>All that stuff they wear in magazines. All that stuff they do on TV. All that ain't working out for me. So I</segment1>
		<segment2>Like that, I'm free to comb my hair. Like that, I'm free to rock my wear. Like that, I'm modest with a flare. So I</segment2>
		<segment3>When I dance I'm gonna do it like this this. When I prance I'm gonna do it like this this. Every chance I'm gonna do it like this this. Like this this gotta be myself. When I smile I'm gonna do it like this this. When I style I'm gonna do it like this this. Honey chil' I'm gonna do it like this this. Like this this. Gotta be myself</segment3>
		<segment4>I like chewing gum when I sing. I like H2O with evertying. I like idiosyncrasies. I like cute ugly kinda shoes. I like just kicking it with you. I like being free enough to choose. So I</segment4>
		<segment5>When I bring it I'm a do it like this this. When I sing it I'm a do it like this this. When I fling it I'm a do it like this this. Like this this. Gotta be myself</segment5>
		<segment6>When I walk if I'm a do it like this. When I talk it I'm a do it like this this. When I rock it I'm a do it like this this. Like this this. Gotta be myself</segment6>
		<segment7>SO hum de um de ai.. (Rap)</segment7>
		<segment8>When I dress it I'm a do it like this this. When I press it I'm a do it like this this. If He bless it I'm a do it like this this. Like this this. Gotta be myself</segment8>
		<segment9>In the morning I'm a do it like this this. In the noon I'm a do it like this this. In the evening I'm a do it like this this. Like this this. Gotta be myself</segment9>
		<segment10>When I raise 'em I'm a do it like this this. When I praise Him I'm a do it like this this. Everyday I'm gonna do it like this this. Like this this. Gotta be myself. Oh    </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
