<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Thrive </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Been fighting things that I can't see in.  Like voices coming from the inside of me and.  Like doing things I find hard to believe in.  Am I myself or am I dreaming?</segment1>
		<segment2> I've been awake for an hour or so.  Checking for a pulse but I just don't know.  Am I a man when I feel like a ghost?.  The stranger in the mirror is wearing my clothes</segment2>
		<segment3> No I'm not alright.  I know that I'm not right.  A steering wheel don't mean you can drive.  A warm body don't mean I'm alive.  No I'm not alright.  I know that I'm not right.  Feels like I travel but I never arrive.  I want to thrive not just survive</segment3>
		<segment4> I come alive when I hear you singing.  But lately I haven't been hearing a thing and.  I get the feeling that I'm in between.  A machine and a man who only looks like me. [ Lyrics from: http://www.lyricsmode.com/lyrics/s/switchfoot/thrive.html ].  I try and hide it and not let it show.  But deep down inside me I just don't know.  Am I a man when I feel like a hoax?.  The stranger in the mirror is wearing my clothes</segment4>
		<segment5> No I'm not alright.  I know that I'm not right.  A steering wheel don't mean you can drive.  A warm body don't mean I'm alive.  No I'm not alright.  I know that I'm not right.  Feels like I travel but I never arrive.  I want to thrive not just survive</segment5>
		<segment6> I'm always close but I'm never enough.  I'm always in line but I'm never in love.  I get so down but I won't give up.  I get slowed down but I won't give up</segment6>
		<segment7> Been fighting things that I can't see in.  Like voices coming from the inside of me and.  Like doing things I find hard to believe in.  Am I myself or am I dreaming?</segment7>
		<segment8> No I'm not alright.  I know that I'm not right.  A steering wheel don't mean you can drive.  A warm body don't mean I'm alive.  No I'm not alright.  I know that I'm not right.  Feel like I travel but I never arrive.  I want to thrive not just survive</segment8>
		<segment9> I want to thrive not just survive    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
