<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Time </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I can't explain. Can't quite put my finger on it. The difference that makes us so different. We've said everything. Our words only betrayed us. Nothing is left nothing was left unsaid</segment1>
		<segment2>This time I have nothing left to lose. I'm stuck the second hand won't move. Its about time that I speak my mind. Its about time, about time to find pieces of me I have lost. Without any choice I move on. Hey time you're no friend of mine. Hey time you're no friend of mine</segment2>
		<segment3>You cover yourself you cover your skin. You cover yourself like you cover your sin. Please untie my hands. I'm a sinner, I'm a man. I ask for one minute to make you understand</segment3>
		<segment4>This time I have nothing left to lose. I'm stuck the second hand won't move. Its about time that I speak my mind. Its about time, about to find pieces of me I have lost. Without any choice I move on. Hey time you're no friend of mine. Hey time you're no friend of mine</segment4>
		<segment5>Will you be there. To catch when I stumble when I fall. When I fall</segment5>
		<segment6>Its so very clear. You left me when I had no one at all. No one at all</segment6>
		<segment7>Who will be there. To catch me, to catch me when I stumble. When I fall, when I fall. Its so very clear. You left me with no one at all. No one at all</segment7>
		<segment8>This time I have nothing left to lose. I'm stuck the second hand won't move. Its about time that I speak my mind. Its about time, about time to find pieces of me I have lost. Without any choice I move on. Hey time you're no friend of mine. Hey time you're no friend of mine</segment8>
		<segment9>No friend of mine. Time, you're no friend of mine. No friend of mine. Hey time you're no friend of mine. Hey time you're no friend of mine</segment9>
		<segment10>The pieces of me I have lost. Without any choice I move on</segment10>
		<segment11>Time. Time you're no friend of mine    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
