<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Timothy Hay </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>on a cold December, just before dawn. as the sun said &quot;hello&quot; to the sky. the mantis prayed while the lamellicorn tumbled and rolled in a threadbare tie</segment1>
		<segment2>the holland lops in the Callicoon glades indignantly thumped their feet. and hopped away when they cut their noses on the sharp-tipped blades. (since the grass doesn't mind in the least). the heat pad waiting in the chicken-wire hutch where the does from the netherlands stay. but that dry alfalfa don't taste like much and we're tired of the timothy hay. (hey)</segment2>
		<segment3>i touched her back, she was lying face down. the dew turned to frost in her eyes. me and sister margaret in the pentagon lawn with our wrists in a plastic tie. while the rats by the tracks on these winter days seeking shelter from the cold. make a nest in the traps of our various ways that they can save their immortal souls</segment3>
		<segment4>oh no, timothy hay. oh no, timothy hay. oh no, timothy hay. oh no, timothy hay. oh no, timothy hay. oh no, timothy hay. please no more timothy hay. no more timothy hay. oh no, no more timothy hay. oh no, no more timothy hay. oh no, no more timothy hay. no more timothy hay</segment4>
		<segment5>cold december, just after dusk. as the sun bid its cordial goodbyes. we get split to pieces like an apple core husk to reveal the tree that's been hidden inside. we're a sapling caught in a tattered sirah at the seams from the shepherd's purse-belt. broke the news to mom: we found a better Mom we call &quot;God&quot; (which she took quite well). what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God there must be!. what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God there must be!. what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God there must be!. what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God, what a beautiful God You must be!     </segment5>
	</english>
</song>
