<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>To Know You </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>To know you is never worry for my life, and. To know you is to never to give in or compromise. To know you is to want to tell the world about you. Cause I can't live without you</segment1>
		<segment2>To know you is to hear your voice when you are calling. To know you is to catch my brother when he is falling. To know you is to feel the pain of the broken hearted. Cause they can't live with out you.</segment2>
		<segment3>More than my next breath. More than life or death. All reaching for, I live my life to know you more. I leave it all behind, you are all that satisfies. To know you is to want to know you more. To know you is to want to know you more</segment3>
		<segment4>To know you is to ache for more than ordinary. To know you is to look beyond the temporary. To know you is believing that you will be enough. Cause there is no life without you</segment4>
		<segment5>More than my next breath. More than life or death. All I'm reaching for, I live my life to know you more. I leave it all behind, you are all that satisfies. To know you is to want to know you more. To know you is to want to know you more</segment5>
		<segment6>All this life could offer me, could not compare to you. Compare to you. And I count it all as lost, compared to knowing you. Knowing you</segment6>
		<segment7>More than my next breath. More than life or death. All I'm reaching for, I live my life to know you more. I leave it all behind, you are all that satisfies. To know you is to want to know you more. To know you is to want to know you more</segment7>
		<segment8>Compared to you. Compared to you. And I count it all as lost, compared to knowing you. Knowing you. And I count it all as lost, compared to knowing you. Knowing you </segment8>
		<segment9>Copyright © Casting Crowns    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
