<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>To Say They Hit It off Would Be an Understatement </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>If I talk will you listen, and pay some attention. Ff it's the last time you spend. What good sound advice. When the sounds of your vices are the only thing that you comprehend. I see the tears in your eyes, I gotta pull you aside. (Don't make a scene they'll here us arguing)</segment1>
		<segment2>This happened once before. You wound up at his door. (I have nowhere to go). You still go back for more. (I hate to be alone). Got to know that, got to know that. This time won't be the same. (You just don't understand). You're trying to explain. ('Cause he's the difference). Some people never change. Got to know that, got to know that guy</segment2>
		<segment3>For your lines. And you'd think you'd have your fill by now. But instead, you stay fed. To afraid to bite the hand that feeds you. Your pain it's your guilt. Corner in his room while his anger builds</segment3>
		<segment4>No one deserves what happens next. (What happens next). Got promised the world. Why on earth would you settle for less</segment4>
		<segment5>This happened once before. (I swear I didn't know). You wound up at his door. (I have nowhere to go). You still go back for more. (I hate to be alone). Got to know that, got to know that. This time won't be the same. (You just don't understand). You're trying to explain. ('Cause he's the difference). Some people never change. Got to know that, got to know this time. This time. This time. This time</segment5>
		<segment6>I didn't know that. I didn't know that. I didn't know that. I didn't know that. I didn't know that. I didn't know that. I didn't know that. Got to know that</segment6>
		<segment7>This time won't be the same. (You just don't understand). You're trying to explain. ('Cause he's the difference). Some people never change. Got to know that, got to know this time. This time. This time. This time     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
