<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Touch Me </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Give me a old school beat. This is what we gon' do with it</segment1>
		<segment2>I gotta be feel with the Holy Ghost. Knot that ties me from my head to my toes. You said if I pray You would deliver me. Break those chains, Lord, that were bindin' me</segment2>
		<segment3>Hey, only You can make me right. Lord, I'm askin' You to change my life</segment3>
		<segment4>I need You. Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time</segment4>
		<segment5>I wanna be free with Your Holy Spirit. And there are days when I just can't feel it. But I know You're there, You said You'd never leave me. And I must say, Lord You've been good to me</segment5>
		<segment6>Lord, I'm askin' You for help. You've been better to me that I've been to myself. I need You to touch me</segment6>
		<segment7>Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time</segment7>
		<segment8>Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time. Touch me one more time</segment8>
		<segment9>One more time. One more time. One more time. I need You to touch me</segment9>
		<segment10>One more time. One more time. One more time. I need You to touch me</segment10>
		<segment11>People right there clap your hands. I've just got a question. Anybody need a touch?</segment11>
		<segment12>Anybody need a touch, a touch. Need a touch, hey, one more time. Anybody need a touch, a touch. Need a touch, hey, one more time</segment12>
		<segment13>Anybody need a touch, a touch. Need a touch, hey, one more time. Anybody need a touch, a touch. Need a touch, hey, one more time</segment13>
		<segment14>I need it, I need it, I need it. I need it, I need it, I need it. I need it, I need it, I need it. I need it, I need it, I need it. I need it, I need it, I need it    </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
