<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>TV Family </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Just a calendar day (ba ba ba ba). its funny how things can stay the same. or drastically change. some things seem so close on some days but still so far away. dont know the right tings to do (ba ba ba ba). in fact i dont have a clue sometime i feel like a tool. and i want to be truthfully true to you. and do all the things that you do. but when i hate everything about the mean things that i say. it feels like i mess up so much and i can only say. &quot;i hate everything about my ways&quot;. but you tell me im OK. and one day one day i know you'll say</segment1>
		<segment2>&quot;B im so glad you made it&quot;. &quot;oh well Jesus thank you so much for saying that&quot;. because the truth you know is that i have just been hating so many things i do. but now i realize forever that you're my friend. no matter what you will never leave me to fend. i don't know much but i know we will be. as happy as a 195o's TV family. except times infinity</segment2>
		<segment3>two calendar days (ba ba ba ba). and still my life is the same. and other people's have changed. i wonder what if im too late. all the time that i said i would wait?. and yeah does anyone care. about us here or anywhere?. well i just want to try adn dare. to be there, to care cus i know- i know thats rare. but when i hate everything about the mean things that i say. it feels like i mess up so much and i can only say. &quot;i hate everything about my ways&quot;. but you tell me im OK. and one day one day i know you'll say</segment3>
		<segment4>&quot;B im so glad you made it&quot;. &quot;oh well Jesus thank you so much for saying that&quot;. because the truth you know is that i have just been hating so many things i do. but now i realize forever that you're my friend. no matter what you will never leave me to fend. i don't know much but i know we will be. as happy as a 195o's TV family. except times infinity</segment4>
		<segment5>a family that i will be in. a family- its jsut not pretend. a familt that i will be in, a family</segment5>
		<segment6>i don't know much but i know we will be. happy as a 1950&quot;s TV family.. except times infinity. just a calendar day.    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
