<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Twenty-Four </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Twenty-four oceans. Twenty-four skies. Twenty-four failures. And twenty-four tries. Twenty-four finds me. In twenty-fourth place. With twenty-four drop outs. At the end of the day </segment1>
		<segment2>Life is not what I thought it was. Twenty-four hours ago. Still I'm singing 'Spirit, take me up in arms with You'. And I'm not who I thought I was. Twenty-four hours ago. Still I'm singing 'Spirit, take me up in arms with You' </segment2>
		<segment3>There's twenty-four reasons. To admit that I'm wrong. With all my excuses. Still twenty-four strong </segment3>
		<segment4>See, I'm not copping out. Not copping out. Not copping out. When you're raising the dead in me </segment4>
		<segment5>Oh, oh. I am the second man. Oh, oh. I am the second man now. Oh, I am the second man now. And you're raising these.. </segment5>
		<segment6>Twenty-four voices. With twenty-four hearts. All of my symphonies. In twenty-four parts. But I want to be one today. Centered and true. I'm singing 'Spirit take me up in arms with You'. You're raising the dead in me </segment6>
		<segment7>Oh, oh. I am the second man. Oh, oh. I am the second man now. Oh. I am the second man now. And you're raising the dead in me. Yeah </segment7>
		<segment8>I wanna see miracles. To see the world change. Wrestled the angel for more than a name. For more than a feeling. For more than a cause. I'm singing 'Spirit, take me up in arms with You'. And you're raising the dead in me </segment8>
		<segment9>Twenty-four oceans. With twenty-four hearts. All of my symphonies. With twenty-four parts. Life is not what I thought it was. Twenty-four hours ago. Still I'm singing 'Spirit, take me up in arms with You'. I'm not copping out. Not copping out    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
