<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Unstoppable </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Be strong, be brave, be beautiful. One of these days you'll have it all. If you believe you can. Wake up and hold your head up high. Challenge your future to a fight. Open up your hands</segment1>
		<segment2>No more lonely house of tears. Slam the door on all your fears. They're not welcome here</segment2>
		<segment3>Anything is possible, possible. You got to believe and see. That love is unstoppable. You can never go too far. Never been too gone. Cause you can turn it around. You will see that love is unstoppable</segment3>
		<segment4>(Keep going, keep going). (Keep pushing, keep pushing)</segment4>
		<segment5>Sometimes life seems so typical. Somedays you might see a miracle. But if you believe you can. (Keep pushing, keep pushing)</segment5>
		<segment6>This world is cold, this crazy place. Makes you feel like your losing everything. Your mind, your faith, your way. But you can find it all again. Reclaim your inner self. You know it's not the end</segment6>
		<segment7>Anything is possible, possible. You got to believe and see. That love is unstoppable. You can never go too far. Never been too gone. Cause you can turn it around. You will see that love is unstoppable</segment7>
		<segment8>(Keep going, keep going). Nothing's going to break you down. (Keep pushing, keep pushing). Stop you now (possible, possible). Nothing's going to be that bad. Hold you back</segment8>
		<segment9>You can never go too far. Never been too gone. But you can turn it around. Just believe that any thing's possible</segment9>
		<segment10>Nothing's going to break you down. Stop you now. Cause love is unstoppable. Anything is possible, possible. You got to believe and see. That love is unstoppable</segment10>
		<segment11>You can never go too far. Never been too gone. But you can turn it around. You will see that love is unstoppable    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
