<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Vices </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Feeling cold, feeling empty. Set the stage, where you want me. And this crowd right before me doesnt care that Im dying. And the audience stands with their eyes fixed on the preconceived version of me. Im so betrayed by your hopes, but I will not hide myself for your peace of mind. </segment1>
		<segment2>Oh, but Child. Ive got Vices like any other man. </segment2>
		<segment3>Raise a boy to a cynic. Take his love, and then let it turn into something passionate. Something sick, something rabid. And I vent to keep myself from caving. I dont hate you, I just hate where Im heading. Im left here asking, when did I trade in my bleeding heart for a selfish win? </segment3>
		<segment4>Oh, but Mother. Ive got Vices like any other man. Vices that youre not used to. Vices thatll make you think less of me. </segment4>
		<segment5>Leave me numb. Leave me jaded. Shes a dream, I just play dead. Ive been blessed, Ive been hated. Shes the constant, and Im her addict. Shes the only peace in this world, uneasy. While I bite my tongue to keep from breaking the heart that Ive spent my whole life seeking. The only heart Ive ever needed. </segment5>
		<segment6>Oh, but Lover. Ive got Vices like any other man. Vices that youre not used to. Vices thatll make you think.. Oh, but Lover. Ive got Vices like any other man. Vices that youre not used to. Vices thatll make you think less of me. Less of me. </segment6>
		<segment7>Feeling cold, feeling empty. I am low, unworthy. Bleed the God. Bleed the blessing. Like a vulture feasting. Ill exist as if I dont feel conviction of my ignorance to my perfect prison. But I feel the stabs on my wrists and ankles every time I try.. </segment7>
		<segment8>To forget you. To forget you. </segment8>
		<segment9>Oh, but Jesus. Ive got Vices like any other man. Vices that youre so used to. Vices that wont make you think less of me.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
