<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Vice Verses </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Walking along the high tide line.  Watching the pacific from the sidelines.  Wonder what it means to live together?.  Looking for more than just guidelines</segment1>
		<segment2> Looking for signs in the night sky,  Wishing that I wasnt such a nice guy.  Wonder what it means to live forever?.  Wonder what it means to die?</segment2>
		<segment3>[Chorus].  I know that there's a meaning to it all.  A little resurrection every time I fall.  You got your babies, I got my hearses.  Every blessing comes with a set of curses.  I got my vices, I got my vice verses.  I got my vice verses</segment3>
		<segment4> The wind could be my new obsession.  The wind could be my new depression.  The wind goes anywhere it wants to.  Wishing that I learned my lesson</segment4>
		<segment5> The ocean sounds like a garage band.  Coming at me like a drunk man.  The ocean tells me a thousand stories.  None of them are lies</segment5>
		<segment6>[Chorus].  I know that there's a meaning to it all.  A little resurrection every time I fall.  You got your babies, I got my hearses.  Every blessing comes with a set of curses.  I got my vices, I got my vice verses.  I got my vice verses</segment6>
		<segment7> Let the pacific laugh.  Be on my epitaph.  With it's rising and falling.  And after all, it's just water.  And I am just soul.  With a body of water and bones.  Water and bones</segment7>
		<segment8> Where is God in the night sky?.  Where is God in the city light?.  Where is God in the earthquake?.  Where is God in the genocide?</segment8>
		<segment9> Where are you in my broken heart?.  Everything seems to fall apart.  Everything feels rusted over.  Tell me that you're there</segment9>
		<segment10>[Chorus].  I know that there's a meaning to it all.  A little resurrection every time I fall.  You got your babies, I got my hearses.  Every blessing comes with a set of curses.  I got my vices, I got my vice verses.  These are my vice verses.  These are my vice verses</segment10>
		<segment11> Yeah.  These are my vice verses    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
