<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Wade in the Water (The Lord Will Make a Way/Hush) </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Chorus: Wade in the water. Wade in the water children. Wade in the water. Gods gonna trouble the water</segment1>
		<segment2>I stepped in the water and the water was cold. (Gods gonna trouble the water.). Chilled my body, but didnt touch my soul, You say (Gods gonna trouble the water.)</segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus</segment3>
		<segment4>I went to the water one day to pray, (Gods gonna trouble the water). (Said my soul got happy and I stayed all day, yes). Gods gonna trouble the water. (Gods gonna trouble the water-2xs).</segment4>
		<segment5>Did you find it (In the water). Did you find it (In the water). Where did you get it (In the water). Where did you get it (In the water). Said I found what I need (In the water). It was right there (In the water). Said I got what I wanted (In the water). It was right there in the water (In the water). Got my deliverance (In the water). In the water (In the water). Got my healing yall (In the water). Right there in the water (In the water). Got my salvation (In the water). Right there in the water (In the water). Got what I needed (In the water). Right there in the water (In the water).</segment5>
		<segment6>(Yes, yes the water). Oh yes (Yes the water). Yeah yes (Yes the water). It was right there (Yes the water). Everything I needed (Yes the water). Was right there in the water (Yes the water). Everything I needed (Yes the water). In the water (Yes the water).</segment6>
		<segment7>Everything you need (Everything you need in the water- 3xs). Right there in the water, Everything you need. In the water yall.  Hey!</segment7>
		<segment8>I found it (I found it- 16xs). Everything I needed, everything I wanted. Had to step on in the water, but the water was cold. I found what I needed, but the water was cold. Right there. Lady- Oh I found it. Oh I found it. I found it. In the water. The water was cold. But not my soul.</segment8>
		<segment9>Everything you need, yes it was (Everything you need in the water -4xs). Everything you need was right the in the water. Music volume lowers out.    </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
