<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Walking on Sunshine </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Lyrics: I used to think maybe you loved me. Now, baby, I'm sure. And I just can't wait 'til the day. When you knock on my door. Now every time I go to the mailbox. Gotta hold myself down (every time I go, gotta hold myself down). 'Cause I just can't wait 'til you write me. You're coming around</segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus: </segment2>
		<segment3>I'm walking on sunshine, oh, oh. I'm walking on sunshine, oh, oh. I'm walking on sunshine, oh, oh. And time to feel good. Hey,alright now. And time to feel good. (Walking on sunshine)</segment3>
		<segment4>I used to think maybe you loved me. Now I know that it's true. But I just can't spend my whole life. Just a waiting for you. I don't want you back for the weekend. No back for a day (want you back for the weekend, back for just). 'Cause baby I just want you back. And I want you to stay (and I want you to stay)</segment4>
		<segment5>I'm walking on sunshine, oh, oh. I'm walking on sunshine, oh, oh. I'm walking on sunshine, oh, oh. And don't it feel good!. Hey, alright now. And don't it feel good!. And don't it feel good!. And don't it feel good!</segment5>
		<segment6>I'm walking on sunshine. I'm walking on sunshine. (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop). I'm walking on sunshine</segment6>
		<segment7>I feel alive, I feel the love (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop). I feel alive, I feel the love</segment7>
		<segment8>I'm walking on sunshine, oh oh. I'm walking on sunshine, oh oh. I'm walking on sunshine, oh oh</segment8>
		<segment9>And time to feel good!. And time to feel good!. And time to feel good!. And time to feel good!</segment9>
		<segment10>I'm walking on sunshine (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop). I'm walking on sunshine (walking on sunshine). I'm walking on sunshine (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop). I'm walking on sunshine (walking on sunshine). I'm walking on sunshine (yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah). (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop). I'm walking on sunshine (yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah). I'm walking on sunshine (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop). I'm walking on sunshine (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop)</segment10>
		<segment11>(do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop). (do wop, do wop, do wop, do wop)</segment11>
		<segment12>    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
