<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Walk On </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19,segment20</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>And love. Is not the easy thing. The only baggage. That you can bring. Not the easy thing. The only baggage you can bring. Is all that you can't leave behind </segment1>
		<segment2>. And if the darkness is to keep us apart. And if the daylight feels like it's a long way off. And if your glass heart should crack. And for a second you turn back. Oh no, be strong </segment2>
		<segment3>. Walk on. Walk on. What you got, they can't steal it. No they can't even feel it </segment3>
		<segment4>. Walk on. Walk on. Stay safe tonight </segment4>
		<segment5>. You're packing a suitcase for a place. None of us has been. A place that has to be believed. To be seen </segment5>
		<segment6>. You could have flown away. A singing bird. In an open cage. Who will only fly. Only fly for freedom </segment6>
		<segment7>. Walk on. Walk on. What you got. You can't deny it. Can't sell it or buy it </segment7>
		<segment8>. Walk on. Walk on. You stay safe tonight </segment8>
		<segment9>. And I know it aches. How your heart it breaks. You can only take so much </segment9>
		<segment10>. Walk on. Walk on </segment10>
		<segment11>. Home. Hard to know what it is. If you never had one </segment11>
		<segment12>. Home. I can't say where it is. But I know I'm going </segment12>
		<segment13>. Home. That's where the hurt is </segment13>
		<segment14>. And I know it aches. And your heart it breaks. You can only take so much. Walk on </segment14>
		<segment15>. Leave it behind. You've got to leave it behind </segment15>
		<segment16>. All that you fashion. All that you make. All that you build. All that you break </segment16>
		<segment17>. All that you measure. All that you feel. All this you can leave behind </segment17>
		<segment18>. All that you reason. All that you care. (It's only time. And I'll never fill up all I find) </segment18>
		<segment19>. All that you sense. All that you scheme. All you dress up. And all that you see </segment19>
		<segment20>|:. All you create. All that you wreck. All that you hate    </segment20>
	</english>
</song>
