<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Walk On The Water </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>You look around. It's staring back at you. Another wave of doubt. Will it pull you under. You wonder</segment1>
		<segment2>What if I'm overtaken. What if I never make it. What if no one's there?. Will you hear my prayer?</segment2>
		<segment3>When you take that first step. Into the unknown. You know that he won't let you go</segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus:</segment4>
		<segment5>So what are you waiting for?. What do you have to lose?. Your insecurities try to hold to you</segment5>
		<segment6>You know you're made for more. So don't be afraid to move. Your faith is all. It takes and you can. Walk on the water too</segment6>
		<segment7>Verse 2: So get out. And let. Your fear fall to the ground. No time to waste. Don't wait. Don't you turn around and miss out. Everything you were made for. I know you're not sure. So you play it safe. Try to run away</segment7>
		<segment8>If you take that first step. Into the unknown. He won't let you go</segment8>
		<segment9>(chorus)</segment9>
		<segment10>Bridge: (step out). Even when a storm hits. (step out). Even when you're broken. (step out). Even when your heart is telling you telling you to give up. (step out). When your hope is stolen. (step out). You can't see where you're going. You don't have to be afraid</segment10>
		<segment11>So what are you waiting, What are you waiting for?</segment11>
		<segment12>So what are you waiting for?. What do you have to lose?. Your insecurities try to hold to you</segment12>
		<segment13>You know you're made for more. So don't be afraid to move. Your faith is all. It takes and you can. Walk on the water.. Walk on the water too </segment13>
		<segment14>Copyright © Britt Nicole     </segment14>
	</english>
</song>
