<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Walk With the Wise </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I prayed a prayer for wisdom like a farmer prays for rain. 'Cause I knew that I must have it to survive in this life. And I stared out in the distance 'cause it seemed so far away. And I waited for the lightning. But the thunder and the lightning never came. So I took a look beside me to my left and to my right. And saw people full of wisdom all around in my life. And it started to come clearer I began to understand. that my prayer was being answered it's all part of God's plan</segment1>
		<segment2>If we walk with the wise we will grow wise ..wo..wo. If we walk in the light then our path will be bright I know. There's someone who's already been where we must go. In the light of what they've learned we find. That we will grow wise if we walk with the wise</segment2>
		<segment3>I've learned to look for answers in those born before my time. As I listen to them tell me what they've learned in thier lives. I talk to friends with understanding much deeper than my own. And gain wisdom beyound measure I could never find alone</segment3>
		<segment4>If we walk with the wise we will grow wise ..wo..wo. If we walk in the light then our path will be bright I know. There's someone who's already been where we must go. In the light of what they've learned we find. That we will grow wise if we walk with the wise</segment4>
		<segment5>One life can be a candle with widom as it's fire. And everything it touches with it's flame is set ablaze</segment5>
		<segment6>If we walk with the wise we will grow wise ..wo..wo. If we walk in the light then our path will be bright I know. There's someone who's already been where we must go. In the light of what they've learned we find. That we will grow wise if we walk with the wise </segment6>
		<segment7>    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
