<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Waste Of Time </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>This troubled heartache. won't go away. I think there might be. something wrong with me. I take a deep breath and maybe. I'll stop this shaking. God please don't forsake me. I might be crazy </segment1>
		<segment2>Am I losing my mind?. Sometimes I feel like. things are getting worse in time. If I try will you open my eyes?. And make me a part of you. like you're a friend of mine </segment2>
		<segment3>Next time I'm losing my mind. I'll remember that to find my way out. is just a waste of time. In place of all my mistakes. You've seen through the shadows above me. No one could ever love me like you </segment3>
		<segment4>If I finish what I started. and get swept under the carpet. I'll still be thankful for all you've done. Take a note to remind me. that you know where you can find me. I'll probably end up right back here again </segment4>
		<segment5>Am I losing my mind?. Sometimes I feel like. things are getting worse in time. If I try will you open my eyes?. And make me a part of you. like you're a friend of mine </segment5>
		<segment6>Next time I'm losing my mind. I'll remember that to find my way out. is just a waste of time. In place of all my mistakes. seen through the shadows above me. No one could ever love.. </segment6>
		<segment7>I'll be everything that you want me to. except for perfect. I'm trying hard just to understand. your plan for me. I'll be everywhere that you want me to. unless I fall. I'm just trying to get my life back again </segment7>
		<segment8>Next time I'm losing my mind. I'll remember that to find my way out. is just a waste of time. In place of all my mistakes. You've seen through the shadows above me. No one could ever love me.. </segment8>
		<segment9>Next time I'm losing my mind. I'll remember that to find my way out. is just a waste of time. In place of all my mistakes. You've seen through the shadows above me. No one could ever love me like you.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
