<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>We Are One Tonight </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Check!</segment1>
		<segment2>Tonight!</segment2>
		<segment3>Tonight!</segment3>
		<segment4>I'll rise. I'll fall. I'll fail you all</segment4>
		<segment5>We built these cities to stand so tall. We've lost our walls</segment5>
		<segment6>I don't want to lose it, coming down. With the whole world upside-down. I don't have a soul to trust in now. With the whole world upside-down</segment6>
		<segment7>We are one, tonight!. And we're singing it out!. We are one, tonight!. And we're dreaming out loud!</segment7>
		<segment8>And the world is flawed. But these scars will heal</segment8>
		<segment9>We are one, tonight!. Tonight!. Tonight!</segment9>
		<segment10>Two eyes. One tongue. I've come. Undone</segment10>
		<segment11>I'm no victim. I paid these dues. I came to lose</segment11>
		<segment12>I don't want to fight about it now. With the whole world upside-down. I don't have a soul to trust in, now. With the whole world upside-down</segment12>
		<segment13>We are one, tonight!. And we're singing it out!. We are one, tonight!. And we're dreaming out loud!</segment13>
		<segment14>And the world is flawed. But these scars will heal</segment14>
		<segment15>We are one, tonight!. Tonight!. Tonight!. Tonight!. Tonight!. Tonight!</segment15>
		<segment16>I don't want to lose a common ground. With the whole world upside-down. I don't want to fight about it now. And the world was burning out</segment16>
		<segment17>Let's slow the evening down. Slow it down. Slow down. Please slow down. Down. Down</segment17>
		<segment18>The stars are comin' out!</segment18>
		<segment19>We are one. We are one. We are one. We are one tonight. We are one tonight. And were singing it out. We are one tonight. And were dreaming out loud. And the world is flawed, But these scars will heal!.     </segment19>
	</english>
</song>
