<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>We Preach Christ </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>(Flame speaking). Yeah. I got a couple of questions for you real quick. I want you to think on these questions, man</segment1>
		<segment2>Verse 1: If you were dyin of thirst. and I offered you some water to drink. how hard would you think. before you fought to grab my glass (you wouldn't think). but if I told you your sin stinks. but said you could still drink. my water if you turn from your past (then you'll think). and look to the present and. look to the Father through Jesus Christ. would you still want a sip of my water (ask yourself). or would you die dehydrate. because of your mind state. dont wanna just leave your sins on the altar. listen. I found that cats do wanna be saved. but we wanna be saved from our consequences (that's what we want, man). cause we play in our sin. cause we stay in our sin. so I pray how can I convince this (what can I say, Lord?). generation of men. generation of women. that we sinners in need of a transplant. in the heart I mean. cause its dark Hakeem. naw I mean would you please understand that</segment2>
		<segment3>Hook: We preach Christ. in His fullness, dawg. in His fury and endless love. Seek Him now you can know Him as Savior. Seek Him later youll know Him as Judge (repeat Hook)</segment3>
		<segment4>Verse 2: If you were starvin to death. and I came to your house with a meal. how long would you chill. before you fought to grab my food (not long). but if I told you your sin stinks. but said you could still eat. my meat if you turn to His truths (question). or would you starve and die. would you crawl and cry. cause you really love cars and shoes (think about that, man). or would you kill your pride. and then spill to God. my sin natures got me singin the blues. listen. I know young dudes who hate to live. I know girls who know where their rapists live (now that's pressure). and they hate this life and wont take to Christ. so they keep tryin to escape with pills. this is real thats why I preach with passion. cause my cousins Nick, Dennis, and Galisha is askin (what they askin' man?). Am I weak if I dont run the streets and look neat in my sneaks and expensive fashion? </segment4>
		<segment5>Hook</segment5>
		<segment6>Verse 3: If you were born in sin. and the Father sent His beloved Son. would you surrender to Him. or would you stay on the run (we're born sinners). or would you stick with your block. listenin to the rock. speak slop just to chief with your duns. listen. your whole life is like a walkin abortion. you aint even had a chance to live (you aint even had a chance to live ). I got fam man Thisl and J-son. if not me listen to my mans and nem (if not me listen to my mans and nem). we certified teachin people. who aint scared of God call us evangelists (call us evangelists, man). until we die preachin that Jesus is God. please listen to our stanzas kid yo</segment6>
		<segment7>Hook    </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
