<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>We Shot The Moon </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>How do you plead?. I know you know everything, I know you saw everything. And the person that you want to be is me, And the person that you want to be is me.</segment1>
		<segment2>It's self determination, And you should have noticed that by now. Our time is running out, And you can't believe..</segment2>
		<segment3>We walk like dead men. Our killer instinct,</segment3>
		<segment4>Wrapped in a smile, This will not end well.</segment4>
		<segment5>We shot the moon, we shot the moon, And we will take it in stride, If we should lose, if we should lose, At least we gave it a try.</segment5>
		<segment6>We shot the moon, we shot the moon, And we will take it in stride, If we should lose, if we should lose, At least we gave it a try.</segment6>
		<segment7>How do you plead?</segment7>
		<segment8>I know you know everything, I know you saw everything. By all means go and make the headlines scream, By all means go and make the headlines scream. You lack compassion, You lack the things that we all need, And much worse than it seems, You can't believe..</segment8>
		<segment9>We walk like dead men. Our killer instinct, Wrapped in a smile,</segment9>
		<segment10>This will not end well.</segment10>
		<segment11>We shot the moon, we shot the moon, And we will take it in stride, If we should lose, if we should lose, At least we gave it a try.</segment11>
		<segment12>We shot the moon, we shot the moon, And we will take it in stride, If we should lose, if we should lose, At least we gave it a try.</segment12>
		<segment13>You lack compassion,</segment13>
		<segment14>You lack the things that we all need, And much worse than it seems, You can't believe..</segment14>
		<segment15>We shot the moon, we shot the moon, And we will take it in stride,</segment15>
		<segment16>If we should lose, if we should lose, At least we gave it a try. We shot the moon, we shot the moon, And we will take it in stride, If we should lose, if we should lose,</segment16>
		<segment17>At least we gave it a try.    </segment17>
	</english>
</song>
