<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>West Coast Kid </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>INTRO. (paul). yo i'm a west coast kid livin in nashville. (toby). and i'm a east coast kid livin in nashville. yo i'm a west coast kid. and i'm a east coast kid. yo i'm a west coast east coast west coast east coast</segment1>
		<segment2>VERSE 1. yo i'm a west coast kid livin in nashville. moved here in the summer when i got my record deal. plan to make a mill but i've only sold a thousand. so i relocated to low income housing. i'm all about singing the blues take a walk in my shoes. you can see my point of view. country folk on the back porch pickin banjos. grams and gramps are bustin a move with the dosey doe's</segment2>
		<segment3>CHORUS. it's all hip-hop to me yea (it's all hip hop to me it's all hip-hop to me). it's all hip-hop to me alright (it's all hip-hop to me it's all hip-hop to me). it's all hip-hop to me i'm a grab my guitar( it's all hip hop to me it's all hip-hop to me). it's all hip-hop to me so tight (it's all hip hop to me it's all hip-hop to me)</segment3>
		<segment4>VERSE 2. (paul). and i'm a grab my guitar and play you this song. and all the people come on now and sing along. west coast kid living in nashville moved here in the summer when i got my. record deal. (tobymac). and i'm a east coast kid livin in nashville moved here in the winter when i. got my record deal. started with some vynil and a mic in dc. suburban little punk with an urban degree. i'm all about makin some noise and givin people a choice. long as i'm hearin god's voice. all my folk on the back porch tru, me and moses. mandy, marley ain't it sweet how it grows us</segment4>
		<segment5>CHORUS. VERSE 3. my mother used to sing me rhymes (sing me rhymes) when she put me to sleep. (c'mon). i wonder if she realized she was sowing seeds (sowing seeds). and now there growing growin growing to the sky (to the sky). and now i'm flowin flowing (flowin) flowing on this mic. it's all hip-hop to me. BRIDGE. what you want what you want what you want what you want what you need. it's all hip-hop to me. what you want what you want what you want what you want what you need. (paul). yo i'm a west coast kid livin in nashville. (tobymac). and i'm a east coast kid livin in nashville. (paul). moved here in the summer when i got my record deal. (tobymac). moved here in the winter when i got my record deal</segment5>
		<segment6>CHORUS. BGV CHORUS. free your mind and free your soul listen to the rhyme in stereo. turn the music up so that you can hear a sweet sound coming down loud and clear. make a simple melody and we lay it down put it all together make a brand new sound. maybe it's a symphony or maybe just a melody it really doesn't matter cuz</segment6>
		<segment7>CHORUS. OUTRO. (paul). i'm a west coast kid living in nashville moved here in the summer when i got my record deal / he's a /. (tobymac)east coast kid living in nashville moved here in the winter when i got my record deal. (paul). i'm a west coast kid living in nashville moved here in the summer when i got my record deal / he's a /. (tobymac)east coast kid living in nashville moved here in the winter when i got my record deal. (paul). i'm a west coast kid living in nashville moved here in the summer when i got my record deal / he's a /. (tobymac)east coast kid living in nashville moved here in the winter when i got my record deal. (paul). i'm a west coast kid living in nashville moved here in the summer when i got my record deal / he's a /. (tobymac)east coast kid living in nashville moved here in the winter when i got my record deal.     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
