<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>What About The Love </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I went to see my sister. She was staying with a friend. Who had turned into a preacher. To save the world from sin. He said, &quot;first deny your body, And then learn to submit. Pray to be made worthy, And tithe your ten percent.&quot;. I said, &quot;is this all there is, Just the letter of the law? &quot;. Something's wrong.</segment1>
		<segment2>I went to see my brother. On the 32nd floor. Of a building down on wall street;. You could hear the future's roar. He said, &quot;here we make decisions, And we trade commodities;. If you tell me where there's famine, I can make you guarantees.&quot;. I said, &quot;is this all there is, Power to the strong? &quot;. Something's wrong.</segment2>
		<segment3>Something's wrong in heaven tonight. You can almost hear them cry. Angels to the left and the right, Saying, &quot;what about the love?. What about the love?. What about the love? &quot;</segment3>
		<segment4>I went to see my neighbor. He'd been taken to a home. For the weak and the discarded. Who have no place to go. He said, &quot;here I lack for nothing;. I am fed and I am clothed. But at times I miss the freedom. I used to know.&quot;. I said, &quot;is this all there is, When your usefulness is gone? &quot;. Something's wrong.</segment4>
		<segment5>Something's wrong in heaven tonight. (something's wrong.). You can almost hear them cry. (cry.). Angels to the left and the right, Saying, &quot;what about the love?. What about the love?. What about the love? &quot;</segment5>
		<segment6>(yeah, yeah, yeah..)</segment6>
		<segment7>(yeah.)</segment7>
		<segment8>(yeah.)</segment8>
		<segment9>I looked into the mirror, (yeah.). Proud as I could be, (yeah.). And I saw my pointing finger (yeah.). Pointing back at me, Saying, &quot;who named you accuser? (yeah.). Who gave you the scales? &quot; (yeah.). I hung my head in sorrow; (yeah.). I could almost feel the nails. I said, &quot;this is how it is. To be crucified and judged. Without love.&quot;</segment9>
		<segment10>Something's wrong in heaven tonight. (something's wrong.). You can almost hear them cry. (cry.). Angels to the left and the right, Saying, &quot;what about the love?. What about the love?. What about the love of god? &quot;</segment10>
		<segment11>Something's wrong in heaven tonight. (something's wrong.). You can almost hear them cry. (cry.). Angels to the left and the right, Saying, &quot;what about the love? &quot;. What about the love?. What about the love of god? &quot;</segment11>
		<segment12>Something's wrong in heaven tonight. (something's wrong.). You can almost hear them cry. (cry.). Angels to the left and the right, Saying, &quot;what about the love?. What about the love?. What about the love..? &quot;    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
