<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>What If We Were Real </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Well, I'm tired of saying everything. I feel like I'm supposed to say. I'm tired of smiling all the time. I wanna throw the mask away. Sometimes you just have a bad day. Sometimes you just wanna scream. Tell me I'm not the only one. Tell me that you feel just like me</segment1>
		<segment2>We keep tryin to make it look so nice. And we keep hidin' what's goin on inside. But what if I share my brokenness. What if you share how you feel. And what if we weren't afraid of this crazy mess</segment2>
		<segment3>What if we were real. What if we were real</segment3>
		<segment4>I'm over hidin my tears. I think I'm gonna let em' go. I'm over actin so strong. When I ain't even in control. We make it so complicated. But why does it have to be. Why can't we open our hearts and let everybody see</segment4>
		<segment5>We keep tryin to make it look so nice. And we keep hidin' what's goin on inside. But what if I share my brokenness. What if you share how you feel. And what if we weren't afraid of this crazy mess</segment5>
		<segment6>What if we were real</segment6>
		<segment7>We'd think a little less of ourselves. We'd care about someone else. 'Cause we'd know just how they feel. Maybe we could let someone love us. Maybe we'd a little more like Jesus. Why can't we learn to real</segment7>
		<segment8>Na, na, na, na, na, na, na (yeah, yeah). Na, na, na, na, na, na, na</segment8>
		<segment9>We keep tryin to make it look so nice. And we keep hidin' what's goin on inside. But what if I share my brokenness. What if you share how you feel. And what if we weren't afraid of this crazy mess</segment9>
		<segment10>What if we were real</segment10>
		<segment11>You've got to be real. You've got to be real. You've got to be real. You've got to. You've got to</segment11>
		<segment12>Na, na, na, na, na, na, na. Na, na, na, na, na..    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
