<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>What Do We Know? </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Pick up the phone, nobody's home, I'm all alone, We've all been here before, But yesterday, I saw a change, another way, As you walked out the door. It's a twist, a little bit, I'll admit, But we're stronger than before, Open up, we've had enough, we've had enough, Now we're holdin' on,.and waiting</segment1>
		<segment2>What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. I'll tell you what they're all sayin' (X2)</segment2>
		<segment3>We all try to be somebody, but the world around us. Makes it so cloudy, when, We all trust where we're supposed to, but the blood on. Their Hands says we're not close to, the answer yet. But maybe if we pulled together, we could change. A million lives for the better, And maybe, if we prayed a little more, we would stop, Living in fear from the storm. And everyone sings</segment3>
		<segment4>What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. I'll tell you what they're all sayin' (X2). ..Tell you what they're all sayin'</segment4>
		<segment5>Bridge. Every part is you, every part is me, Raise your hands and sing, Tell them we can be. Show them who you are, Show them you can see, Raise your hands and sing, Tell them we are free </segment5>
		<segment6>What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. I'll tell you what they're all sayin' (X3)</segment6>
		<segment7>Every part is you, every part is me, Raise your hands and sing, Tell them we can be. Show them who you are, Show them you can see, Raise your hands and sing, Tell them we are free </segment7>
		<segment8>What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. What do we know? What do we know?. I'll tell you what they're all sayin'    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
