<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>What Is Love?! </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I have to tell the truth. I have a weakness for women. In every state wherever I go. I know it isn't right I feel I'm barely swimming. And the waves keep on crashing down. After every show (Oh boy). And what am I to do now. Where the he** is my crew now. Supposed to be watching my back. But they're jibbing too. And here she stands before me. And I'm trying to ignore thee. Possible chance of doing wrong. And now I sing my song</segment1>
		<segment2>Chorus: What is love, and am I in it. I really like girl and I think I should. What I feel, is there something in it. Cause if not I'm wasting her time. And that's just not good</segment2>
		<segment3>I'm in the mall in Altadena. Looking through a new magazine. Takin' a little love test to see. If I'm even there. And now it's looking like I'm failing. And now I'm slowly inhaling. Is this issue of Sassy's for real. If so the next step's ill. And dude I'm way past confused now. What do I have to do now. Break up with the girl of my dreams. In the past made mistakes and. Regret every step so I say</segment3>
		<segment4>Chorus</segment4>
		<segment5>Bridge</segment5>
		<segment6>And if I don't know what to say. And I'm just standing there in a daze. Please don't walk away so soon. My lady this it might just bloom. And if I don't know what to say. And I'm still standing there in a daze. Please don't walk away from me. Cause I am trapped now set me free</segment6>
		<segment7>I have to tell the truth (n****). Right now I have a girlfriend (uh oh). And she'll probably break up with me. After hearing this song (it's like that). But what am I to do ( I don't know). I gotta share what I'm feeling (share it boy). Cause if I can't tell the truth. Then there's something wrong. So I still ask</segment7>
		<segment8>Chorus</segment8>
		<segment9>So I have to ask, So I have to ask. Da da dada, da da dadaadaa (repeat). I like you, I hate you. I want you, I love you. I like you, I hate you. I want you, I love you.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
