<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>When The Rocks Hit The Ground </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Verse 1. It felt just like a setup. Somehow I knew it was this time. I didn't really want to do it. Such a tug-o-war inside. But by now this was the routine. I became desensitized</segment1>
		<segment2>Pre-chorus. So here I go once again. To the sea of lust I dive</segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus 1. And then I'm thrown down on my knees. Brought to Jesus by enemies. They wait with stones to condemn me. And if I've never heard the sound of grace before. I heard it when the rocks hit the ground</segment3>
		<segment4>Verse 2. I know it's an old story. But in reality it's me. And the more and more I messed up. It became harder and harder to flee. But I knew I wasn't gettin' by. I knew I wouldn't go scott free</segment4>
		<segment5>Pre-chorus. But that's when I discovered Christ. And His endless love towards me</segment5>
		<segment6>Chorus 2. I had to fall down on my knees. I thank God for my enemies. They wait with stones to condemn me. If I've never heard the sound of grace before. I heard it when the rocks hit the ground</segment6>
		<segment7>Vamp. Let the rocks fall. Fall to the ground. Let your grace rain. Let grace rain down</segment7>
		<segment8>Repeat vamp</segment8>
		<segment9>Bridge. Thought it was over for me (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). Thought I was counted out (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). You loved me (Tenors). I thought I strayed too far (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). I thought you cut me out (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). You loved me (Tenors)</segment9>
		<segment10>Thought it was over for me (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). Thought I was counted out (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). You love (Tenors). Oh oh oh oh (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). Oh oh oh oh (Tenors). You did not condemn me (Sopranos &amp; Altos). You loved me (Tenors)</segment10>
		<segment11>Ending. I had to fall down on my knees. I thank God for my enemies. Those stones should have landed on me. And if I've never heard the sound of grace before. I heard it when the rocks hit the ground</segment11>
		<segment12>Copyright © Tye Tribbett    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
