<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>When Darkness Reigns </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>My failure is so evident. And I cannot hide the torment. Face first to the earth. Plagued by the earthly mindset. I cannot escape my basement. Face first to the earth. Hands around my neck. I might as well bow in shame. Overmatched, outwitted. Defeat is my only name. I believe everything you tell me. You've got me convinced I'm guilty. I'd better close my eyes and sleep. Runaway because tomorrow's a better day. But this is your hour when darkness reigns.. When darkness reign across the channels and mediums. I feel the loss. Face to face with the possible death of dreams. Mental purity fades to the obscene. Hence the search for another crutch. Another voidfill, another cane to serve as much. And we'll mourn for death of the bother lost. And we'll toast to the death of another farce. Have I lost the battle?. Have I lost the war?. Do I have what it takes to endure the setbacks, ignore the scars. You'd have me adopt that suicide. You'd have me succumb without reply. But you forgot the thousand deaths I've died. You'd have me continue this pace. You'd have me join your race. But that grave will be nothing but an empty space. Arise from the dead, O sleeper. Prepare for the battle cry. Because this is the hour when truth divides.. When truth divides it's done. Revive the sick, the surge of blood. Grab a torch and we'll light and burn. Ignite offensives to claim the loss of sight. Wipe the sleep form your eyes. Release the fate of soul demise. And it's clear for you to understand that the smoke will clear and fill the land. And now the claims are made. Downcast eyes accompany shame. The chaos amassed against will redirect to find a home anew. To face the depths.. You've lost my enemy. Now taste defeat. Now taste your own saliva. Because you'll never quench the heat. Arise from the dead and wake    </segment1>
	</english>
</song>
