<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>When The Tears Fall </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I've had questions, without answers. I've known sorrow, I have known pain. but there's one thing, that I'll cling to. You are faithful, Jesus You're true </segment1>
		<segment2>when hope is lost, I'll call You saviour. when pain surrounds, I'll call You healer. when silence falls, You'll be the song within my heart </segment2>
		<segment3>in the lone hour of my sorrow. through the darkest night of my soul. You surround me and sustain me. my defender, forevermore </segment3>
		<segment4>when hope is lost, I'll call You saviour. when pain surrounds, I'll call You healer. when silence falls, You'll be the song within my heart </segment4>
		<segment5>and I will praise You, I will praise You. when the tears fall, still I will sing to You. and I will praise You, Jesus praise You. through the suffering still I will sing </segment5>
		<segment6>when hope is lost, I'll call You saviour. when pain surrounds, I'll call You healer. when silence falls, You'll be the song within my heart </segment6>
		<segment7>oh yes, You are good to me. You've always been good to me. so trustworthy </segment7>
		<segment8>when hope is lost, I'll call You saviour. when pain surrounds, I'll call You healer. when silence falls, You'll be the song within my heart </segment8>
		<segment9>and I will praise You, and I will praise You. when the tears fall, still I will sing to You (I will sing to You). I will praise You, Jesus praise You. through the suffering still I will sing </segment9>
		<segment10>how faithful and true. sustain me through and through. You are hope and truth. You must bring a little water. You must bring a little water </segment10>
		<segment11>in the lone hour of my sorrow </segment11>
		<segment12>who springs never fail. be faithful and true. like.. like a spring it never fails. you're my spring never fails    </segment12>
	</english>
</song>
