<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>When The Boys Light Up </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>When the boys light up, light up. When the boys light up, light up. When the boys light up, light up</segment1>
		<segment2>Back and forth like a daytime drama. Up and down like a yo-yo mama. Say there's gonna be days like this. Cause light and dark don't coexist</segment2>
		<segment3>How ya gonna see through this fog. How ya gonna get back on course. Ya ain't never gonna feel the force. If ya don't connect to a power source. Cause ya been swapping out day for night. But ya see a lamp light burning bright. If ya get your flip-flops off the porch. We're passing you the torch</segment3>
		<segment4>When the boys light up, ya know. Who gets the praise who owns the show. When the boys light up, it's on. We ain't stopping till we're done. We ain't nothing but the conduits. He's got the power, He'll flip the switch. Leaving the dark behind. Light up and let it shine</segment4>
		<segment5>When the boys light up, light up. When the boys light up, light up</segment5>
		<segment6>I was feeling all overcome. Had a faith gone dim and then some. Gotta call from a band of brothers. Turn the mic on, flash the Nikons. All the doubters, I heard them say, Now the band's gonna fade away. But the boys are back for a second act. No excuses, we're lighting fuses. You're in the dawn of your finest hour. So get wired to the highest power. If you're down pick any sight. Get ready to ignite</segment6>
		<segment7>When the boys light up, ya know. Who gets the praise who owns the show. When the boys light up, it's on. We ain't stopping till we're done. If we ain't nothing but the conduits. He's got the power, He'll flip the switch. Leaving the dark behind. Light up and let it shine</segment7>
		<segment8>When we walk in His footsteps. It's a brighter day. When we follow His word. He lights the way. When we lift up His banner. And raise it high. We light up the sky</segment8>
		<segment9>When the boys light up, light up. When the boys light up, light up</segment9>
		<segment10>When the boys light up, ya know. Who gets the praise who owns the show. When the boys light up, it's on. We ain't stopping till we're done. If we ain't nothing but the conduits. He's got the power, He'll flip the switch. Leaving the dark behind</segment10>
		<segment11>When the boys light up, ya know. Who gets the praise who owns the show. When the boys light up, it's on. We ain't stopping till we're done. If we ain't nothing but the conduits. He's got the power, He'll flip the switch. Leaving the dark behind. Light up and let it shine    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
