<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Who Needs Air </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I long to taste adventure like the nature of the sea, Always moving, always hiding all the creatures from beneath. Singing silent songs of sadness my heart waits for its chance, To dance upon the ashes of my burned up little plans.</segment1>
		<segment2>And I stand alone before the night. My nakedness is so clear in the glow of the moonlight. Life is old but so short. We are young we want more.</segment2>
		<segment3>I'm drowning, but I don't care, Because when you got what I got, what I got, what I got. Who needs air?. I don't need air.</segment3>
		<segment4>My addiction to danger like the rush of the sea, Like a wave on the rocks the lessons crash down on me. I don't need to prove the world to you only to myself. So step back and look away as I dive into this well.</segment4>
		<segment5>I'm drowning, but I don't care, Because when you got what I got, what I got, what I got. Who needs air?</segment5>
		<segment6>So take me down to the river like a little child, and take my hand and tell me it's ok to be wild, I never knew the world until I saw it through your eyes, I never knew myself until I ripped off my disguise (I ripped off my disguise)</segment6>
		<segment7>I'm drowning, but I don't care, Because when you got what I got, what I got, what I got. who needs air?</segment7>
		<segment8>I'm drowning, but I don't care, Because when you've got what I got, what I got, what I got. You don't need air. (x2). [in the background](I have come to the realization that life is more than what I have accomplished. And life is more then the realization that we have accomplished nothing at all. True success is so selfless so drown in the lyrics of your life. and give up the air that you breathe. You don't need anything. You don't need anything)</segment8>
		<segment9>I don't need air.     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
