<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Who Would've Thought... [Live] </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Heard folks talk about the things You'd done. And I would just laugh at what they'd say. Who would've thought, in time, that I would be the one?. Who would've thought. that I'd get to know You this way?. Who would've thought. I'd know you this way?. I'd know you this way? </segment1>
		<segment2>Just like a shining light. from out of the blue. Before I could waste my life away. You came and took my life, made it brand new, Yes you did!. Who would've thought. I'd get to know You this way?. Who would've thought. I'd know You this way? </segment2>
		<segment3>I know You ,Lord, since You've entered in. I can't believe the things You've done. You came and saved me. changed me and forgave me. Then You took me in as one of Your own </segment3>
		<segment4>Now when I feel my world is falling apart, (Oh yeah). I can just bend my knees and pray. (You know what?). Feels so good to feel this love in my heart. Who would've thought I'd get to know You this way?. Who would've thought I'd know You this way? </segment4>
		<segment5>I know You ,Lord, since You've entered in. I can't believe the things You've done. You came and saved me, changed me and forgave me. Then You took me in as one of Your own </segment5>
		<segment6>Now when I feel my world is falling apart, (Oh yeah). I can just bend my knees and pray. (You know what?). Feels so good to feel this love in my heart. Who would've thought. I'd get to know You this way?. Who would've thought. I'd know You this way? This way?. I got to know you I got to know you. I got to know you I got to know you this way. (Repeat) </segment6>
		<segment7>Got to know you in a better way. I got to know you in a better way. I got to know you in a better way. I thought I knew you on yesterday, But I got to know you in a better way. I thought I knew you on yesterday, I got to know you in a better way. I got to know you I got to know you. I got to know you. I got to know you this way (Repeat)     </segment7>
	</english>
</song>
