<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Why Do I Do </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Why do I do the things I do. Sometimes I feel like I am so insecure. If I could learn a thing or two from you. Then popular opinion I could ignore </segment1>
		<segment2>You are enough for me. I don't need anything but you(ya). You are enough for me. And I don't need anything </segment2>
		<segment3>Chorus: Cause you have given me more that I can ask for. More that I can ever imagine. And you keep giving me love you keep on lifting me up. It doesn't get any better </segment3>
		<segment4>Why do I do the things I do. Thought everyday is showing me something new. I need to slow down need to learn from you. Cause your the only one I should listen to </segment4>
		<segment5>You are enough for me. I don't need anything but you(ya). You are enough for me. And I don't need anything </segment5>
		<segment6>Chorus: Cause you have given me more that I can ask for. More that I can ever imagine. And you keep giving me love you keep on lifting me up. It doesn't get any better </segment6>
		<segment7>Lord you show me how. To do it life as it comes around. Even when I'm down. I can count on you to help me stand my ground </segment7>
		<segment8>Cause you have given me more that I could ask for. More than I could ever imagine. And you keep giving me love you keep on lifting me up. It doesn't get any better </segment8>
		<segment9>Cause you have given me more that I could ask for. More than I could ever imagine. And you keep giving me love you keep on lifting me up. It doesn't get any better </segment9>
		<segment10>you keep giving me love. you keep lifting me up. you keep giving me love. you keep lifting me up. you keep giving me love. you keep lifting me up. you keep giving me love. you keep lifting me up (fades).     </segment10>
	</english>
</song>
