<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Wit's All Been Done Before </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I wish I could, innovate, And try to stretch your minds, Cause when often, times guys like me, Do that they leave themselves behind, To clean the mess, or to impress, A little bit of everyone, But to innovate, is a mistake, Cause there's nothing new under the sun.</segment1>
		<segment2>Cause we're all getting tired of the media, Cause they tries to hard to make you write something, Cause we're all getting tired of the media, Cause creating something new just recycling, Wait wit's all been done before, Yeah we do something to death, Then we dig it up just to do it some more.</segment2>
		<segment3>And all my lines are pointing signs, But not all with dead ends, And im not sure if the clever words, All sit well with my friends, I will not just sit and watch, And me the victim fall, I'll just have to do, What my gut tells me to, And hope that you will buy it all.</segment3>
		<segment4>Cause we're all getting tired of the media, Cause they tries to hard to make you write something, Cause we're all getting tired of the media, Cause creating something new just recycling, Wait Wit's all been done before, Yeah we do something to death, Then we dig it up just to do it some more, Wait wit's all been done before, Yeah we do something to death, Then we dig it up just to do it some more.</segment4>
		<segment5>Originality is a ghost town, And it's oh so hard to get to, And when you do, then people start to hate you, Just scream what you belive out loud in a crowd, People will hate you, Cause repitition's just so safe, And repition is just like prison, And I prefer to be out of place, Cause I'm not really into prison.</segment5>
		<segment6>Wait wit's all been done before, Yeah we do something to death, Then we dig it up just to do it some more, Wait wit's all been done before, Yeah we do something to death, Then we dig it up just to do it some more, Cause we're all getting tired of the media, Cause they try to hard to make you write something, Cause we're all getting tired of the media, Cause creating something new just recycling, Wait Wit's all been done before, Yeah we do something to death, Then we dig it up just to do it some more, Wait wit's all been done before, Yeah we do something to death, Then we dig it up just to do it some more.    </segment6>
	</english>
</song>
