<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Word </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I solve math problems at my senior high. We got a hundred things we gotta read and write. There ain't no gangs like Grease and no cool cars. It's hard to be real wild, but we can teach you the art. It's in the Word</segment1>
		<segment2>They think our Lord is just a ball and chain. Why don't they understand it's just their pride and shame. They live for science, only He is real. Just got to find right now the God that Jesus revealed. Jesus' the Word</segment2>
		<segment3>Jesus' the Word, He's the Word, as you've heard. We've got proof, it's got Spirit. He is the life, He's the Way, He's the Logos. Now these things we base on experience</segment3>
		<segment4>He came a-blessin' and He chose to stay. Condemned at Calvary, rose on that blessed third day. There is a choice that we can make if we're smart. We start believing now and He can redo our hearts. Receive the Word</segment4>
		<segment5>Jesus' the Word, yes the Word, as you've heard. It's not rules, it's not teasing. Jesus the Christ is the face of the most high. Now this is the day to receive Him</segment5>
		<segment6>They say it mocks evolution. That's just a subtle envious excuse. What are we doin' here?</segment6>
		<segment7>We make confession and he shows us the way. No technicalities, no long-term debts to pay. There is a plan so we get saved from above. Let's start to read it now it's in Ephesians, you all. Faith is the Word</segment7>
		<segment8>Faith is a word that's conferred undeserving. It's not you, it's not me then. Grace is divine, it's through faith, there's no boastin'. Now read in 2:8 in Ephesians</segment8>
		<segment9>So search the Word, yes the Word, that you've heard. It's got truth, it's God's teaching. This is the time, it's the place, it's the moment. Now Jesus is waiting, receive Him </segment9>
		<segment10>Jesus' the Word. Yes the Word (x 9)</segment10>
		<segment11>Ephesians 2:8 For it is by grace you have been saved, through faith - and this not from yourselves, it is the gift of God.     </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
