<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Write My Song </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>(Chorus). Your my Savior,your the lover of my soul. Write my song, Please Lord, Write my song</segment1>
		<segment2>My creator, Your the one who makes me whole, Write my song. Mystro write my song.</segment2>
		<segment3>(Verse 1). I was sitting here thinking of the possibilities, If my life was a song, Then what would be the melody, God could you sing it to me, Think I know some of the lyrics. Would you like to hear it, Although its not finished, I have yet to live it, Could you help me through this.</segment3>
		<segment4>(Chorus). Your my Savior, Your the lover of my soul. Write my song, Please Lord, Write my song</segment4>
		<segment5>My creator, Your the one who makes me whole, Write my song. Mystro write my song.</segment5>
		<segment6>Verse 2. My life was lean on black and white. Just like the piano keys, I want you to play me, So that you get the glory, Whatever you do is pleasing to me. Now play my song like your pretty strings. My heart be your temponaies, And one last thing for thee, Let it be a beautiful symphony. (yeah)f illed with pretty harmony.</segment6>
		<segment7>(Chorus). Your my Savior, Your the lover of my soul. Write my song, Please Lord, Write my song</segment7>
		<segment8>My creator, Your the one who makes me whole, Write my song. Mystro write my song.</segment8>
		<segment9>(Vamp). Now it could be. It could be a palet filled with encouragement</segment9>
		<segment10>Or it could be. Or it could be a song of praise telling the world how you made a way</segment10>
		<segment11>Or it could be. Or it could be simple hymn telling the sentlement come in revenge</segment11>
		<segment12>Better yet make it worship,cause I know my purpose, Purpose</segment12>
		<segment13>Let the sound you hear,be pleasing to your ear</segment13>
		<segment14>(Chorus). Your my Savior, Your the lover of my soul. Write my song, Please Lord, Write my song</segment14>
		<segment15>My creator, Your the one who makes me whole, Write my song. Mystro write my song.    </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
