<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>You Are My Strength </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>. I don't know. I don't know. Don't know</segment1>
		<segment2>It seem like I had to lose in order to win. And when they walked out on me, it's when Your love came in. And when I feel like dyin', You made me feel better. You took me by the hand. You told me we could make it through this together</segment2>
		<segment3>You were my strength, You were my strength. When I was exhausted. You were my strength, You were my strength. You were my strength, helped me climb the mountain</segment3>
		<segment4>You were my. My body, my sword, my shield, my joy, my life. Your love so real. You were my strength, You were my strength. You were my</segment4>
		<segment5>It's amazin' to me when I look back and see, whoa, whoa. How I made it over, then I thought it was over. And when my heart was shattered into a million pieces. Your love put me back together again. You know just what I needed</segment5>
		<segment6>You were my strength, You were my strength. When I was exhausted. You were my strength, You were my strength. You were my strength, you put me by the mountain</segment6>
		<segment7>You were my. My heart, my sword, my shield, my joy, my life. Your love so real. You were my strength, You were my strength. You were my</segment7>
		<segment8>That is why I love You. That is why I love You. Took me back is why I love You. That is why I love You</segment8>
		<segment9>You were my strength, You were my strength. When I was exhausted, yeah. You were my strength, You were my strength. You were my strength, helped me climb the mountain</segment9>
		<segment10>You were my. My body, my soul, my shield, my joy, my life. Your love so real. You were my strength, You were my strength. You were my</segment10>
		<segment11>You were my strength. You were my strength when I was exhausted. You were my strength. You were my strength, helped me climb the mountain</segment11>
		<segment12>That is why I love You. That is why I love You. Took me back that is why I love You. That is why I love</segment12>
		<segment13>You were my strength. You were my strength. I would never forget how You were</segment13>
		<segment14>You were my strength. You were my strength. You were my strength. You were my strength</segment14>
		<segment15>You were my. My heart, my soul, my shield, my joy, my life. Your love so real. You were my strength, You were my strength. You were my.     </segment15>
	</english>
</song>
