<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>You Get Me </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Wonderful </segment1>
		<segment2>Is what I percieved. This life would be. Pain and problem free. But over time. I found reality. And through it all I see. That you're the only one who gets me </segment2>
		<segment3>I may be missunderstood 'cause I wouldn't ever fake it. You're the only one who understands my pain. Cause you get me. Doesn't matter what they do what they think what they say. At the end of the day I'm okay anyway. 'cause LORD you get me </segment3>
		<segment4>No more tears. It's a silent night. You're broken down on fear. 'cause you remain in all of me. You know me better than I know myself. The key to my security. There is no one else who gets me </segment4>
		<segment5>I may be missunderstood 'cause I wouldn't ever fake it. You're the only one who understands my pain. 'cause you get me. Doesn't matter what they do what they think what they say. At the end of the day I'm okay anyway. 'cause LORD you get me </segment5>
		<segment6>I don't care what the world may say. I hear you calling my name. And I reach for you reach for you. There is nothing that I'd rather do. Than just worship you, LORD. I'm going to worship you. Worship you </segment6>
		<segment7>I'm okay [4 times]. Yeah. I'm okay [6 times]. Yeah. I'm okay I'm okay. Yeah. I'm okay [4 times] </segment7>
		<segment8>I may be missunderstood 'cause I wouldn't ever fake it. You're the only one who understands my pain. 'cause you get me. Doesn't matter what they do what they think what they say. At the end of the day I'm ok anyway. 'cause LORD you get me </segment8>
		<segment9>I may be missunderstood 'cause I wouldn't ever fake it. You're the only one who understands my pain. 'cause you get me. Doesn't matter what they do what they think what they say. At the end of the day I'm ok anyway. 'cause LORD you get me </segment9>
		<segment10>I'm okay [4 times]. Yeah. I'm okay [6 times]. Yeah. I'm okay [2 times]. Yeah. I'm okay [4 times] </segment10>
		<segment11>You understand me. So completely. Now I am free. LORD you get me. [repeat]    </segment11>
	</english>
</song>
