<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Younglife </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Hey brother, do you remember when. We used to play outdoors. Til the light was absorbed by the night?. Hey brother, it was a nicer time. We used to laugh til we cry. We're still boys on the inside. (I want to do it again) </segment1>
		<segment2>The first time staying out all night. The last that we got away with lies. I can hear it in the back of my mind. Over and over again. (I want to do it again). Late nights and early lights. Never thought it would come to a goodbye. I replay it in the back of my mind. Over and over again. (I want to do it again) </segment2>
		<segment3>Lala la, lala la la la. Lala la la la. (I want to do it again) </segment3>
		<segment4>Hey lover, do you remember when. We would dance in your apartment. Til neighbors would knock on your door?. And I remember, you remember when. We had no money to speak of. No where else to eat but your floor. (I want to do it again) </segment4>
		<segment5>The first time staying out all night. The last time you look me in the eyes. I can see that in the back of my mind. Over and over again. (I want to do it again). Late nights, all entwined. Made a promise to never say goodbye. I replay in the back of my mind. Over and over again </segment5>
		<segment6>All those days gone forever. Wonder if we're going to ever. See all our younglife friends that we made again. Have we all lost connection?. The life pulls in all direction. Memories bring us back to where we've been </segment6>
		<segment7>(I want to do it again) </segment7>
		<segment8>The first time staying out all night. The last time that we got away with lies. We can hear it in the back of our minds. Over and over again. (I want to do it again). Late nights and early lights. Never thought it would come to a goodbye. We replay it in the back of our minds. Over and over and over. (I want to do it again) </segment8>
		<segment9>Lala la la, lala la la la. Lala la la la. (I want to do it again). (Repeat until ending).     </segment9>
	</english>
</song>
