<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Your Love </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>I felt it first when I was younger. A strange connection to the light. I tried to satisfy the hunger. I never got it right. I never got it right</segment1>
		<segment2>So I climbed a mountain and l built an altar. Looked out as far as I could see. And everyday Im getting older. Im running outta dreams. Im running outta dreams</segment2>
		<segment3>But Your love. Your love. The only the thing that matters is Your love. Your love is all I have to give. Your love is enough to light up the darkness. Its Your love. Your love. all I ever needed is Your love</segment3>
		<segment4>You know the effort I have given. And you know exactly what it cost. And though my innocence was taken. Not everything is lost. Not everything is lost nooooo</segment4>
		<segment5>But Your love. Your love. The only the thing that matters is Your love. Your love is all I have to give. Your love is enough to light up the darkness. Its Your love. Your love. all I ever needed is Your love</segment5>
		<segment6>Youre the hope in the morning. Youre the light when the night is falling. Youre the song when my heart is singing. its Your love. Youre the eyes to the blind man. Youre the feet to the lame man walking. Youre the sound of the people singing. Its Your love</segment6>
		<segment7>But Your love. Your love. The only the thing that matters is Your love. Your love is all I have to give. Your love is enough to light up the darkness. Its Your love. Your love. all I ever needed is Your love</segment7>
		<segment8>But Your love. (Your love is all that I needed). The only the thing that matters is Your love. Your love is all I have to give. Your love is enough to light up the darkness. (Your love is all that I needed). Its Your love. Your love. Its all I ever needed     </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
