<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>You're Beautiful </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Down A Cold And Darkened Hallway. a Doctor Stood Alone, with A Young And Frightened Father. who Knew Something Was Wrong. he Said, Son This Isn't Easy. but We Really Need To Talk. so He Put His Arm Around Him. and They Began To Walk.</segment1>
		<segment2>he Said Your Wife Is Finally Sleeping. she Just Needs To Be Alone Right Now. and Your Baby, Well She's Healthy, but There's Something You Should Know. son, She's Slightly Less Than Perfect, and There's Nothing We Could Do. so Before You Go To See Her, i Thought I'd Talk To You.</segment2>
		<segment3>as The Young Man Held The Warm, and Sleeping Bundle To His Chest, he Saw The Imperfections, and Although He Tried His Best, he Couldn't Stop The Tears From Falling, as He Held His Little Girl. and In A Low And Trembling Voice, he Gently Said These Words;</segment3>
		<segment4>you're Beautiful In Every Way, So Beautiful. how I've Waited For This Day. if The World Was Offered To Me, i Just Couldn't Make The Trade. cause You're Beautiful</segment4>
		<segment5>when I Think Of How I've Fallen, and All The Times I've Tried, to Hide My Imperfections, from My Father's Eyes. there's A Voice That Still Is Calling, deep Inside Of Me. and I Can Always Hear It. when I Get On My Knees.</segment5>
		<segment6>you're Beautiful In Every Way, So Beautiful. how I've Waited For This Day. when The World Was Offered To Me, i Just Couldn't Make The Trade. cause You're Beautiful. you'd Be Amazed At How Some Things Matter, and Some Things Don't, when You're Seen Through, the Eyes Of God. though We Try To Hide Our Darkness, and Fill Our Dreams, he Only Sees What's In Your Heart.</segment6>
		<segment7>and You're Beautiful, In Every Way, so Beautiful. how I've Waited For This Day. when The World Was Offered To Me, i Just Couldn't Make The Trade. cause You're Beautiful</segment7>
		<segment8>i Know God Knows, You're Beautiful. you're Beautiful.. you're Beautiful.. you're Beautiful.    </segment8>
	</english>
</song>
