<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>Youth of the Nation </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13,segment14,segment15,segment16,segment17,segment18,segment19,segment20,segment21,segment22</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Last day of the rest of my life. I wish I would've known. Cause I didn't kiss my mama goodbye </segment1>
		<segment2>I didn't tell her that I loved her and how much I care. Or thank my pops for all the talks. And all the wisdom he shared </segment2>
		<segment3>Unaware, I just did what I always do. Everyday, the same routine. Before I skate off to school </segment3>
		<segment4>But who knew that this day wasn't like the rest. Instead of taking a test. I took two to the chest </segment4>
		<segment5>Call me blind, but I didn't see it coming. Everybody was running. But I couldn't hear nothing </segment5>
		<segment6>Except gun blasts, it happened so fast. I don't really know this kid. Even though I sit by him in class </segment6>
		<segment7>Maybe this kid was reaching out for love. Or maybe for a moment. He forgot who he was. Or maybe this kid just wanted to be hugged. Whatever it was. I know it's because </segment7>
		<segment8>[chorus:]. We are, We are, the youth of the nation </segment8>
		<segment9>Little Suzy, she was only twelve. She was given the world. With every chance to excel </segment9>
		<segment10>Hang with the boys and hear the stories they tell. She might act kind of proud. But no respect for herself </segment10>
		<segment11>She finds love in all the wrong places. The same situations. Just different faces </segment11>
		<segment12>Changed up her pace since her daddy left her. Too bad he never told her. She deserved much better </segment12>
		<segment13>Johnny boy always played the fool. He broke all the rules. So you would think he was cool </segment13>
		<segment14>He was never really one of the guys. No matter how hard he tried. Often thought of suicide </segment14>
		<segment15>It's kind of hard when you ain't got no friends. He put his life to an end. They might remember him then </segment15>
		<segment16>You cross the line and there's no turning back. Told the world how he felt. With the sound of a gat </segment16>
		<segment17>[chorus]</segment17>
		<segment18>Who's to blame for the lives that tragedies claim. No matter what you say. It don't take away the pain </segment18>
		<segment19>That I feel inside, I'm tired of all the lies. Don't nobody know why. It's the blind leading the blind </segment19>
		<segment20>I guess that's the way the story goes. Will it ever make sense. Somebody's got to know </segment20>
		<segment21>There's got to be more to life than this. There's got to be more to everything. I thought exists </segment21>
		<segment22>[chorus]    </segment22>
	</english>
</song>
