<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<song>
	<thainame>none</thainame>
	<englishname>You Wanted It </englishname>
	<mienthainame>none</mienthainame>
	<order>segment1,segment2,segment3,segment4,segment5,segment6,segment7,segment8,segment9,segment10,segment11,segment12,segment13</order>
	<english>
		<segment1>Run you coward, you run. These words crippled my confidence. The hymn I can't escape from. This is over and done with. This race has made me more than weary, I am dead</segment1>
		<segment2>I created everything here that I wanted to see. So was that your plan, to leave me out?. We were all reciting messages and pushing repeat. But this world you made does it let you breath</segment2>
		<segment3>Does it let you feel anything but yourself?. When was the last time. Does it let you breathe?. Does it let you feel anything but yourself?. When was the last time you saw anyone else?</segment3>
		<segment4>Whispers and echoes of love fading. The plans you made, you wanted it. The bitter taste, you wanted it. What god became you wanted it. But the one thing you need you'll never get</segment4>
		<segment5>There was more of you and less of me. You blamed it on the chemistry. Can you close your eyes when you rest your head?. It didn't have to be this way but you wanted it</segment5>
		<segment6>They were just calendar days. I'm sure it's all written down. But if you'll let me just ask. Is this how you bring the crowd to their feet?. You hurt because it wasn't about you. About me?. You're always scared the floor is gonna give way. I call the shots. We could end this, we could end this. Don't you ever tell me what I've got</segment6>
		<segment7>Whispers and echoes of love fading. The plans you made, you wanted it. The bitter taste, you wanted it. What god became you wanted it. But the one thing you need you'll never get</segment7>
		<segment8>There was more of you and less of me. You blamed it on the chemistry. Can you close your eyes when you rest your head?. It didn't have to be this way but you wanted it. I wanted, I wanted, I wanted, I wanted this</segment8>
		<segment9>You made it such a lonely world. Such a very lonely world. You bent the answers into questions. You let the voice go unheard. And you couldn't trust yourself. Cause what if everything you felt. Meant this was not yours alone</segment9>
		<segment10>Every single word, every single little word that was said. And all the simple fears. And all the nights that you cried in your bed. Hoping I was there but you told yourself. You're old and alone. But you were never the widow you left on your own</segment10>
		<segment11>I was washed in the blood. I was born of a spirit but I drowned. When you found me out there. Rejoice, Rejoice the old King is dead. Long live the new king. I am the new king</segment11>
		<segment12>Whispers and echoes of love fading. The plans you made, you wanted it. The bitter taste, you wanted it. What god became you wanted it. But the one thing you need you'll never get</segment12>
		<segment13>There was more of you and less of me. You blamed it on the chemistry. Can you close your eyes when you rest your head?. It didn't have to be this way but you wanted it    </segment13>
	</english>
</song>
